Oh, sorry guys, he's so insane
Goodness gracious guy
Do you think I have the best mods
Hi guys, no one's here
We'll see. Oh gosh any shadow bami or something Alex. I mean Jesus
It's like yeah, it's like
He's messing with my channel doing that shit
So anyone that messes with my channel messing with me and my my cats and
The whole rest of the chat so
I hope they stop doing that.
Hi, everybody.
Yeah, crazy guy.
Happy 4th of July, guys.
Yeah, thank you for being here.
There's lots of places on YouTube to be,
but we're gonna have fun someday.
But yeah, it's been pretty crazy to see
all the stuff happening,
like all the,
Much of I got a bunch of videos. I made they got clips. That's it. They put a pretty really cool
other videos so I
Love having those kind of things out there. I'm gonna make sure I share all this today
Yeah, so other people are sorry don't want to do shows and stuff. I know but it's like he's so unfortunate. Yes, the big piece so
So rude to do that shit
Kind of like this reading. It's the clear good reading. I'm gonna watch this soon. It says your strange presence baffles people
I don't know. It says they
They know you're not normal
Thank you. Oh, no, you figure that out guys
Well
They're not normal. I'm not normal in a good way. I think
Hi
I think like the truly crazy is like where you're like you have like kind of an urge or I'm gonna
Negative urges and if you're like what if you've heard anybody else any other people
It's a people hurt their friends or enemies. It's like especially some of these toxic
Toxic personalities and there's a lot of them. It's just like rampant the media stick like people become sick
consuming like some of the entertainment and
You know chasing and people are blinded by materialism. They think that's that's what's real. It's just a very temporary
state very compared to like billions of years of our souls of illusion incarnate to millions of bodies and
Maybe even longer, you know, so I
Would you believe we've lived on this earth? I mean it's like the earth like life is just familiar to me
You know, but maybe it's just what I'm used to being here, but
Thank you for being here guys happy 4th of July. I don't know what it's cause a coffee place up maybe open at 7
You don't think they kind of do close a little bit. They pin my link on yeah, they close a little bit or open a little bit
Later and close a little bit early
So I'm trying to link up. Yeah, so I'm no Alice
Got on fire like he said like talking about us. Well, we weren't talking about him. He said he thinks
the same negative things that has like, oh, he was like, you know, kind of like
being weird talking to Paige like
How's it gonna sound like he's in love with her and stuff like
I mean, it's fine a lot of guys will I'm sure fall in love with Paige. She's a lovely person
Okay, how do I get my comments shit?
Sorry guys, let's slow this morning
Here we go, there's a live chat. Okay, link is 10
Okay, guys, how are we doing it? But it's I'm notice like not everyone's talking lately
They were not too many people it's been quiet like I know a lot of people other places right now
Thank you for coming in here. Let's see what's going on. We're just starting. We're just restarting. Yeah, I'm Alex
You know, I don't like
That kind of language or it's like so many rules broken at once first of all
it's disrespect to the guest which is this is respect for the host, right? Then it's also slander and it's also
You know about you know pretty discussed. It's just that the word he said that the worst way it was they are were I mean
Alex you insane really Alex
But I did get my kitchen clean last night. I got another step done. So let's see. I'm gonna find something
Share with you. What was I looking at? So we get some book
guys wanna
This is called, you know, confessions of an Illuminati by this guy named
Leo Tsankami, okay, this is about a bunch of different stuff
Let me see.
Here's about some initiation stuff
and some cool esoteric stuff, okay.
So,
okay, okay.
This is that if the theme of the descent into the underworld or more exactly the catabasis
Catabasis is certainly not new. There are many examples in various cultures since ancient times
It's sufficient to recall Hercules Pollux Orpheus for the Greeks the Babylonian Inanna the hero Hittite Kessie
Zolotol in Mexico the A&E's of the Latin or Dante in Italian literature
Jesus himself
would die and then rise again, so it's clear how the ability to go down to the underworld
before returning to the living is an expression of an ancestral need of human beings.
Of course, various myths and stories likely to give rise to different interpretations,
but at the same time they're always related to an ego-soul transformation, cathartic process,
or the idea of eternal life with the consequent defeat of death.
But as the same Galassia writes on his excellent essay of the subject, the concept of death
could take on various meanings, the end of it all as the last act of existence without
any possibility of extension, a simple transmutation through the migration of the soul until the
rebirth to a new life, a spiritual life that lasts for eternity.
I open the last volume of my trilogy with Plato's allegory of the cave and its two
I would like to present to you the correct interpretation of the most beautiful and famous
metaphor in Western philosophy thanks to my father, Dr. Ilyo Zagami.
Ilyo wrote about it in his unpublished essay entitled The Experience, where he states,
Socrates, after comparing our nature in regards to education or lack of education, described
the following picture of mankind in Book 7 of the Republic, where we find the famous
description of Plato's experience, perhaps among the most beautiful pages ever written,
undoubtedly among the most cited, although not equally understood.
It is a catabasis and later a mental rise with specific reference to various degrees
of initiation.
On the myth of Plato's cave contained in a work through public, I will attempt, with my father's help, a
cautious analysis and description in connection with the initiation rites of the time,
which have always been the basis of the Western initiatic tradition, and in this way
I hope to help you, my reader, understand the importance in the eyes of an illuminated master.
My father used to tell me that Plato is blamed by the Sicilian
Pythagoreans for having created an important allegory and put it into writing.
They were sort of forerunner to the mafia of today where they obviously wished to control such secret knowledge and monopolize it in order to
Facilitate their personal goals. They did not agree with Plato showing such truth outside certain initiatic circles in the hands of the elite
Blaming him for revealing to the masses the secrets related to the control of the matrix a bit like Jesus did
Elio writes, we call him Socrates, his teacher was punished and accused by his opponents of having aroused the youth protests
Which his disciple Plato still denied. Here we go again. We always want to save prisoners of the system. The truth scared
The mafia back then as it does today and Socrates was condemned to die by taking hemlock
Do not forget this becoming a guided unaliving. My father Elio Zygami also wrote
It is a descent into hell, which is already made by Ulysses in the A.N.S., Jesus and Dante,
made to meet with the thousand possible faces of ourselves.
It is the heart of the Platonic esoteric transmission, the place of ideas, the mental
point of constant reference of our civilization.
It is time then to reinterpret the myth or allegory of the cave in a modern way for it
Thinking you see men who have been trapped in there since they were children with chain legs and necks
so as they have been
So as to have them standing only able to see forward unable because of the chain to turn around their neck
Unable to see other levels of existence beyond their own the man enslaved only looking ahead
But in front of him there is nothing only shadows. There will never be a sun shining in the depths of the cave
We have become specialists of the dark
And now, we want to go to other planets, systems, galaxies, like we are able to move.
Well, we cannot truly move ourselves mentally from our present position.
We want to travel to the universe,
we travel to the universe to defeat nature,
confusing such things with reality.
We all want to be
Icarus high and far behind us shines the light of fire and between the fire or the prisoner rides the road along this road
You think you see a low wall built like a screen
It's a puppeteer put in front of people to show them the puppets and who are the puppets?
Masters of this reality. Hey Christine
Thank you for being back. I know I can't believe you crazy Alex. I mean fuck
But it says, if we look to the platonic metaphor, we must not overlook anything.
Dr. Ilyos Zagami urges us, and he continues his analysis by writing.
Man enslaved, tied, prisoner in the bottom of the cave is actually us, or at least most of us, so the question arises
Who are the puppeteers? Glaucon replies to the allegory of the cave
I see. At that time this meant here and see. Imagine seeing men carrying all along the low wall objects, all sorts protruding from the edge, statues.
and other figures of stone and wood crafted in all sorts of ways and as is
natural that some carriers talk and there's a silent in the process. So
Plato described to us in these allegory of the cave the power and men of power
who continually stun us with their ideology. Some of these men speak during
their work while others are silent. My father wrote that the silent ones are
the ones who rule the system.
They are the ones who lead or command humanity, linked to the bottom of the cave, which provides
to us a glimpse or projection of false things built for us, proposing this as the only possible
reality.
Even the sun, or the fire, in their eyes is constructed for them.
Perhaps cousins of Prometheus, they think they are so close to God as to believe they
know that God does not exist.
The world maneuvered out of their hands gives them vertigo and therefore they believe
From the glorious heights to be the gods of the world, but this is not the case
They are only a visible manifestation of the infinite loop chain of this prison planet
Some people talk and write in bombardous in so many ways in their own words
Public on political religious prophets psychologists critics others prefer to manage the power and silence never saying anything
Those are the businessmen
Easter terraces masons court of sands friends and friends of these
An excellent description of the allegory of the cave made by my father Ilio in his unpublished
essay written in the mid-70s, just as good a time superior to what we find in more recent
times.
In the movie The Matrix, a 1999 American-Australian science fiction action film written and directed
by the Wachowski brothers, a film that, as some of you know, is considered a great importance
to the initiatic process of the masses at this crucial time for humanity.
The film in question revolves around the opposition between real and fictional worlds, between
truth and falsehood, between truth and appearance, a certain duality of all Western philosophy.
a nice game of empty phantasmicoria to deceive us and keep us subjugated in chains. This is what
the dark side wants. The filling question may partly be relied on as a representation of Plato's
thought. The Matrix seems to rewrite them at the Plato's cave with a new interpretation,
with that's of course a technological upgrade which is compelling when you refer to the sleepy masses
of today, lost in the virtual world of the internet. If a slave could escape, says Plato,
But then he would be able to see the truth clearly, where the shadows which the shadows concealed and he would finally understand the prison planet that surrounds him.
If he wanted to go back into the cave to reveal such a truth to the other slaves, he would not be believed and indeed he might even be killed.
Okay, there we go. Well, that's just just about the matrix, right?
But it's based on this allegory of the cave and they told the story there
We heard heard it, but it's a really interesting story about which these men are just chained to this cave
See only these dark shadows. What does this kind of remind us of it? It's like sometimes when we're just watching
TV shows or you know, you know the TV and TV has a lot of
You know that you know YouTube's on a TV has a lot of good stuff, especially now with YouTube people making their own content
less control in the hands of the
mainstream media but
Still is you know for media and we are sometimes changed to this and where we see the shadows on the screen and we see
Acting we see oh, this is what the world is like
But we go outside walking around the Sun right before I was a cool in the Sun. I take a deep pressure. That's pressure, right?
Okay
It says some may not want to dissolve the chains of human existence
that lead to truth. They are the poor prisoners of Plato's ideal cave with the
realization that this is the prison planet and knowing that one could be
opposed and persecuted by the controllers of the famous matrix for one's
choice or even killed or unaligned by the slave gods. This term was defined
By the discarnate entity named Iwas that dictated the book of the law to English magician Alistair Crowley and his wife Rose Edith Crowley
And Cairo in 1904 if the elite could have it their way
They would try to stop any future mutiny of cavemen as it did with me over and over in the past
Hoping I would eventually give up the truth is so scary that most ordinary people prefer to refuse it
And not all men had the courage to face the risk involved in fighting such a battle it involves
a radical choice in one's life and in the life of one's family. This is what happened to me
when I suffered the betrayal of people close to me after my dramatic choice over a decade.
I go, I find myself in isolation, in a prison in Norway. In the end, there will always be an
infamous character like Cypher, the traitor, the Judas of the Matrix movie, the companion
of Neo-Amorphius, who reveals secret plans to artificial intelligences. The gist of the speech
tied to its false security and they feel it's better to remain ignorant than to know the truth
that can radically disrupt their lives. Okay.
There's a hidden manipulation, it says, characters who were persecuted, ridiculed,
insulted, and eventually brutally unalived by the smart pseudo-illuminati elites simply
for revealing the truth about the system that governs our physical and spiritual world.
Remember, it is not the crowd that decided the death of Jesus, but it was the notorious demagogues.
who were obviously instructed by someone behind the scenes.
They are hidden manipulators from the dark side
of the Illuminati, the slaves of the occult elite
that still dominate the world.
Just like Jesus at the time, those who managed
to brainwash and control the sheep who were with their lives,
away with this man released unto us barbarus.
Crucify him, crucify him, Luke 23, 18.
So Socrates in turn, the Inventure of Logic was condemned by a totally illogical verdict
issued by men who acted in the name of a supposed justice that keeps offending the system and
controllers regardless of the outcome.
At the point, just about a second time, they had to choose between the sentence proposed
Socrates was sentenced to death with 80 votes, more than those who had pleaded guilty, and
so he had been found guilty by 280 to 220 that was sentenced to death with 360 votes
against 140, and all this was hard to see the good in man.
You see, the idea of good in the physical world is, in fact, extremely rare.
For this reason, the experience of enlightenment depends on several impalpable factors, and hopefully at some point in our lives
we understand the true master we've been searching for resides within us.
Once activated, you will quickly develop the feeling that for the reality that surrounds you is invisible to the reality of most people,
majority of most people.
Okay.
No, that interest they have was not boring, you know, it's just that no one's talking
Some of these are I just I want to make it no
But I don't tell too many of the secrets because I think people first of all people were just told secrets
They don't appreciate them
they
you know, they
probably would doubt them or
Just like trash, you know, throw pearls to swine, you know
But I think in this case, it's like, you know, some secrecy is good and like some people say, I think if you want to discover them, you can. I mean, they're out there.
But I don't want to, you know, I do, I don't want to just like, you know, tell everybody and then everybody's like, oh, okay.
I hope they can learn how to teach them in a more profound way.
And then that helps you to learn them yourself. So how are we guys doing today?
Yeah, unfortunately Alex ruins another stream another stream probably the third one tonight or something
What gives Alex
Where my viewers go, I don't know Joe, but I Joe
Do you remember this show? I think you saw it. I don't know if you've probably seen it Joe
I have a few questions to ask you. Who is this? Hold on
Joe, are you here?
Oh, shit.
History.
Okay.
Oh, here.
I was on this one.
Joe, what is this?
Joe, are you looking at the screen?
So are you looking at the screen?
Here we go.
Okay
Anyway, you like that Joe oh
You're a different Joe, okay
It's over for me. Oh, wow. Oh, no because of this quick said. Oh, no this quick. Well, I'm gonna turn you some pancakes, okay
doing some pancakes and
Cover you in syrup butter
Eat you
I love this. I actually make a good coffee to get up this quick guys the real Joe won't even come here
He was here last night trying begging to come on the show half the time, please
You know what he's talking about
This was such a hater
That was some good AI on that side that was I think J Joe might have seen it
They're like, I'm a different show.
I don't know.
I always remember seeing you in the chat.
Look it, I'm your number one.
Oh no, guys, can you guys please start chatting
so Bisquick is kicked off the number one spot?
I don't know, I want Bisquick to win.
Because fuck.
But why are people quiet though?
They know it's hot. There's like 20 people in here
I've been chats with things for people and then everyone's talking
I've like four times that and no one's talking like or a couple of people are but I
Don't know are you that what are you what are you here to see they come you come to you see this view?
I mean I have the speedos right here. I mean I'll put them on later guys
It's like today is early the fourth of July celebrations just getting started
God
Guys, please get someone kicked you up
This week off the number one spot. Why is this quick such a hater?
I don't know who are you do I know you and feel I have to know you for you hate me so much
Yeah, I think it's I do have some random people that don't know me. They hate me, but
for you like, you know
Come at the 7 a.m. Los Angeles time to my chat
Like rubbing my face again. Oh, I just started again, you know, 24 minutes. So there's sorry. Yeah, it's kind of low right now, but
You know, yeah, all right. This was their name Kate is on stuff. So
You know, and I know they're after they don't say very nice things about me
They put their audience probably don't like me very much their audience is like a lot of the times would troll me
Some people like me some people didn't my we have a kind of a different
I don't know. I think that my chat just got infiltrated by trolls so many times
I kind of like some troll that thinks I like I love people. I like talking to people
Trolls are they do participate?
So there's nobody here. They're the ones that are coming up on panel. They're the ones that are in the chat and
Their locals aren't happy with your behavior the locals well, whatever
It's like, you know, we mean the locals like people in my area or the people that are like on local on YouTube
We mean the locals
What do you mean the panel verse okay, they're not happy with my behavior all the dining and dashing I
Think I maybe I think I've gone like maybe four times on my stream to go pick up some fish tacos for six dollars
For three or something like that
You don't pay. Oh, please. I do so and I do
This quick do you think I would I be banned from the pier if I've died and dashed you to pay first of all before you
Order and then they serve they serve you the food
It's like it's not a restaurant. It's like more of a you were with the counter and then they give it so you can eat it
There take it home
So I do pay for all my fish I don't ever dine in dash great
Very honest person. I don't steal I am honest with people. I have a you haven't seen me out on the pier
I know I haven't I can't go for a few days. I'm not in hiding. I just I'm out of data on my phone
Not hiding. Oh, I mean hiding. I'm like, I'm fucking right here on camera
It's for hours and hours a day
This is hiding
Everyone can see what everything I'm doing for 24 hour, you know, 18 hours or however many hours of the ice stream
But look, I'm here talking with you this week's making the chat pop right now
It's pretty a fan or not. Like, are you here? Do I know you? Who are you?
Who is this Alex
Who is it not a hiding oh you're so silly
Joe Christine
Yeah, oh, I love you Christine. Hey Christine. You're a neighbor
Oh my god, I mean my neighbor because my neighbors are under a count. You're a neighbor the locals aren't happy. What?
What I don't know what you're talking about, but this quick
I'm gonna beat you with a
You know because you're but you're a
Yeah, I doubt it's a neighbor. Yeah, my neighbor does come in they have may or does come in the show
I'm gonna beat you with it with a whisk, you know, cuz you're you're a you're bisquit
Yeah
My neighbor they are there and they have put to the chat and they've been there's sweet people in there
It's like hi, I've done full cards for them sometimes and
They are they love cats. They have a beautiful
golden fever named in Gus
No, who is this big this quick? Oh, he must be I
Saw people someone was talking saying that they're like talking like that in in a Samans chat
I forgot who it was and you were like it was a fake Jim Nick. Are you the fake Jim Nick?
I recognize you're like your insults
I'm pretty good at sniffing I'm better at Alex then uh
Yeah, then trolls and Alex I'm being better at smelling up trolls and Alex's and like who's who and stuff
he is like he'd be he
I don't know if he like he really hears myself like he was literally saying crucible goes was the same person as
The other guy in the chat, but they're talking at the exact same time. I'm trying to be careful. Yeah, I know he does
And then it's like we were just talking about you know
People are getting their channels bleated over some stupid like little little thing and the guy the guy speaking Alex
Maybe it's something to do with that. We're like, you know, even we're like, yeah, you know, we don't think he would do that
I mean, you know, we give him the benefit of the doubt. We don't know
Formums are very anonymous, you know, they
They don't have to show their face or give their real name. We know people have multiple accounts. He does he keeps doing me wrong
It's like why don't I keep going back to him? Why do I keep going back to a mama? I don't know
It's hard to be so forgiving I would love to be able to say oh fuck that person
I would love to I would say oh fuck him and then say never talk to me yet
I need to stop giving people the benefit of doubt. Yeah
Who nukes my channel Alex did what do you mean?
I think nukes like there's like not many people here or it's like nukes like what every start my stream like it was Alex
but
There's also, you know, Kate and be there are on right now too, but you know what it's like if
We're all gonna have people that love us, you know, and so
People that are here. Yeah, I know you love me because you know
You're hanging out with me now, right? And so I appreciate you and so it's also great
I'm not even though it's all in the room people. It's like I know that you guys want to you're here to watch me
You're like are
Well, I used to give him chances over and over and no more and more yet. Yeah, but you also pop me
I mean it's 7 a.m. It's like there's other people in the kind of the community that I stream in
You know stream right now it puts a bit on for like you know several hours today. We I don't yeah
That's the thing. I'm just trying to predict the channel
You know, and that's like they know people know how protective I am that's what they kind of troll on they're kind of like always trying to get me to like
second guess myself vinter
Do you stuff? I just have to go with my gut on it like
Work so far. I mean, I don't have any
Nothing's wrong. Nothing's on my channel. No strikes or anything. I
Making excuses
For what I mean is oh why my channel is not big
Maybe some maybe people don't like me. I don't know because I guess I'd be there like like, you know
Trashing my name all the time saying I'm this terrible person that oh, she'll reveal the real me and so stuff like that
Yeah, and then if I say oh for Alex. Yeah. Oh, yeah, well for Alex
No, yeah, sometimes we make excuses for people
I like him. It's like it's getting kind of too, once he starts messing with the show and like, because I would like, I wouldn't think he would do that, but
He's done it probably and it's like
Sometimes it's hard to prove. I just don't know and
I don't know
Maybe I'll get, I'll put him on a little punishment and then maybe he'll improve his behavior
They're like about him. Well, he's I think he's a character. I think he's a good character
He's funny. Sometimes I get a kick out of him and the guy tonight. I was on I forgot the guy that's a boxer
We got Sean or something Sean was like laughing so everything Alice said he was like laughing
I'll turn on him. You know see Alex
We have one fan probably on on YouTube in your yellow just hit him
I mean, yeah
Yeah, there's one person like Sean is like laughing actually laughing at his jokes, you know
He's like hysterically you can even you know, it's his breath
And then and then I was yelling at him over some stupid like he said he had a better car
I don't know where the hot girls go, you know pages now started her own channel
Christine's here Summers. I think doing a panel right now
You know
Hot girls have their own stuff to do. You know, I appreciate when anybody's here and I really
Hope that you know, they've introduced me to people. I hope to have introduced them to people
John has an old soul. Okay. Yeah, he seems like a genuine kind person
But it was I like people that can laugh but it's like, you know, he's left
He was the kind of like everything and I say he's like, oh, and he was like when I was off stage
I'm listening to back listening and he's like
He didn't say, oh, come on. I want to talk to psyche. He would say oh
Where's um, you know, where's I need any easier Alex back. He didn't want to talk
He's like he just wants to hang out with them here. And it's like I'm insulting. I like to
They said I'm the host, you know talk to the host like you want to I know it's like I know it's not even on stage, but I
Like being maybe called back and I like it. We'll say we're psyche
But it's okay. If they don't I whatever you like on the show you'd like
You probably meet people here you're like more than me and
They'll sort of show and you know, and I'll be like, oh, you know, I'll be like, hey, what's up?
And you'll be like over there panel like ah, I
Do you have this so many times, but it's okay. Okay. I
understand how YouTube works, so
Okay, so let me try to read.
Oh yeah, so I was reading this really cool book.
Do you guys want to hear these myths?
These are like myths from around the world,
but they're told in like a really fun way.
Like I'm finding it for my life.
Where is it?
It's called Zeus.
Hold on.
I grant stupid wishes. Okay, so I'll skip this story because I got it enough. Okay, so it says
Hephaestus gets dicked around a lot. Oh, thank you panel verse. I appreciate that
So this is about Hephaestus Hephaestus is of course like he's like the the god of metallurgy
He wouldn't forge weapons, but he got me. I kicked out of Olympus because I think
Hera thought he was like ugly or something but it says Hephaestus gets dicked around a lot
So one of the most inexplicable things about the Greek pantheon is that Aphrodite is married to Hephaestus.
Aphrodite is like the high school cheerleader of the Greek pantheon and
Hephaestus is a guy with the gimple leg who's always making historically accurate World War II models.
He doesn't actually make World War II models because World War II hadn't been invented yet, but
He does have a gimp leg. I'm not making that part up. He got it because when Zeus and Hera first had him
He was so ugly that they actually threw him off of Mount Olympus
And he fell for seven days and they only ever ever let him back up to Olympus
Once he showed them that he could make some really nice jewelry
So says Zeus and Hera ultimate parenting look the point is that of Aphrodite is the goddess of boning everyone all the time
And if this is the god of sitting in the forge all day making armor and swords for all the must-leads use
Who had murder other must-leads use and then bone everyone all the time?
So why the fuck is the festus married to Aphrodite?
How did he score such a sweet tale? Well, first of all, Hera felt bad about chucking him off a cliff and
Herp idea of an apology was to give him Aphrodite
ultimate parenting and second of all Aphrodite is the goddess of boning everyone all the time
So it's not like she's gonna actually be faithful or anything
And in fact she's sort of making a habit of boning Aries the god of war who is like the quarterback to her slutty cheerleader
He is actually doing this in FS is his bed and he is out working at the Ford probably making armor for Aries even
But FS this gets wise through the tricky scheme the crafty street scheme because mainly because the Sun is such a gossipy bitch
And he decides to show his cheating horrible wife. What's what with science?
So he melts down the armor he was making for Ares, and he uses all the metal to make some chains, and then he uses his mad skills to turn these chains into a giant indestructible net that is invisible somehow, and then he hangs the net over his bed like a canopy.
So the next time Aphrodite and Ares hop into the little bit of Wango-Bango, Hephaestus leaves in the room all like,
Except he can't leap because he has a gimp leg but anyway
He drops the net on them and then traps them on the bed
But the jokes on him because they have no intention on leaving the bed
They're both like well, we're caught might as well continue our burner fiesta in plain view
But the jokes on them
Because the Festus invited all the other gods to come hang out in his bedroom today
So they all start rolling in and Dionysus is lapping his ass off because he can totally see nipple and
Poseidon pokes Zeus and says would you tap that and Zeus says it probably I already have I'm not making that up
The shit is in the Odyssey
But really the joke is still on a Festus because his wife is boning another man right in front of him and even the best
Blacksmiths cannot repair a broken relationship
Wow
How'd you like that one? Okay, these are kind of short and sweet we're now in the Nordic miss
You guys want to hear about some Nordic miss you see?
Because one's door gets hammered no, it's not history another one, okay
This looks a little too controversial.
Hey, Vicki, happy 4th of July.
Happy 4th of July, everybody.
Okay, this one says, sex for gold.
It says, before we go any further,
this is Norse mythology, right?
This is the Nordic, right?
So before we go any further,
I need to tell you a little bit
about the kind of person Freya is.
Because it's difficult to find a myth about Freya
in which her main role is that it just,
Something people give each other that is because Norse appear to treat women as a currency, but don't worry guys
I found one kind of so Freya wakes up one morning
And she's like I had just had a wet dream about some gold and now I want some but where shall I get some?
Oh wait, I live in this world. It has dwarves. What a stupid question
So she walks over to the dwarf house while she's walking Loki sees her and is like oh man
That chick looks like she's about to get some treasure
I want to ruin that accomplishment for her because I am Loki and that's what I do
So Loki follows Freya all the way to her house on these four dwarves, and they're sitting
on their pedestal.
It is the most astonishing display of gold-duggery ever.
Gold-duggery is kind of like gold-duggery except doing crimes, you do gold.
It is a necklace of such indescribable value that all Norse scribes purposefully lost most
of the test of the myth.
And no one actually knows what it looks like or even if it is a necklace really we're kind of just guessing here
More or less based on the fact that a necklace is only from form of gold big enough to fit four door for dicks
Simultaneously and so these fourths easy door pop out and pray is like it grows. I mean hey guys. How's it going?
Think I can have with this necklace or whatever it is and they're like I'll pay you gold for it
And the doors are like we don't need any more gold
Well record scratch did you just hear what I heard doors do not need more gold
These are clearly not four doors or rather eight babies in four door suits
But just to make the next part weirder, because Freya's like, well, gold pretty much is all I have.
Credit cards have been invented yet, nor has investment banking.
The Doors are like, well, you have a vagina, right? How's about we all use that for like 24 hours a piece?
And Freya's like, hmm, okay.
So the Doors...
So each of the dwarves does the teeny weenie with Freya for a solid day and night cycle.
And they are very civil about it, and no one minds getting sloppy seconds.
And at the end of the four days, the dwarves are like,
well, we're about as sexually satisfied as we're ever going to be in our sad, sad lives.
Here's the necklace. And Freya is like, sweet.
And that was almost worth the basing myself in this manner.
Meanwhile, Loki, who we remember following Freya here, is like, damn, I wish I had filmed that.
I bet there's a whole internet fetish about this kind of shit.
I guess I'll have to settle for ruining her accomplishments just like I planned so Freya goes home to enjoy her necklace and take a long shower and
Loki hauls that so we're the Odin's place. He's like Odin Odin. Guess what? I know I'm the god of lying all the time
But you got to trust me when I say Freya just fucks four dwarves and it for a necklace and Odin's like yeah
That sounds like Freya. I mean what I wanted to fuck Freya. We all wanted to fuck Freya
That's the whole reason we keep her around and they'll always do three these years with opera jewelry unacceptable
Go steal her necklace and Loki's like did somebody say stealing and Odin's like yes, Loki
And it was me that said that but Loki doesn't hear him because he was already at Freya's place stealing
So he gets to Freya's place and the door is locked and he turns into a fly and goes into
a crack in the roof.
But then Freya is sleeping on her back with a clasp of her necklace completely inaccessible
as Loki turns to a flea and mauls her cheeks until she flips over and then Loki turns into
Loki and steals her necklace.
So Freya wakes up and notices her necklace is gone, notices her door is open and is
like damn it Loki!
But wait, Loki would be too much of a pussy to do this on his own.
Damn it Odin!
But how would Odin know about my necklace?
Damn it, Loki!
But Loki's probably nine countries away at this point.
I'm gonna yell at Odin!
So she shows up at Odin's place, all angry and shit, and Odin's like, well, well, well,
if it isn't Slut City, hey, I have some brass plates and a shiny rock.
Want to give me a rim job or something? They're all yours and Freya said you're very funny asshole and Odin's like
I bet you won't think my asshole is very funny when you're giving me a rim job
But seriously because of shit like this they're gonna keep trying to sell you to Giants
So I'm gonna punish you and Freya's like off rig
What's it gonna be and Odin's like well, I'll let you have the necklace back
But only if you make all the races of men and men guard fight wars forever. Oh wait, that's not really a punnit
Oh and phrase like yes
Done. Thank you. And now there's war forever, but at least Freyja looks pretty. So the moral of the story is that apparently women are currency, but the exchange rate of women to gold isn't actually that great.
Okay, that was a pretty good one. Lowkey be lowkey stunting on them like no peace, Odin's son, bitch, you don't know me.
Okay, okay. Well, maybe that's the only one I'll read out of the Nordic. Let's see what else we have. Oh, hold on.
This one says, the end of the Norse world as we know it.
Do you want to hear about the winter and the Seathless War?
And now this is too boring.
OK, let's go to Egyptian.
You might not guess from their tame to the cave paintings,
but the ancient Egyptians like to tell some seriously
messed up myths.
They've got all the essentials, booze, blood, and jerkinet.
If you thought that the essentials were food, water,
and shelter, then my friend, you have been reading the wrong myths.
And if any mortals actually managed to survive the constant barrage of nonsense from above
Egyptian lore says you had to get your soul weight against a fucking feather
By a pitiless demon with a dog for a head and if your soul is heavier than the feather you go to hell
So I hope you hear me in hell every dude who ever lived in ancient Egypt because I'm about to seriously bastardize your cannon up right here
So says raw has sex with himself drunken in America's favorite pastime
of the worlds. Okay, Ra has sex with himself. Jerkinet, start with the Jerkinet. Ra has sex with
himself. So there's a dude named Ra. The dude does not exist, at least not in the beginning of the
story. All that is, all there is is a totally boring infinite water called Mu. But then Ra, who
remember didn't, didn't exist, is like, this sucks. How do I create myself using pure willpower?
So now Ra is standing around, except actually he's not standing, he hasn't been standing yet, so anywhere there's no place to stand.
So Ra is like, okay, time for some terrain features. Let's start with the ones that look most like tits.
So he makes a hill and he stands on it, but later he, someone builds a temple, but let's not get ahead of ourselves.
So Ra gets pretty bored seeing as there is...
All there is in the entire goddamn universe is a hill in some water
So he bangs he hangs out in the hill for a bit waiting for awesome dudes to wield themselves in the being but they did it
And he's like man you guys are so lazy fine
I'll make my own friends, but there's a problem because although rock can make hills and also himself
He apparently can't make people sexual reproduction is ruining everything as usual but Rod doesn't even give a shit
Uh, he goes ahead and he fucks his own shadow until he gets pregnant and he gives birth to kids out of his mouth
In the two least classy ways possible. Yes guys
It's easy just to be believed you're either descended from spit or puke depending on whether you're a boy or a girl
Anyway, see rise two kids the phlegm kid is this dude called shoe and the god of air and stuff meanwhile the vomit
Kid is a chick named Tef Newt and the goddess of moisture
Not water reminds you about moisture, which makes me sense with the whole vomit thing, I guess, which makes sense of the whole vomit thing.
Anyway, Shu and Teph nuts get together, and by their powers, combined,
managed to be exponentially more bored than even their omnipotent father could have imagined.
So they're sitting around and they're like, hey, want to eat each other with bricks?
Oh wait, bricks don't exist. Just like absolutely everything else other than hills. Fuck it.
Let's make up some codes of laws and then get lost.
So they make up some of the laws and then they get lots in the middle of an endless ocean fiasco
which is kind of like SeaWorld. If SeaWorld was everything everywhere and there's no
shampoo and there's no amusement park or hot dogs or whatever it was just actually the water
part of SeaWorld and there's only three people there and two of them are lost and they're made
Actually, the last part sounds a lot like SeaWorld.
So, Ra is like,
Guys, I fucked my own shadow, so I won't be lonely.
Come back.
And then he takes out his one eye.
By the way, he only has one eye.
And he's like, hey, I go find my kids.
And so it does, and it brings them back to Ra.
And he starts crying either because he's so happy
to have his kids back,
or because now he has to raise kids.
But the myth is not clear
whether he puts his eye back in before his death.
He does this or whether it's the weird floating sadness or but that's not important at all
What's important is that those tears hit the hill raw made and they turn into people and then shoe and tiff nuts start
Boning like siblings do they pop out this kid gab the earth and newt the sky
These are extremely large babies no lie then later
Give a newt give birth to all the trendy gods that go at Isis and Osiris and whatever and things
Proceeded pretty much as would be expected with a lot of murder and sex and stuff
So, basically, what it all comes down to is that we are made of tears from the disembodied
eyeball of a guy who fucks his own shadow and surrounds himself with spit and puke.
I'm going to cry now.
I hope it doesn't turn into babies.
Yeah.
Okay.
Was that a good one?
I'm going to hang out for a little bit, or if you're having fun.
So, it says raw and segment or how beer saved the universe.
So so rock creates the world sure great, but you just because you create the world doesn't mean you get to be king of it forever
I mean you get to be king of it for a while
Like for example in rod does with citizens done creating everything he turns into a dude and becomes king of Egypt
But the problem with dudes is that they get old and the problems the old dudes as they're constantly getting guffed from all directions
And the problem with being a god is that you're con can't constitutionally and capable of taking any guff whatsoever
So naturally when everybody starts laughing at Rod's old hair and senility he gets real pissed and when you're a god
And you get real pissed. There's only one solution my friends genocide
So basically what Rod does is he turns around and he gives Egypt the deadliest stink eye
This eye is so stinky it produces an entire new brand of goddess the goddess is named segment
She's basically like a lioness with chainsaws for legs
segment the original thunder cat
Sekhmet's job is simple. Kill everyone. So this is what she does. She just tears all around everywhere,
mulling that ever-living crap out of people until the ground is like permanent red,
which is a... this can certainly tacky. Eventually, Ra wakes up from his old man's sleep and he's like,
whoa, where did all the people go? Damn, I kind of feel bad now. Gods are always doing things like
this, if you haven't noticed, but the problem is that by now Sekhmet is an unstoppable murder engine.
But the good thing good news is there's one if there's there's one thing with the power to stop an
Unstoppable murder engine and the thing is booze
So what rod does and gathers up all this really good beer and all this really good red food coloring and mixes it together
He dumps it all over the fields a segment has scheduled for murder in the next day
And when she shows up she just sees a big lake of what she can only assume is blood
Blood that smells like booze and it's like the blood of really drunk people and she's like all right
It looks like murderings done early today. I'm from my second favorite pastime. They're valuing the blood of the innocence
so segment just dives right in and starts slurping the booze blood, which is
Such good shit that everybody calls it a sleepmaker and because of that she ends up passing out pretty quickly
She wakes up all hungover and rods like ha ha ha from now on you will be known as hot door
And the only thing you will kill is people with kindness.
And basically, whatever Ross says, this immediately happens.
And so that's what segment becomes from then on.
So obviously, the moral of the story
is that the best way to deal with rampaging psychopath
is to get them really, really drunk.
You're shook.
OK, let me see.
Another one.
Well, I'll do one more.
I'll do one more that we can chat for a little bit.
Bagel who says so Isis has bad taste in jewelry and says so time passes and now
Osiris is the king of the gods he thinks he's hot shit with his godly
appendages up whole vast swaths of blouse but meanwhile there's this dick set
that's his name set I don't know
I'm not talking about some kind of dick set,
such as you might purchase for an adult tea party.
I'm talking about the Egyptian god of the desert
and also storms, darkness, and chaos.
Basically, if you're not having a good time,
said is right there flipping you off with both hands
while jacking off with his third hand
or maybe with a hand he stole from a baby.
What I mean is, that is the dick.
The reason I mentioned set is that he gets all butthurt over not being the king of the gods
So he has a great plan which is he makes this coffin out of wood
Which is like Taylor made for Osiris basically and then he calls them all the gods like hey you guys you should come over I
Mean I have a weird coffin party and the gods are all like oh shit weird coffin party
We'll be right over and so they all get there and said is like all right
I made this coffin whoever fits perfectly inside gets candy
It's called Zeus makes called Zeus a grants stupid wishes, and it's a no-nonsense guides in mythology. It's really good
It's if you got it has Egyptian has
Nordic it has the gypsum Nordic Greek and a few other cultures. I think I think I'm
the South American too
So they all get there and said is okay, so of course all the gods think this sounds like an out of my DS
They turn take turns trying to get into the coffin and they all fail
But then it's Osiris's turn and Osiris is like, I don't know guys
It seems like a transparent ruse, but then he gets into the coffin anyway
It slams shut and locks and set lines it with lead and throws it in the Nile River and everyone's like whoa
Major coffin party foul and said it's like so I get to be king now, right and he does
So naturally Osiris' wife, Isis, decides to find him so that she can bury him properly
now that he's drowned, and she finds his coffin, has floated all the way to Biblos, which
is actually just Lebanon in disguise, and gotten absorbed by an oak tree, which has
got cut down and used to build a support pillar in a palace for the king of Biblos.
Shit.
So Aysen shows that the biblo is like hey queen my husband is embedded in your palace may please extract him and the queen is like
Oh sure go ahead
It's not like he's a major structural support or anything, right and Aysen is like ha ha sucker
And she goes removes the pillar without damaging the palace at all and that's inventing Jenga
Except instead of delicately placing the coffin on top of the palace, Isis takes out Osiris' body and drags it back to Egypt and bears it in the desert so we can finally rest in peace.
Apparently forgetting that Set is the god of the desert.
And she goes and removes the pillow without- oh, hold on.
Okay, so Set very quickly sniffs Osiris' grave out and is like, hmm, I haven't fucked with this guy enough. How about I tear him into 14 pieces and eat his dick?
So what he does is he
That's what he does
He chucks the other 13 pieces and all the fuck everywhere and then ice is like what what is that noise?
It better not be my husband being ripped up and thrown everywhere
But it's too late
This already happens and I just finds out and she's like seriously
I just buried this guy now. I got to find all these body parts and bury him again
Even though said we'll probably just buy them and rip them to smaller pieces anyway
She manages to find all the pieces most of which have turned into full moons by the way except for his dick because like I said
That ate it
So I said like my son my son Osiris and dick was like the most important part of her personality
Man Osiris and dick was like the most important part of his personality
So what she does is she makes a gold dick a gold cock and she hangs it around her neck and damn
Osiris is alive again with his golden dong that's landing the groundwork for Mike Myers cinematic triumph gold member
And also getting Isis pregnant with Horace because I guess that dick necklace was more potent than she bargained for
So ladies, I guess the moral of the story is don't wear a cock around your neck because unplanned pregnancy is the worst accessory
Okay, well, I'll go to one more I'll go out of Egypt and let's go to like the left. Oh, so my in let's do a Mayan
Because the minds of the most brutal calendar like you're in your royal highness. Yes
So this is one Mayan dude, right?
He has like 50 goddamn names like huru Khan or Google Mots or Heart of the Sky
And I'm not even really sure if he's one Mayan dude or like a collection of Mayan dudes because they keep acting like he's
It's two people, but the two people never do anything independently, so they're basically just the same person or some kind of hive mind anyway
We're gonna call this thing Ketso-Cottle
Quetzalcoatl is bored because all that is anywhere is a bunch of water and some sky and it's not an interesting sky
Because there's no light so Quetzalcoatl is like okay boom
There's some light and then he goes boom again
There's some land but this is still pretty lame because what is the point of being able to do this kind of shit if there's no one
Around to get freaked out by how cool it is
Now this may sound pretty familiar so far, but here's where it gets crazy
Ketsukato's master plan for getting worshipers was to invent jaguars, and then he's like whoa jaguars
Look, I just fucking made you pretty neat, huh?
And the jaguars are like raw we're jaguars we can't talk or be impressed so Ketsukato
It's like ah fuck you guys
I'm gonna make some more awesome creatures
They're gonna worship me and you're gonna be their slaves
So we get some dirt and he makes them dirt people but the dirt people really suck because first of all they're made out of dirt
Second of all, they only speak gibberish, and third, they dissolve in water.
So Ketsukwado figures that even if they could worship him, they would be pretty embarrassed,
so he kills them by dumping water on them and then calls these two other Jews, Zumukkain
and Zepaiokok, who have the names that sound like prescription drugs designed to treat nasal
congestion and erectile dysfunction, respectively.
Is it a good time for me to make people out of wood and they're like, yeah, go for it
And so he makes people out of the wood and a whole bunch of wooden robots basically
They can now speak and walk around but they don't dissolve on water, but they're tremendous assholes
One might even say they have a stick up their asses get it get it
I'll screw you guys anyway. They totally forgot to worship ketsukato even a little bit and he's getting pre-pissed
at this point because he takes
He has seriously made everything that exists and no one is giving him any credit
So we kind of freeze out a little and cause this fire to rain from the sky and burns everything to cinders
And it makes all the wood people's cookware come alive and kill them and all the animals move into their houses and eat them
Even though they're made of wood and totally not tasty and meanwhile quetzalcoatl makes a bunch of actually delicious people out of
Portillas and those people are supposedly us
And as soon as Quetzalcoatl grates board, he's going to make us into burritos.
Oh, that's perfect with my fish taco.
And then feed us some jaguars or whatever.
But the story is apparently plausible enough to freak out the entire goddamn world all through the waste of 2012.
But anyway, everyone is happily ever after, except the wood people who got chased into the wood and turned into monkeys.
So the moral of the story is never set fire to a monkey because he is made of wood and you'll start a forest fire.
Oh, you guys are talking about Bigfoot and stuff?
Interesting. You like it. You like that one? Okay
How about who know who who know poo and the ball in the ball in K ultimate ballers?
You want to hear about the ultimate ballers?
So there's these two dudes who
Who know poo and Vukap who know poo their twins at least brothers
Anyway, they pissed off the gods of the underworld with their constant ball playing
Yes, that is right. They played sports so hard that it upset mine Satan
You're buying the book now awesome
Anyway, the gods summoned them down to the underworld which is called the Balba because no mine story is complete without about
6,000 proper nouns beginning with X so the gods are like hey guys. We heard you like ball playing get it
We heard it because you're so loud and the twins are like what what on it and the gods are like
Well, if you like ball games so much
How about you play ball with us for your lives and the twins are like this sounds like the ultimate rush
Now if this was a Greek myth the twins would probably use some kind of mad scaler trickery to beat the gods
This is a Mayan myth that Jews get killed before the game even starts for smoking a cigar the wrong way
And then they get decapitated and buried under the ball court except for Hoon's head
Which they put on the kalabash tree for some reason this turns out to be a bad idea
Because some chick named Zequik walks by and Hoon spits it in her hand, and he is such a true man that this caused her to get pregnant
And she gives birth to twins
So as you think you're hot shit because your penis is one and a half inch longer than the national average
Try impregnating a random chick in her hand with her saliva from a tree on which someone has deposited your severed head
Wait, wait, I wonder I want I read it again. It wasn't even his head. It was just a skull
Skulls don't even makes the liva
So I guess what he had some skin and stuff. He just collected a big glob of spit and there he held it waiting I
Want that shit on one of those posters that say hang in there
Hang on there. So yeah, is the quick gives birth to twins and they're called who know to and it's a ball cave
And these two guys are alive for like five minutes before they discover their dad's ball playing here and start
Playing ball so goddamn hard that they piss off the underworld again and they get summoned down there and the gods like hey
You may have noticed that severed head hanging from the tree by your house
That was the last dude who kept us awake with ball playing. That was also your dad FYI
Why the hell do you guys even like playing ball this much? Okay? Look you want to play ball?
For your lives and the twins are like the ultimate rush so they play ball
And see if that was a Roman myth or maybe a Norse myth the guys would have totally like won an adventure father
But like I said the Mayans were assholes
So the gods went again they killed the twins and buried them under the ball court
But there is a twist because it turns out the twins are immortal somehow
And so they dig themselves up and sneak away and they come up with a crafty plan
Which is to come directly back to the underworld dressed as traveling performers
And the gods were like, sweet, because it is boring in Zabalba with the constant noise of ball playing.
So Hunapu and Zabal-K put on a fantastic show full of amazing feasts.
Maybe they even did an astonishing magic trick where they make their names easier to fucking type
But anyway for the finale one of them cuts off the other's head and puts it back on without any problems
And the gods like awesome do me do me do me the twins like sure
Okay, and they go and chop up the gods heads without any resistance whatsoever because that's how slick they are and then they go dig
Up their dads and resurrect them and no one can ever forget how lucky they are to be able to use their dicks to get women pregnant
So the moral story is to ball so hard motherfuckers when I'm murder you and
bury you under a balkwood.
Well, that is that all?
Oh, no, actually, there's there's one more country.
I'll read the last country, but I don't know if there is.
Oh, there is.
OK, Judeo, Christian, Hindu, or Japanese.
OK, let's do Hindu.
Oh, and they also have African.
We'll just do Hindu.
We'll do maybe a couple of Hindu.
OK.
So back in the days before there was stuff and things there was a dude just this one dude as far as the eye could see
Spanning the entire breadth of the universe plus like 10 extra feet for good measure. His name was the dude
But not the dude from the big Lebowski this wasn't significantly bigger in Lebowski we're talking about here
This is by Lebowski as big as the entirety of creation. He is so big
He exists at all times before and after his birth and like a quarter of his body is made up of all the animals ever and
Like the other three forces all the gods and he's actually gives birth to a dude named Verge who gives birth to him what?
So obviously the gods gets hired trying to conceptualize this universe
Universal zoo they're like screw this. Let's sacrifice them. They tie him down and cut him up and
this is
Then and just start splitting pieces of his body absolutely everywhere
All these giblets are turning into things all the case he clarified butter that boil up turns into animals
And even though I thought animals were already quartered of his body. I guess a quarter of his body was butter fatty
Anyway, the gods are pretty much making up ceremonies as they go along, so these kind
of get written down and preserved for eternity.
Also, I got to hand it to these gods to take some serious effort, Cajones, to kill in butch
or something of 75% composed of you.
But anyway, his mouth becomes priests, his arms become nobles, his thighs become the
His feet become the slaves, his brain turns into the moon, his eyeballs are the sun, and
the sky comes out of his ears, and the ground forms under his peasant feet.
And God starts to make a whole assload of fires because you start to butcher the universe
that might as well be on fire.
And so these fires turn into the ideal social order somehow.
No one mentions what happens to the Duke's dog or his chest actually my guests
I'm creeper God stole that shit and built himself a pangalactic real doll
So the moral of the story is next time you're getting sexed up
Just remember that both of you and your honey are made out of the same dude. So basically everybody's gay
Okay
Okay, so we're gonna hear about Shiva. Here's a Shiva. He's a cool dude
The Shiva cannot be stopped. So okay, so there's this dude Brahma, right?
He's the creator of everything
So he's one day he takes his mind makes his mind it makes a hot shit come out of it
The hot chick is his daughter, but as soon as he pops out his brain baby, Brahm is like,
oh damn, I want to do things that I haven't even been invented yet.
Good thing I'm a creator and I can invent those things right away.
And then he goes ahead and gives himself three extra heads.
So he can check out his daughter from all angles, thus causing the world to get divided
into four directions because the creator suddenly desires something that is outside
of himself.
But enough spirituality, back to the tits and bad decisions.
Okay, so Brahma's daughter gets wind of this exquisite voyeurism going down.
She's pretty embarrassed, and since she can't stop being hot, she decides to stop being
on earth instead.
She goes up to heaven. So now Brahma is like, oh, I want to continue to look at tits
But my head only looked down looks like I need another head
So this is the thing about being into creator you do not consider options. It's just I don't know moving your neck
No, you grow an extra fucking head looking straight up and then you send it's shooting down toward heaven
All like nom nom nom nom tits time at this point Brahma's daughter is up in heaven
Like what am I going to do with this encroaching molester's head?
And this is when Shiva steps to the plate and it's like that's enough bullshit Brahma, and he chops up Brahma's head
using only a thumbnail
But instead of a hearty thank you and maybe some victory prudent hang
Shiva gets Brahma's gross skull stuck in his hand and he's like ah balls
This is my jerkin at hand and he transforms into Brahma
All right, and he transforms this by Raava,
AKA the chief of ultimate rage.
And he's like, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna wreck some shit.
And then I'm gonna wreck some shit.
And Brahma's like, oh no, you're not son.
You're going to get banished all the way out of here.
That is what you're gonna do.
And then you're gonna roam around the land
as a mad beggar until you're arbitrarily forgiven.
So this is what Shiva does and so one day he stumbles upon a group of sages all sitting around and praying the
Bejesus out of themselves that Shiva rolls up like hey, hey, ooga booga crazy homeless guy here
What's up? And the sages are like what and the sages wives are like, oh, man
I want to tap that like a king of boners and they all go dance the crazy wango bango tango with Shiva and the sages like what?
So obviously they send a tiger up from Shiva and she responds by taking off the tiger's skin and wearing it as a skirt
So then they just send a poisonous snake after Shiva and Shiva picks up a snake and wears
it as a goddamn necklace.
And so then they send the evil dwarf after Shiva rightly assuming there's probably no way for Shiva to wear a dwarf
That's right guys. That's how fuck that's how fuckable gold it in India
They have fuckable gold in India, too
The Shiva just sort of kicks the door over stands on his face and takes his club
Then he turns around like come on hot bitches follow me to the forest and so they do and then Shiva
I K by Robber remember it was to Vishnu's crib like Vishnu
Let me in Vishnu's bouncer is like who are you? You're not on the list
And by Rava, it's like, I am the guy who's...
S-T-A-B-B-I-N-G-U, to death with a trident.
And then Vishnu jumps out of the black room,
like, oh snap, I wish you blood out of my face
until you go away.
And by Raba, feels Rama's sticky skull
with Vishnu's blood, like, thanks, sucker.
I was just dropping by to ask
if I could borrow a cup of your blood.
And then he dances off into the forest,
carrying a doorkeeper's body and a skull full of blood.
He dances all over everywhere
until he gets to the holy city of Varanasi,
at which point he's pardoned for his crimes.
gets back to heaven. So I guess the moral of the story is if you're ever
indicted for murder, your best bet is to do more murders, then fill the skulls of
your victims with the blood of some of your other victims and maybe stage an
impromptu dance party with some women you stole and eventually people will
realize you can't be stopped and you can go to heaven. Excuse me while I go
convert to Hinduism.
Okay, I'll tell one more story. That's it one more
30 people. Okay. This is about Ganesha. You know the Indian
Elephant-headed God Ganesha. He's very beloved in India and all over the world now
This is Ganesh is the very definition of an unplanned pregnancy
So she was married to Kali right wrong. Well, yes, he is married to Kali, but it also turns out
She was also married to a other chick poverty
Who's a gentle goddess of life and stuff, but, as it turns out, Parvati and Kali are
the same person.
Whoa, snap plots with, yeah, apparently she can transform between sweet, loving, life
goddess and unspeakable hurricane of death for any reason at any time.
This is what we know as an exciting marriage.
Anyway, in this story, poverty is busy being poverty,
which is good news for everybody, except for Shiva,
because now, all the time,
Kaldi would have spent murdering and busting
sweet dance moves,
poverty spends thinking about having babies,
and Shiva's not ready to be a father.
I mean, he kind of created the universe, but he does not want to be tied down, okay?
So Parvati gets sick of bugging him that a baby with her. She's like, wait a second. I'm a goddess
Having babies in unconventional ways is what we do
so she
Goes ahead and makes a baby all by herself and she names him Ganesh and
Then goes to the shower and tells Ganesh to guard the door because apparently her soul motivation besides have behind having kids
It's to make sure no one sees any naked boobs while she's washing up
It would probably have been just simpler to lock the door, poverty, children, or a serious
responsibility.
And of course, this is the exact moment that Shiva decides to come along and prove beyond
a shadow of a doubt that neither of these people should have kids because he sees the
shower house where his wife is showering, and he's like, oh man, what a perfect opportunity
for some steamy shower sex.
So he just marches on there.
Uh, except instead of getting inside, he gets some input and baby blocking his path and she was like, you know
I am and goodness is like, no, dude
I'm a baby and she was like, well then you can call me the guy who just chopped up your head right now ding
and of course
This is the moment that poverty chooses to finish her shower and comes
Sauntering out of the shower house and sees her husband standing over her dead baby
She's like, you bring my baby back to life or else and she was like or else what?
And probably his name is, or probably he's like,
or else I'm gonna turn into Kali
and you're gonna have to chase me down
and dance me into submission again.
And she was like, hmm, good point.
Okay, hold on, there's baby Ganesha, okay.
And Shiva sends out some of his dudes to grab the first head they find and they bring it to him
And I guess he is pretty dumb servants because they come back with the head of an elephant and she was like guys
I feel it would have been just easier to decapitate a baby rather than a full-grown elephant
And also you should have figured out from the context clues what I meant
But whatever I guess I'll make it work
So he just glues the elephant head onto the dead baby and causes it somehow to come back to life
And that is why Ganesh has an elephant head now.
And also why he's the God of Wisdom,
which is bad news for Shiva
because an elephant never forgets.
So the moral of the story is that you shouldn't worry
if you accidentally kill your baby
just to kill another baby and glue pieces of it
to the first baby until it comes back to life.
Works every time or at least this one time.
That was fun.
That was funny.
But yeah, this kind of I do love that's you know, it's like I haven't seen the myth written up like in such a modern style
Happy Fourth of July ghost of mr. P
Hi, how are you doing? Welcome to show nice to see you. Well happy fourth of July everybody if they're you're in America like
Lot of the chat some people are in England and all around the world. We can all celebrate
The Speedos are universally loved, right?
Fireworks. Okay, so that was that book. Yeah, I'll read some more stories some other time, you know
That one
I just I have that like I told you I have thousands and thousands of books
I just want to fly
But you are around me baby. Oh, so this one's called gas. Oh
Oh
Oh look
How was your concert? Oh, it's a big day. Oh, don't do it. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding
There's no party at a good time. How guys do not show up there. The police will be there
Protecting him. Yeah, they will. Yeah, they will. There's nobody there. Everyone's cancel the plans. It's the next fire festival
It was a big bus
No, no refunds. Okay. Hey, how are you?
I was playing on my end. I know. I know. It was a prank. It's on. Hey, no, no. It goes to Mr. P. Don't type. Don't type those words in my chat, please. Okay.
Well, what up, Matt? I just want to say happy 4th of July, man. Aw, thank you so much. Happy 4th of July to you. God bless America.
What are you reaching for there?
Okay, okay, and then
Okay, you're fine. Oh, you're very fine. Yeah, do you have any plans for the day?
Okay, you don't fireworks or like, you know
Fourth of July parade to do
There's not there's not a fair parade you can go to these we used to go to these fourth of July
We have bike parade and play egg toss and
Watermelon you contest stack races, but what do you you don't do that?
Okay, you're just gonna sit home. Okay. Well, what are you gonna watch on TV? Are you watch?
What do you like to watch on TV?
well 4th of July, I don't know, born on the 4th of July?
well, yeah, as you say, what's a good movie to watch on 4th of July?
born on the 4th of July, maybe like, some kind of patriotic movie or, I don't know
well, you can watch a Patriot with Mel Gibson
okay
Yeah, it's very patriotic
But you know what's no Gibson's in Australia. He's Australian. You know, he's I know I know he's Australian
If you ever heard him talk to his normal voice
And he's a little mate. Good. I might and I'm milk you soon. Oh, yeah, you know, it's weird
Yeah, it's like people from Australia in England. They can
They can sound American where if we try to sound like them like we sound stupid
Yeah, we mean that's maybe kind of like
More to do with like the acting ability of some American and acting
You know Nicole Kidman is as the after course Australian. He's ledger. They play a lot of American roles
Who else you know
It's about the dialects. Yeah, but I think people there's people that can imitate dialects
I think there's but I think they're foreign actors probably more snobby about their countries like you know
They're all Americans so easy to imitate, but you get to appreciate accents. My mind is bad. I'm sorry
I can sound like a Southern boy if I won't, I can talk like this, you know.
Well, aren't you from the South first of all?
How are you doing today, sir?
It's not very good Southern accent.
Dialects are dialects.
It's not a good Southern accent.
If you need to work on that.
I actually have a very good Southern accent.
Guys, what do you think?
Can you write down what's in chat?
How was the accent?
Yeah, I know.
That's what I said.
Arthur born on 4th of July watch Robo cop is that a 4th of July theme movie?
Dingo
It's 753 a.m. in California. I don't know what time it is over there. Where are you located?
it's almost 11 a.m.
Okay, almost 11 a.m. Well, I'm thinking about getting some breakfast. Let me see.
If I can get a good deal, some coffee and bagels maybe? Let me see. The bagel savage three offers available.
They have garlic bagels. I'm sold. Okay, $5.15. That sounds like a great deal. Okay
Well, thank you, I appreciate that, you know, it's you know, there's more people in the chat, but yeah
Nice talk, you know, you know, sometimes people get in the way and then we start to fight and say I think we could be great friends
I just don't understand why we have to argue sometimes
Okay
So yeah, and guys, you know, you know, beautiful lady come up the panel. So he times doesn't
Feel uncomfortable, you know, I'm not gonna reach over your square. I promise. I won't know I'm reaching over
Not reaching over
Okay, yeah
Oh, I know if there's one day you can all come together it's fourth of July
Yeah
So, celebrate our independence, yes.
Yes.
So, let me get this.
What?
Sorry.
So yeah, I do look forward to July.
Well, I did one more as a kid,
now it's kind of not an exciting holiday,
but I do have the Speedos,
and so that's something.
There'll be a new tradition.
And I'm gonna auction off the Speedos tonight.
And the starting bid is $20.
So guys, if you wanna bid on those speedos.
That's weird.
Why is it weird?
There's just my slightly soiled speedos.
No, that's weird.
That's like selling your underwear or something.
No, it's a bathing suit.
They're speedos.
No, that's sell underwear.
No, they're like a bathing suit material.
No, some people know
I already I already talked to a potential buyer out is like I said it will probably be slightly soiled and
I said, oh, I want it slightly soiled. They said they want it like that
We're and we're into watching before you sell it. I'm not going to that's the whole point
It's like it'll have my my sense on it. That's your question. Yeah
Do you smoke crystal meth or do you have attention deficit hyperactive disorder?
I do have ADAs. Yeah, I don't I don't I don't do drugs
Well, you seem like you're tweaked out all the fucking time
Well, it's not there for that because I do have a tendency that I guess rock a little bit, but
It's because of a I guess it gets a comforting
That's okay, I can ask you a question. Are you are you plastered right now?
I'm not drunk, no.
You're not drunk.
Why are you slurring your words?
That's how I talk.
It is?
But are you drinking a beer?
I drink water, I fucking water drink.
I know I'm not saying you can't, I'm saying,
but I'm saying, I asked if you were drunk
and you're like, no,
I think it looks like you've been drinking all night
and you're highly intoxicated.
I would not want you to
I'm completely sober
Oh, completely? Okay
You wouldn't even want to know how much it takes me to get drunk
Okay
Well, you're not a fan
What's your record for drinking in one night?
My record is
a pint of whiskey and 65 beers
Why'd you drink that much?
I woke up the next day and I felt amazing
Felt amazing and we're probably still drunk from the night before I would guess but how'd you feel the next day after that?
Have you ever
Slammed a pint of whiskey and fucking drank 65 beers on top of that
Never not one time. Yeah, I did it live
It is that like
Something you should be doing like you know showing anybody. I mean this thing sounds very reckless
Look, it just means I have a very high tolerance
Wasn't it like expensive I mean, it's like that's like probably a hundred dollars worth of
Would you do with the brand name beer was it like the cheap?
No, it was like cheap beer
Yeah, I can I can be probably 15 of those that are getting too drunk. I can drink a whole 12 pack without hardly a buzz from regular beer
but
So you're saying you're alcoholic
No, I'm not I've been cut way down. You're so mean. This isn't you're so mean to me. Why are you so mean?
Okay
Good times. What's wrong? Where are you? Why are you smiling?
You want to wait? Oh, come on Dingle Dingle. Come on
You want to we all want to have a nice long
I don't know if you know this, but you're like you're crashing out man. You're crashing out hard
I I know streaming is fun, but like
You're you're crashing off pretty hard man. Guys. Guys. This is the efficient of crashing out guys. Am I crashing out tell me?
Yeah, yeah
This is a crashing out worse than when you up worse than when he
Pulled him by my Aldi and was so fucked up. He couldn't even delete his stream or
When he like face cancer so crystal Marie we get naked is that that that guy? Okay, that's just making sure
anyway
Shocking shocking turn of events
I just want to fly. So I'll crush it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I say that bad
If I remember if I ever ever tell somebody they're passionate
Just like I don't know. It kind of was so ridiculous. I think that I hope you saw
I'm like I'm fine. I'm just I'm getting coffee. Yeah, I'm looking at the
delivery
If I can get the Einstein bagels, or not the Einstein, the Noah's bagels, if I can get a coupon, is there a coupon?
No, there's not a coupon. Shit.
Okay.
Is there a bagel place with a sail? Please. Somewhere with a sail.
And some coffee. Flying into the spine. Yeah, you fly until your dreams. It's great. Yeah,
I love to have a dream. I have dreams where I can jump up in the air and I can like stay in the
air for like, you know, I can fly in the air for like a few minutes. Sometimes I can fly higher, but
Anybody ever experienced that
I'm gonna check one you lost though your flying super high you don't recognize the countries from there
Wow, you're you you are high
I've dreamed like I've flown like right over this area like right over this area
I remember the dream like what was flying it was like right over down a beach
And I was flying above the water and I came above the land
But I did wasn't that high where I could it was like everything seems small. You sound like you're like Peter Pan
Yeah
so
Guys I feel I feel
Strange or or bad that good times since they're crashing out. I mean good times
He's talking about he's drinking 60 beers and a bottle of whiskey and there's something wrong with me. I
Don't know guys some people
Dog come on come on you're bad. I get that. Okay. Yeah, just yeah. Oh
Look, oh, I got 25 dollars. I don't want to buy that much
Do you ever have Vietnamese coffee? You have a good day, too. Yeah, you have a wonderful day
You wouldn't feel any way about it. Yeah, I'm not really I'm not worried about it. I'm not worried at all
They're in Dippity restaurant. Let's see if I want to go in free. Oh
That's too much food
Give some good deals here though, it's burritos toast and yoke
Looks good
He does is dropping the n-word and doing the h-h salute when Bita went
To get her band. Oh my god. He's a vital man. Yeah, I'm gonna avoid him from now on
It seems like I don't know if he was like going to do something. I think he was a too drunk too, but
I don't like the feeling I was getting from him
Looking for a nice bagel place, but I just looking for a sale. I don't think I've seen one. So
Thank you. Why do I hate black? Oh, no, I do not I love all people
You are being ridiculous and I did not pick it. Okay. I
Found you these Eastie boys. I'll be Eastie boys. That's cool. What do I get? Okay?
Ooh some of this looks really good. Oh, they have it's nice
half of
They have coffee. Oh, they don't have coffee. Oh, they do they do drinks
Liquid they don't have coffee. We just have liquid death
It's oh you oh you're you are good times 30 times
Who is gorgeous stack is oh, okay, okay, I see I see you're pointing up gorgeous stack you've been called out
Don't try to get something over my chat my chats the sharpest on on YouTube
Get to the bottom of everything.
Okay.
I know, I have a great, I have a, I'm so frickin'
blessed guy above, gorgeous stack.
Yeah, sad good times.
Good times, what happens to you?
Hmm.
Gosh, there's a lot of fucking breakfast places
But if I smart is just to get a something close by bagels
That's what you call him sad time
Well, it's all you know, we make our own life, right?
He seems like he's happy if he's happy hating on me and
$5 up $35 that's the best deal they have oh my gosh
He's happy making miserable and he's happy making people visible energy vampire
Yeah, I mean, I don't know him that well. It's like yeah, he seems like you know, he's not picked the
Happiest guy all the time, but
You don't have to be mean to me like I'm like not even a
I'm not a difficult person to be along with I don't think
Okay, Kings of the wine have it. All right. Yeah
Hmm Kings of the wine has an island breakfast. It says ooh, hold on
French toast two eggs and Portuguese sausage spam or bacon
I want to spam top with powdered sugar and serve with butter and maple syrup on the side
Okay, so I would like a breakfast combo with the spam
And the eggs
Over easy and
Damn it, they don't have beverage, okay, never mind
I'm hungry for a nice breakfast. I'm ready for a nice breakfast. I deserve one. I deserve it.
With coffee. Breakfast with coffee. Okay, there's a, oh yeah, this place doesn't have...
Yeah, so guys, energy vampires are everywhere. You know, there's people that are just like,
you're like, well, why are they here? Like, why did they come to this show? It's like,
they're here, harvest energy, harvest something else. If they don't like me,
Like what not like me then what are you here for I don't understand
Either for other people in my chat or something like that. I don't know
Because some people aren't even interested in talking to me. They're like, I just want to talk to other people and then like I
Don't mind. That's like, you know, I want people to go where they really want to I
Don't know what he's doing. Okay, so
This breakfast movies breakfast special
It's almost the same thing as the other one except no spam, but if you have a hot coffee. Yep
hot coffee I can get
French toast and
I can get bacon and sausage and
I can have
Over easy a
He's here to lease when viewers exceed the women on the panel. I feel like that's oh fun
You said you're a super fan. Yeah, please is awesome in page. I'm so happy started her show because
she
You know she started on here. Okay, so
Okay, 1499. Okay, that's everything for 1499 with the coffee included on the 18
third discount
Deal I had to put the deal on apply
Over $15 I need it said 1499. Oh my god. Well, what do I do in this case? I order like some
Side order
I can order a
Another coffee
And that too, okay done done
Let's take off my buzz now. Okay. Now it's now it's perfect
We're gonna have a nice breakfast today guys, there we go
Okay
No, I mean McDonald's only 20 bucks for breakfast anyway, but this I get to coffee. It's gonna be the same
I've only got five dollars off
So I added a copy and then it went two dollars lower than it was before
How do I take the order of stay out? I'm sorry 30 times. It took me forever. I was gonna say get something
It's something healthy, but all the food is dodgy. Yeah, well, there's it's LA here and it's like so there's like a lot of good restaurants
There's like a lot of
Casey
Yeah
To give you so yeah, yeah guys make sure you subscribe to prairie page and wildflowers, you know in this
I'm sure most of you know, beta and you know
You know page and other people that come here Sam and a lot of people have shows
There's a lot of content creators that come here a lot of their audience that does and so just welcome everybody
I'm I like to be friends with everybody some people ID ID subway, but I did not
this week
They have they have these daily subways. I think today's the tuna. She's really good
But uh, you can kind of make a tuna melt in the subway. It doesn't taste exactly like a tuna melt, but it's tasty
But uh, I haven't eaten that for a couple days. Last thing I had was the
pepper pepperoni pepperoni
Honey hot honey pepperoni sandwich pretty decent
I'm sorry it took so long to order the breakfast. I was looking for the right deal. I did it. I got it
Okay, so I'm happy
Hope you guys haven't
Any plans for the fourth they can cheese melts are nice from subway. Oh, yeah, I gotta try
Yeah, I've actually had I had the Philly. I think the Philly cheesesteak, but I didn't get
Like I had I kind of like just like you know custom made it so it didn't have like the right
You know really cheesesteak ingredients, but I think she thinks these though
real Philly cheesesteak has
You always use cheese whiz. I don't think so authentic ones
Yeah, there's also a jersey there's a subway right there across the street there's a jersey mics right there
So, I, you know, I haven't been to Jersey Mike's for a long time.
Yeah, my dad used to take me to breakfast every week.
Like, when I moved here, like every week, we, almost every week, we'd go to breakfast.
There's a place called Eden's shows. We must have eaten there like a hundred times, hundreds of times.
You know that place I love because they had alcohol plus they had you know two for one burgers on a certain day
Yeah, so it's been really hard because they used to go to lunch around here all the time even McDonald's sometimes they're
Take me to Jersey Mike's or try different places
So it's that kind of tea on this
Like getting to hang out
Yeah, but I have to say it's been like so crazy with like so many groups and like
Some of the groups are very malicious like I think it's like
I'm lucky that like it hasn't been without happy meals and had cool toys. Yeah. Yeah
McDonald's had bitter toys when I was a kid, you know
Now they have like Pokemon cards or some crap, you know
Yeah, but it's been so many like groups of people again that they mean like people there's so many like I don't know if it
like sense for other content creators or these like gangs or
These I don't there's just so much going on with
Like I don't know how it's almost every night. There's like some other I've been targeted by some other group and it's like wow
How does this happen in this your big pipe is here like doing excuse like doing some spying and doing black magic on me
Now he's lost his fucking mind like
The guys are just getting really like weird and like I don't like to I don't know much of creeps here
Like it's like seriously when people were like all
Hitting on page. It's like it just felt
Creepy and I felt bad for her and I was like trying to make jokes about it and stuff
But and it's like I don't like guys don't I don't know if guys see themselves sometimes
I know how like, you know
Here's all of it. It's like when they're trying to like woo a girl like I know it's like and then it's like
You just see her cringing the whole time and she's also it's also not the right time, you know, it's like, you know
I don't know what guys are just pigs
Not all guys, but I know I am I am a guy so
Try not to be a pig in our nature sometime
What is there she hates nothing I hate about page but people are but she still gets trolled right
She people just it'll troll any nice person. She's a nice person
She comes and I was a little triggered by some of the mean things said and
But then people also probably like or have a crush on her. So they're trying to get her attention
Oh, those many on page that that was creep. I know wasn't it that and I hope I just
Then she always like leaves and she wants to be on our own channel where she's gonna get people actually respecting her and stuff
Other than a bunch of oh, you're so beautiful and then good times. Oh, I want to I
Don't know. He's making different very lewd comments. He's like she was like she was asking trivia
She's like what is the name of this music my cock and stuff like that
Land appropriate
Because it's worse. He's a top creep on YouTube. Yeah, I think he's gonna use. Yeah, he was the honor
Like it was him and out and they were both wouldn't shut up
They both wouldn't they're both and then I kept and then
Then it's all out. I was like, well, yeah, it's like I felt bad the page was getting it pretty much
Actually, or else I think like what?
What then I said, he's a who did that? He's like, I'm just sad that when you were there
You were one of the people like that thing you were kissing or your dream and
It's a very erotic dream and you know, you're in love with her
You're saying all this your love and he's like whoa, you're pretty worried about now
She actually said that he had a where's she on I'm not sure if I'm asleep
Just scared the women away from the panel. That's why no one lets him on you guys didn't you help me out with the stuff
Yeah
I don't like when they know it's like and especially because it's like and you have like a lot of men on this channel like
Most terror channels will have mostly women
Except for like the only one I saw that didn't have most of them with like Emma's it she had like way more men than women
She had like 80% men or something. I have 55% men or something
He is scared of women. Yeah at 55% men and then like what that's like 35
Yeah, it's like so 45% women, right?
This is pretty low. I'm so kind of surprised. I have a kind of large male audience. That's really cool, but I just
Know would be the majority male. Hey, yeah, I guess I'm a kind of a guy's guy
And I know most guys here are like straight or
I'm like I'm probably usually the gayest person, but sometimes when the other guys look on the panel
They're gay side comes out and it's hard to tell who's the gayest sometimes
Yep, yeah, yeah, happy. Oh happy day. I don't know if you're in America or not even like you're in Russia or
Eastern Europe or England or France. I don't know where you are, but have a happy day
So page yet make sure you
describe the pages page of page because page is now doing stream yard and she's doing readings and you know, I think she's
I think she's gonna do really well here. I've noticed some women like to be treated like oh, well
It's hard it's hard, okay, it's like
Treated like crap and
Sometimes you have these things with these issues. I've seen it before I've seen it with Alisa or Lisa
Well, there's a couple guys that will call her and that's like she'll be like
I'll see like people the guys that call her like you're real nice and like I'm always I was always like trying to be sweet and like
you know just like
Kind of like platonic and stuff
But I think you're beautiful. I love you and then but other guys
Like this guy may mayor and the guy names
Spartan like just say hey you dumb bitch
Let's call her horrible things on the phone and then she's like you know
She always like kind of talks back to them and then it's like sometimes I've seen later in the show
She's like it's emotional and like I think people heard her feeling someone pay to ban ghost. Please. He gives me the creeps
Yeah
Yeah, he was on last night. You know, I don't know and people are people are telling me privately this this is who this person is
This person is like people some people seem to know some people are saying it's not I don't know
Always I can trust usually my mods to look out for me on this
But I don't know I think I don't know but I think women like to not be like they don't want a man to be weak
Right, they want a man that they think can defend them and stuff and we'll be like stand up and they can stand up to them
too, right, but they don't want to be abused they want I think they want to be
Challenge maybe challenge maybe or you know
Sometimes sometimes some of them I don't know
Yeah, I don't think you say oh women like you she's like she kind of gives like an open door like I'll just call it
Say whatever you want to the worst thing, you know, it kind of seems abusive to me
Oh look at piranhas here
Pretty good, how are you today?
Did you sleep at all tonight? Oh, I slept yesterday and so I was up tonight the night but uh
Yeah, it's 4th of July here. So it's a big exciting holiday, you know
Yeah, and we did it first
The Canadian independence day the Canadian
Okay
Okay, she just had it nice. Well
Happy independence day
Yeah
You see Mr. Big Pipes recently there's a guy Mr. Big Pipes that was on my show. Do you ever see this guy?
He comes on he comes on he plays banjo
Where's he where's he live guys? I don't know where you live
He plays banjo and he plays and then he plays like the harmonica and stuff
And he's like a little one-man band who's coming on and then it's like
They're starting to get really weird. He's are really hitting on page. It's like another one of those guys
They're just so weird with page like hey, like he's a he wants to play smaller and like
This is a pace and then he would play like a Beatles song for like hours
He started using this kind of like symbol as an avatar
That's a chaos man. I'm on for hours. Yeah, he'd be on for hours
Yeah, I might well sometimes I just have him in the background
He just be playing a guitar the back and then he could be very temperamental. He's just trying to chill
He's yeah, he's just trying to chill guys, but uh
Yeah, he's using some kind of avatar and someone's like it's a chaos magic avatar. Yeah, I'm just a big pie
Yeah, and uh, someone's like this. He got a fight with st. On a famous stream
He likes he likes st
He like all coaxing all coaxes eyeballs out because they're fighting and I think kind of fights dirty
I don't you see this it was over his guitar because they kept touching his guitar
I don't like a dirty fighter
Yeah, well, he said he's like, yeah, but mr. Big, thanks for fighting him too and like I wanted to ask you about something
Offset up me or mr. Who is somebody's only a chatter me. I'm sorry. Okay good
All right, so when it comes to like music on stream
What are like the rules for that, like you have to mute it, like when someone's like playing music.
Did you hear what happened to me, like what happened, like when I got, I got like strikes, like, well, you know, you only get three strikes, but I got the copyright claims.
They just went and copyright claimed over like 11 streams where that played as the intro and then it eventually got three strikes
Okay, eventually got three strikes that day. And so my channel was closed down for a week. They said they were closing down my channel
Yeah
There's a parade I want to go to tomorrow, but if there's gonna be like live DJs out there and I'm like worried about that
Well
You want to stream there or something? Yeah
Yeah, I say if it's like
You know, there's gonna be places where the it's like not so if I go into
The the fish market and they play music in the where you wait for the food
I just mute there if I walk by a place with too loud music just because not that even when we picked up or even if it is
most of the music they don't care you can just either cut it out of your video or
It's live.
Yeah, it's live.
But you can still, they usually won't pick it up
until after the video is filmed.
It won't pick up the copyright stuff.
Usually it does it within a couple hours.
But, or even longer.
I can hide it after.
Yeah, you can hide it.
You can, and then it's like,
but it should just give you the option
to cut it to trim it out of your video
and it will do it all automatically.
It will like say, oh, you can trim it out of your video.
We'll have like empty spaces in my video.
If you do that, there's options.
generic YouTube music playover you can have it fits out entirely or you can mute it so there's like a few options there and
But as well, I play I played a lot of music
Like the first couple months I was playing music I wanted to and then it's like I bench it would just say oh
This is copyrighted, but it would always say you can print it out or share the revenue or whatever
But then it happens so many times that I got like a community by
Warning on it and that was like for three months. You know, it was three months. Well, that warning is on there
And so it took three months for that to clear up.
And so, you know, it's like people that do false strikes
and there's also people that try to come on the show now
and say things and then flag the things that they say
for like, you know, there's a lot of things
that people trying to do.
You're just slugging yourself.
That's her, she's vindictive as hell.
What?
Yeah.
I've never flagged anybody. I wouldn't I say I don't care if people use my content
I'm like you're gonna re-stream me you can put me in videos you can you know by the way, you know Joe Shippley
Yeah
Here you do. Okay. I don't see this but there's something very shocking. I want to share with you
We do
Was he bad?
Little bit little bit. Not our Joe. Not our beloved Joe
Okay, you might be a little bit surprised, let's see, okay, so this is...
Triptych made this video, okay, one second, you'll probably have to take this out.
Okay, I'm gonna take that.
That's shame.
Fuck.
See, look.
Oh my god! That's so good! Who made that?
Frip kick and they made, there's several videos of me and like, you know,
40 Diamond Joe. That's so creative. It's so
bravo. I'm very proud of it.
I don't know if you ever saw the broke back mountain someone they didn't broke back mountain with Joker myself
And it was like it got taken down because their channel got taken down a bit
But yeah, it was Joker me and like we're like our faces are on the broke back mountain and we're like
Funny jokers been on the show a lot. Yeah. Oh my god. Jamie showed me a clip of Joker
I did not want to see oh
He pulled out his pants, he pulled out his pants, or he's like, um, the sweet, he's on a headstand, what do you see, do you have a headstand?
I turned away, but she told me not to worry that there was, that it ended, there was nothing to see though, okay?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, that was like, oh yeah, he pulled down his, uh, front of his underwear too much one time, and it was like, showed a little bit too much, and I was like, I just had to end this.
Yeah, it was kind of funny.
That is pretty he also like you know, I don't know if you know, but the 40-diamond fiasco, but yes, I saw her junk
I think she's yeah fantastic
Yeah, well Joker had paid her $20 for only fans like on my show
because this was
Everyone's so questioning
And there's one for one or only fans is $20 a month for only fans
There's one photo of her for squirting out breast milk
Um, and then if you want to like see more you have to pay a higher tier
So and so but then so very this guy in bear the turtle and Joker both
You know bought her only fans and there's all the controversy and then I mean
But she's kind of just like shaking up the cantilevers because a lot of guys were very attracted and then they're like
They got fooled and they're kind of more embarrassed and she has beautiful. She's beautiful and you know
You know, it's like a new day and age and that she's eating raging demon. I don't know if you know who raging demon is
Yeah
Their boyfriend girlfriend, okay home dirty old bastard. That's not nice. Yeah, and so
This is an assituation. I'm also have mini Manson on my show. I don't know if you know that that was my like second
Yeah, many handsome several times
Yeah
Several I mean I'm at four or five times one of the times it was a disaster and he yeah
I first saw him on a Lisa's like uh, it was a pretty much disaster interview over there, but uh
That's too bad when Joker did an interview with Mini Manson. It was like phenomenal
Well, yeah, and then but then I you know Joker and Minnie Manson have fallen out now and
I almost fell with Minnie Manson. Minnie Manson got really mad at me
They brought somebody on the panel when he was on at one time
Oh, that I know I didn't but I do I do I do like the name answer is awesome
You know do you Marty do you know the old Marty stuff? You know Marty and Jamie Rose remember Marty?
Yeah, but he pulled it
He's back. He's alive. Well, I slept the rumor. It's not
He thinks I did the Marty fake his death. Oh, that'd be great
So I didn't hear okay. Okay. I don't know. I don't know because I heard it was he was he had a
Fentanyl overdose and then there's a funeral, you know, he was a good nice Jewish funeral and stuff, but I
Don't
Yeah
Yeah, well
mini-manson is uh, I mean mini-manson is streaming and
It's we're working on a coloring book and also, you know, you're watch Howard Stern
The times you showed us. Yeah, well, there's a woman named Wendy the color Wendy the R.E.T.A.R.D.
But they already the slow adult now she's through the hour for years
So I had her on the show for a few hours or a couple hours
Yeah, and also I got raided by Shuli who's a producer of Howard Stern here
It created me from his show one day came in here and he was like wearing a wig and like but he I knew who he was
I recognized it from the show
His randomly came in like it was a big he has randomly came and rated the chat is really exciting as I just got monetized
so but
Monetization is going fine. Like, you know, I was the constant enter attack, but you know, it just doesn't seem to
Think kind of the bigger you get you get a little bit more protection from YouTube about stuff like you know
There I've had people like easy to restream me you restream me and then the restream
got
Like community violation or something like that mine didn't like
So I don't know how that works. You know, I don't know how it works, but I think it's like
Yeah
Yeah, I do think I have a I just got I had 250,000 views recently
I have like 2555 subscribers and I have almost a hundred members. I think I have over over 80 and so, you know
pretty cool like
So it's nice having making oh, yeah, making some my own money and stuff like that and
You know, it's really nice and then I'm having a lot of fun. Do I save any goals? Yeah
Yeah, I
Like my money I have so many things I need to have them working for so long
I think I need a new computer. I need you know, just some new stuff, you know, some other stuff
There's
Things I need that I could spend my money very quickly, but I do have a budget. I've been trying to drink less. I
Have been
Thank you. I just I just got some food delivered
Treat myself to a 4th of July breakfast, but I don't know if it's here yet. No, I don't think it's here
Yeah, so I also have this other thing where I have a thing where I kick I'll kick people off of panels for 24 hours for
$25 and
Yeah, and that has been
Very good idea
That is a great idea because not only are there guests that you know
Everyone wants them banned for 24 hours, but there's all and but also people can participate in the show and they kind of you know decide you
And also I can have the people's controversial that one on and you know, it's like
If the audience hates them enough they can just kick them, but you know, I don't mind talking to people
Everyone's max. I talked to this guy named LD. I love you. You know this guy LD is there's a guy
He's doing
It's annoying. There's a guy named Yacine. I don't know if you know Yacine or Yacine.
I'm very Yacine from Aldi's panel.
Yeah, yeah.
They stream the link for some reason. I don't know why.
Yeah, oh my god. Yeah, he's controversial.
There's all the, because every time some of the people come in the room, all these people come in the chat and say,
oh my god, you can't do this. You know what they did?
And then there's always some kind of like...
There was some kind of weird allegation like oh they were you know on a panel the minor came on the panel and
There's other stuff that you know, I never
Yeah, like a 15 year old like I but then it's like and then she like showed her bra or something. I'm not sure
Yeah, or yeah
Bad, but it was like yeah, and I'm not sure if he knew her age, but yeah, this is kind of dangerous to be talking about
always make sure you're
Talking to adults on on youtube, right? It's like
But yeah, a lot of guys they've meeting down there like they prefer
Obvious sides of the woman is over age instead of like a questionable
Appearance because they're just up of it. They're so fed up
Yeah, and now it's like it. I mean and now we have all these allegations
But everybody basically everybody I said people some people come in the chat
They call everybody these words and that's like it's just so
I think they just don't know what to say, you know, because imagine just trying to stick up a conversation with strangers, you know, like sometimes troll like helps give them some activity.
Yeah, there's no way they could believe all this shit that they're saying. Yeah. I mean, it's it gets ridiculous
But yeah, this like the trolling has been pretty pretty bad in my chat
I have a different communities of trolls come in. You know, I it started as a troll
It's totally communities came to the show, right? It just got worse though
You know, especially people like much fun like we used to ride of like a wave
Yeah, and it's like I'm doing it still I'm doing it. I'm having fun, but you know, it's like, you know
It's hard like, you know Bita and I are like always on the you know, he's going up and down and the back of like we're
Fighting most of the time. She's like, you know, she's he's like hate me right now
and then
You know, you know, Janet like, you know, the whole situation there was a nightmare
You know, I can't don't really talk to her very much
Then I had, you know, I had DJ Electra as a co-host, you know, it's like, and I think
I might have had another co-host, I'm forgetting, did I have another co-host for a little bit?
Oh yeah, Janet, I had Janet as a co-host, and then I had Electra as a co-host, and it's
like, Electra, you know, it's like...
People, he came out of a co-host and they're doing stuff in the back, like people just get so mad and they start yelling at them and blaming them and so it's not, so she's like, I should resign from that, from that stream yard mom because it's not a fun job, it's hard because it's like people want to like take off people and stuff, like they think she shouldn't be on the show and I'm going to have different standards for that too and so I just have to keep her facing.
But I had I do fall asleep sometimes which is kind of bad and it's like it's been kind of dangerous
Like I felt he was earlier on the panel wearing a kilt with no underwear
And he was trying to pour my all night and but I fell asleep like when you let's go on the panel alone
And then he's like when to move the camera and the camera actually turned off or he would have formed on me
but he was
So lucky because
Yeah
Your face glows up shut up
Because well, they've never like I've never
Got in trouble or even had a warning or anything. I've been pulling up over a hundred times
So I figure like that. I'm pretty good at like, you know handling them and stuff and so
You saw like when you see that you're stuck like a deer in headlights stalling to like exit like
Sometimes sometimes it's not on the stream yard screen. It doesn't play like if they play this video or something
And it they don't come up. It doesn't show on my stream yard or get it
I just sometimes people will be saying they're poor bombing and I wouldn't see it and then I just have to take their work for it
but uh
Yeah, I've been formed by like 30 diamond as they pulled down her top a few times on the show
Ilya showed his butt and then he peed in a bucket on the stream and then showed his penis
Joker almost showed his penis
I don't have Aldi showed it. Oh, yeah, Aldi did show his balls on my panel a long time and and we're bomb me
Some people have done this fake penis. They put their finger through the zipper or something like that
I was kind of fooled
Yeah, it can be annoying and it's like it's sad too because I mean I said I had like
250,000 watch hours or something like that like which is like oh, yeah, this is great, but then it's like
That's like my lifetime, but now it's like six, but it's like paired down to like 60,000 because of all the streams
I delete and stuff like that. So that's all the watch hours. I delete them. I delete them because if you private them
If they're porn bombing they can still strike people or they can still strike private videos and someone or someone has that URL and
Reports it still so it's like it. Yeah, so the porn bombs are like a good thing. No, it's not unless it's a good porn
It never is. I mean if a guy like
get snaked you know it's one thing and benefits like if they just put up some porno of like
if there's some blackout of the enormous penis that come exploding everywhere is
a poor gore bombing or um Nazi bombing they've done or inward bombing it's like it's crazy
I don't know it happens so often I've been uh well this one guy has like a
Yeah, it's calm down though it has because it's like I used to get like these text messages all the time
Okay, here we go
Okay, I used to get these text messages all the time like threatening and like I go get pieces sent to the house I get like you know
You know, but that's how the police came and so that was a little bit of a different situation
You have a picture of Joe should these balls DM them to you psyche. Okay, then send them to my discord. Okay?
No
Well ask him I'm sure he'll
Private, you know, I'm just kidding. I really I don't want to see but you know
Some of these guys, though, Barry the turtle sent me a picture of his
You know, do you know Theo? Theo gate? I don't know if you've ever heard of this guy. Theo gate
He has a show, but he's like kind of a cute white guy, but he like
Yeah, he's a picture of his dick. He's gonna be too dick
Yeah
Yeah, so you know a lot of people that was
Yeah, he's not gay. He's not gay
He just shared his dick pic with me.
I asked for it, and it's like, okay,
those are homies.
He did like a homie.
It was very sweet.
But yeah, there's another interesting.
That's so funny, it's a gay homie.
Do you know Chris K?
That's gay, that's gay in the park.
Yeah, I know, it's okay.
Do you know Chris K?
So Chris K said that he would do a...
Shatterbait collaboration with me and he would he'd say I could pick up the girl or something like that and we could do gangbanks and
And then he's like, oh, yeah, then maybe we can do some gay shit like for donations or something
You know, so what would you make in that face?
Okay.
What?
He's silly.
Then he said, but then he like,
then he, I think he like,
I think he was kind of drunk,
but then he was like,
then he started like realizing it
and he started like,
he's like, oh, this woman downstairs
is hitting on my door.
I want to have sex with her.
I don't know.
He's like, I should probably,
eventually he left tonight.
But he's into black.
Hold on.
Chris K. is cloudy, he's into black.
He's like, his neighbor,
his neighbor needs sex.
That's true.
That's why she hears every little detail
and she can't sleep at night.
You know, he should be neighborly he should be nicer to her
He shouldn't be seeing death threats and shit like that like no man. It's going about it the wrong way
Yeah
I know he didn't ask my opinion, but
So much that happened on the show though, it's like, you know, yeah, you know, you've heard about my you've heard about by following out with like, you know
But well some friends are traveling gypsy, but you know clumsy clairvoyance. I'm banned from her
I'm banned from Emma's channel to the extent where my name is banned in her channel. I'm ban on all my accounts
She
With Emma. Yeah, I got worse. I got worse
They kept I kept trying to contact I kept on these go and get readings and stuff or they go under different accounts
And then they she's like things I think some calling all her work line or prior work numbers
I never had a work number people are telling her things like
people are calling her work numbers and yeah and and and Christine's or someone told me that
blade had told her that I was on meth as the mod or something like that and then she changed her
opinion of me they said so he's a huge method yeah he has hallucinations
Okay, like I'm everyone like who needs him and talks to him like notice is it like
Made her judge you I don't think so I don't think so because I'm sure there's a lot of methods that she talks to
From YouTube and you know, I don't know. Yeah
Well, I can't go delete. Huh? Yeah, I think she's just trying to you know stick to her goals, you know, and see what feels right
And then with Alisa like I started like saying oh everyone go to Lisa's chat like when I my shoes sometimes
I would go hang out there
Then people started like harassing her from my from my chat harassing her saying I'm send I sent them to harass her in her
Chat or like the same that I'm a method or other terrible
Parable accusations in her chat and but she knows it's not true or she's like you know
She also gave me good advice to let me interview a bunch of times like I'm streaming all my show and stuff
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, she was she said I can call her when she's like sitting in her car and stuff at the end of her show
And then like I can have it I can have someone share the stream on my side and then just have her
So she's been like that Chris K the real Jeffrey Dahmer on the panel
So Chris K was invited a black homeless dude. She was house and stream yard it the sexual tension awkward
Because the poor guy was so sleepy
And you just sat on the chair where like fuck poor guy. They let him like lay down somewhere or something
It's so sleeping. Well, I don't know. I would be careful about bringing people into my apartment. Like, I don't I don't know
You don't know it. He's definitely goes live and he's on okay
Well, he's tits the unmet the gate. Well
I think truckers and maybe streamers are to uppers, right?
Because it gives them energy to stay awake.
See him not lying.
She didn't see the entire stream.
No, you're not lying.
That's it.
Yeah.
We see it.
I know 30 times.
It's like if 30 diamond in good times had a baby,
it would be 40 times.
That's how cool this is.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
With all the best qualities.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, but I do that was
It's annoying to see all these streamers single all the time. It's been like a year
Well me
Me being single. Yeah, I had it why the disaster is I
Know but well Joker was supposed to come visit me and then it's like, you know
That I was like, I don't know if you were there for the Miser days as guy in Miser. I kind of like
He dated him for like a day or two or two that didn't go through too well
But it's like I don't know but I have I'm kind of have these options now though where it's like I have
People don't want to stream with me like you know come visit and stuff and so who knows
To fund all of his online friends to come visit him
Oh, yeah
Well
I went to Danny because I got a free membership to Danny's so I went to Danny's recently and then I like asked about his
Asked about buying his underwear again, and he was like
He's like psyche. He's like you always ask me and you never you never do it
He's like he's like you're gonna say just hit me on Instagram if you want my underwear and we'll make a deal there
He's like stop asking me that oh my god, but he's serious, but I think he charged too much
Sorry, I don't know.
What?
I DM you.
Did you see this?
Did you see a video of Chris K, a BBC site?
Oh, my God.
I want to see it.
Do you have that?
I'd like to see it.
Put it in your hands.
Are you on my Discord?
You can DM me there or you can come back to my backstage.
I can put some information in the private chat.
The email address for you, okay?
Yeah, I'm thinking about that. Yeah, so Chris K is like serious. He's like yeah, he's like I'm not gay
He's like I'm not gay, but then he's like proceeds to like be very open to some
Yeah
Like I don't know if I could f you up the a but
He said he didn't know it wasn't like oh, I can't you know, he said I was like, oh, we'll see we have
Yeah, I think he needs another he needs another female in the mix though. He thinks I'm gonna go out there and find I'm like
I don't know. He's like hey, maybe he thinks I'm pretty good looking or something that I think I'll be better draw than him
But I think he'd be better. I don't know. I'll be interested in this and him
Let him like be distracted by her boobs and stuff and I
Get behind them and no, I went. I'm just good. No, Chris. I would not do that
What is it Piana's type of guy if I run a type of guy she's into
Strong kind of funny in smart. Oh
Little tech. Well
Yeah, like I don't know if you know, you know page, right? You see page on my show page is a prairie page
Yeah, it's like, you know, she's
Single right now, but you know, it's kind of newly single and she just has all these guys creeping on her like, you know
Mr. Big Five's was then good times was and just good times was saying vulgar things there Alex was Alex was and it's like
They've kind of like these like all the guys that
So they totally creep out of early and everything in love with their stuff. It's like so so weird and then
They're going to like, well, I'm just basically,
they creeped out beyond my show now,
you get by all you guys,
and so that gives her more time for her own show.
I think they were just to respect her more over there,
or at least she can take care of the trolls as she wants to.
But it's kind of sad.
I hate people being scared off of the show.
I even grabbed my coffee at the door
and made breakfast one second.
Oh, you had coffee?
Yeah, I ate two coffees and a breakfast for less than 20 bucks.
Where is he got stairs? Yeah
I'm
Oh, let's say there's one coffee though. I think they forgot my head
to
Like he has enough caffeine
Like no, you know
Like my phone case
Yeah
Yeah, wait, I'm telling I'm showing the crowd. There's this one. All right, this is my old one
Okay
Here's my coffee. Yeah
Wow
See it's a tiger
I like it. You see mine? Like mine's the color of Lisa's car. Oh it does! Oh my god! And I have the green version. It's my older one. I couldn't look. I was looking for new phone cases. I didn't like any of them. Then I saw like my old one. I'm like, oh my god. It comes in my new phone size.
This is my outfit for the day pie.
Oh my goodness.
I mean, I'm auctioning these off after the show, too.
I mean, it's gonna be in the house.
Maybe I'll take a shower and then again, too.
I took a shower last night and everyone was watching.
I also, unfortunately, decided to be fun.
I decided to be funny and put my legs behind my head.
And then now it's people's profile pictures.
It's on clips that people are making, you know.
me with my legs and also making a G string out of the out of the speedo. It's embarrassing.
Yeah, I mean, yeah
We're just having fun. I was drunk at like at like three in the afternoon and in the first beat of that
I was like taking a shower and I was
And then Benny I was just having so much fun and everyone was encouraging it
They edit hold this whole chat was encouraging it and now
Now everyone's saying I was being weird
Okay
Dingo, hey, I'm just kidding. No, it's okay. Everyone, everyone really, everyone really likes it
Everyone really like everyone really liked that thing except for well the guy
And like someone did like a restrictive video the complain about me flagged it because I was like
You know, you're not gonna be able to please
Me I mean, I'm like I look like a huge skeleton, you know, I mean it's just it was like more like ridiculous than it was
Yep
I'm hopefully it's pretty good, but I kind of my shyness it seems you know, it's like
Are you just eating takeout or are you cooking too?
Well, and whole foods, I'll pick up whole foods some food of whole foods and stuff
or subway or
Look at this syrup and butter
Let's see how this looks guys
Pancakes oh and bacon
Yeah, nice
Yeah, I love sausage
I used to never be into sausage was always like dry and gross until like found a way to do you know do it myself
Do it nice. Mm-hmm
There you go, so you're doing
Huh
You would are you dating anybody? No, no, I just got out
I'm not ready yet, but I am happy that I did lose enough weight to get into one of my older dresses because I'm having fun to go out tomorrow.
I'm cool.
Yeah.
Being single is fun too, especially when you're like going out and socializing a little bit.
So that's awesome.
And then next weekend, there's another one.
There's another festival, but it's more about food.
You see the question on the screen.
I'm from Canada.
Oh, she takes girl.
She doesn't want to admit it.
It's weird even like my ex when we were still dating like he was like getting paranoid about that. I'm like why?
no sense
Well Vicky I'm ready. That's why your boyfriend. I want to meet we've been together for seven months. Yeah, a lot of people are ready, you know
But yeah, it'd be too hard for me to date somebody now, but yeah
So, Piranha, isn't Canada, guys?
Actually, we have like 7% of my show
is the Canadian viewers.
It's like 40% of it is like, hold on,
like 75% is like US, then 8% is Canada,
then the UK, some other countries, too.
And yeah, I know Canadian beauty,
you bet, and I count for you, yeah.
You look close to George's back.
Oh my God.
You guys have the Sun all year round and that beach
Well our pools ready, let's go get the nerve
By the way, it's he's been on the show several times. I can still let him on
But he has poor balmy with Peter's boobs before he has
He said he was gonna unalive himself on my stream by drinking himself to the EATH
He needs a wellness shot the hell he's a he's anywhere by me
He he took his he took a shit on for your diamond stream and then
Yeah
And so yeah, he's been basically very bad and also like this friend 300 glow, you know for a glow or three and glow
yeah, he's
He came on and said he wanted me to watch him have sex with his wife
backstage and then show me his armpits and then
And then and then what you did yeah, you're so drunk he did
Well, the next day, I think he chickened out, but I did something, but he chickened out
and then he was coming back and now also Stig says he's gay and he wants to have sex with
him.
He's going to come to California to see three-year-old Glow and not me, and he's going to have
sex with three-year-old Glow, he said.
You guys got to all hang out together.
Oh my God.
I don't know.
I think a little bit.
You ladies like to do.
Yes.
That'd be fun.
Um, uh, what's it called the be Airbnb like that those house and or maybe have people come in like, you know
And like we go to like some like kind of
No
Well, they are insured. They don't allow for such a live parties though
You feel like they if they rent today, they can't they have to say they're not gonna be a party or some things
So no, it's gonna be quiet. It's gonna be quiet over here. You know, it's like just the fireworks them, you know
Party will be inside my house. This is the 4th of July party guys. We're starting with the breakfast. I
Don't know. Maybe I'll have my other beer today and then with some more beers. Oh, yeah, it's like celebrate
Yeah, I've been drinking a little bit less and like, you know trying to
Do a little bit better, but you know
Hanging in there. Oh my Russian my Russian my Russian friend is out of prison. Oh
shit
Hi
Yeah, well she was then she's in like a rehab. She got she got an early release so she could get a GED
And then she's in like a rehab facility kind of thing where she's doing that and then she'll be able to go at get out and
Apply for the firefighter would be a woman's firefighter because she did that firefighting program
And so and she sounds like she really wants to get sober and she sounds really good
I told me yesterday she's broke up with her boyfriend or that old boyfriend
And then now she's talking to some other guys. She was with and oh
She was with him before
Yeah, she's with this guy. Well, she was with this guy and then she cheated on him with this other guy that he knew and stuff
And then because he went to he got locked up
He went if you would hit get the gun charges for error 15 and so yeah, so he was locked up to the other guy running around and
then
And so then she found out about it because she got arrested
and then they were trying to work
and he just sent her a text message saying like,
oh, he's trying to send it to her chick to hook up
but she accidentally sent it to her.
And so she's like, oh, you know, I'm just gonna go with it.
That's why, and she's like, so she sounds good.
But it's like, yeah.
I haven't seen her yet, but she calls me,
calls me, you know, she comes a week, so.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
She's better. Yeah, I know she's a better
Stay of mine. I hope she wants to be continue to be sober. That'd be awesome
We don't wait. I wanted to be for my speedo. You'll join me. I don't have I'm data on my phone, but I'll be like a
Shower stream or like just leave this one. I know I also I was like, I don't know if I like maybe there'll be families there
I don't want to be like running around a speedo in front of like
How can I never go it's kind of packed like I go to the pier I've been to the pier several times
I get fish tacos. It's kind of a joke because I'm in cartoons now
one of them is called the butthole scam one's called the Mexican pizza lady and one's called
I'm turning into a fish taco because I started getting these fish tacos and everyone's like oh my god
He's obsessed with fish tacos. He's yeah
The cartoons are on Lord of the Groove if you go to Lord of the Groove on YouTube and then you'll see
The psyche awakens once if you go to the videos. It's just pretty recent. There's just three of them. They're like pretty short
You can probably
Take them out
They're pretty they're pretty what's that okay, yeah, I think you'll love that's still pretty funny
Lord Lord of the what the groove Lord of the what the groove g.r.o.o.b.
90 subscribers
90 subscribers 2.k. subscribers. Okay
It's a black
Do you see it? I do see them
There are videos are probably a couple rows down
Live
This is not playing the cartridge if she plays them
they're not gonna play on my screen, but I want her to see them and
They're not there. They're not the Alex cartoons all over
Yeah, that one's good too. They have streamers talking about like I'm being stopped
I've been hundred and hundred people calling my work. Please stop. Yes. It's so scary
But do you see the Secky Awakens?
Yeah.
This guy, right?
Yeah, I should say Secky Awakens.
Shorts.
Oh, no, it's in their videos.
It should be right above those gangstalker videos.
It's like just a few rows down.
Latest gangstockers goblin tales lord of the psyche awake
Yeah, you play them because it's my voice and so it's my
Yeah
I'll share the screen.
Oh yeah, you can just watch it,
because it's like, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm,
yeah, I just, I'm really careful about playing stuff.
Oh, you don't want me to share the screen?
No, you can just watch, I want to see your reactions
just to watch, you watch, okay, that'd be awesome.
Because you can, you can, you can hear the audio,
because that's my audio, but this is like,
I don't know if they want me to use the cartoon.
You just see a buffalo until it's eaten.
Did you see it?
New roll.
They after.
And so, yeah, the piece of lady was...
You're saying he's so happy. Aldi, look at that.
What does the Aldi's did, don't you?
Okay, for Aldi.
Oh, that was good.
So then, when I was having all these issues with the strikes and stuff,
someone was like sending all these pizzas to my house.
So that's the Mexican pizza lady was.
Yeah.
I'm hungry
Okay, oh, they're so short. Okay. Yeah
Oh, but where's the food?
Some Mexican pizza, the fish taco one is the best one,
I think.
What's that?
Oh, you kind of cut out a little bit.
The fish, I'm turning into a fish taco one is the best.
Are you watching it?
Watch my...
I might have been trying that day. I'm not sure
They got your clips. I was like, oh, actually I'm kind of funny
such a medic
That's good. He's awesome. My goodness. I'm something he's live
He's live. Did you see the alex one? I don't know if you saw this one
Well
It is live
What are you doing? Oh
Yeah, I'm lagging I can't watch it
Oh god
Oh, yeah, have you seen this one? Have you? Watch this one?
We need what are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and
I've been speeding on the freeway. What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna say sir license registration. I'm gonna pretend it's bad
I'm gonna say step out of the car, and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes
I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, oh my god. I'm gonna in the in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make hot car and just fall my way
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
Yeah, and I love Alex and it's like moments like that like, you know
Well, there's like a parts you there's like a little part in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna get in my top court and just go my way unless you want to go to jail
I can just can't cuff you ticket to jail. I can fuck you on the side of the highway. It's up to you
Okay, thank you guys everyone Alice be controversial
But Alice, he's a sweet guy.
He's a sweet guy.
I'm very sweet.
I'm a sweetheart.
I'm a lollipop.
You can lick me like a lollipop.
How many licks does it take to get to the middle of a tootsie, pop?
Alex, can I try can I can I lick your tootsie pop Alex? Oh, yeah, baby. Oh my god. Okay. I love I got I love this guy
This good. This good. He's my he's my he's my cutie, but he's my he's my cutie, buddy
He gets in that you in the police uniform a handcuffs in the bed and he f's the f out of me
I'm so happy.
Alex and I are fighting right now.
We're fighting right now.
I had to kick him off the show this morning.
And then he comes on screaming about R-A-P-E of like,
it's just a really disgusting.
He comes on screaming, accusing people of my panel of that.
And I had to end the panel and bleed it
because it's like he's just screaming at that.
And I kept on kicking him off,
but it's like, you know, he's the kind of person
that's like, I like, do you know Alex?
Or no.
Yeah, I met him through Theo, and that's also, I think, where I met Frankie too.
Yeah, I mean we know so many of the same, it's like so crazy, like so many people here know you and like, hope you made some new friends.
Are you doing livestreaming yet still?
My social network is so burnt out.
I'm trying to like reserve it so I can actually like talk to a human, you know, yeah
Well, I think you know, I like when you did you're like, you know
Just even if you just did your reading and stuff like that if people like that
I haven't done it in so long when I went to visit my niece and nephew
It was hard to like read them stories all over again, so she's like they're getting their levels are getting up
Oh my god, I should read again. Just like practice
I'm motivated.
We'll see if I go out tomorrow.
We'll see.
Did you finish your school?
I know you were doing math classes.
I switched. I want to start something else.
Because the school I was in,
they changed something,
and they would have made it much longer.
I was like, fuck that.
So I switched something else.
It's not started yet though.
Yeah, you don't take cool
Yeah, well, I just got my cows kind of well someone came and helped me clean my house the cats are all good
No, I mean, I'm pretty good
Those going good I mentioned me a lot, you know, I probably see how much I stream. Yeah
Who is there you were
No, my ex was.
Your ex was?
Yeah.
Who's your ex?
Oh.
What I know?
You would never type that though.
The lurker.
There's a lot of people.
Today I had like 20 people in the room.
I had like 20 people in the room and like no one was typing.
Like no one.
For like half, like no one typed anything.
I was like, are there 20 people here watching?
And they're like not, no one's typing anything.
Because we are sometimes and then I can sometimes like I had over a hundred people in my chat at times
You know and and we've had like a lot of controversy and like
you know then
Beat is going after me sometimes and they will be just being really mean to me right now
She's like she's saying oh, she's like I'm doing tarot now
And I'm gonna oh, she just wanted to give me a reading but then it's like she's just making it up and saying just mean things about me
She goes
I'm gonna expose you and
She's like you're just you just you just everyone's like this one dick. Are you one is dick and?
You can fish talk. I want to dig in fish tacos dick and money and fish taco
Why do you think that's mean?
She knows what you want deep down. Come on. Yeah, I don't know
She's been so mean to me and then it's yeah, she's always mad
You know, I never get mad people. I'm always like gonna be like, you know, sometimes I'll get up fight
You know, forget, but I'll fight with people that when I get drunk sometimes, too
And if they yell at me and I get defensive and I can get in an agitated state
Amalicious or anything for it. I was like, I wasn't like Casey Clark or honey
She's like, I made I made you like I did all this like I think she came to my I think I met her after I started
Oh, no before I heard her do open panels and stuff like that. My show was they I was my show was okay
I had a few people in my chat. I wasn't even like you were gonna be hot you didn't make you
Well, you know, I think yeah, yeah, she would say it herself all the time
Well, I mean it's like yeah, and she's talented too. I don't think I hope like she doesn't think I think you know
I had like
Yeah
She was mad one day because she's like how much have you sent me as they I've never even seen a cash app or any kind of
Donation thing or anything. That's why it's why they never really saw like
And of course, I really appreciate everything she's done for me, and she brought a lot of people, but it's like, she kind of, like,
wanted me to, like, she would demand people off, like, what time LD was on, he had not misbehaved on the panel,
she'd be like, get him off, get him off, and I'll count to ten to one for you to get him off,
and then I was like, but I was like, no, because I'm not just going to, like,
Let's do it. Someone tells me to do like I'm just off to like report that comment move on what Vicky?
Vicky come on. Do you report the comment Vicky? That just hurts my show. Okay, so just let a mod know and a mod would lead it
So you don't have to
To worry about that, right?
You don't want to harm my channel because I can't control people in the chat
So mods and it's like if there was like, you know use use use
This is kind of a gentler language, maybe, you know
We have also all kinds of people of all men all different mental capacities in the room sometimes
And we don't offend anybody. Okay. I think he is joking because she said the R word first
Okay, are you joking Vicky? I can't tell you my cat is just much a jokester. Yeah
But I do want to, I do want to go eat those.
Nice seeing you.
Okay, sweetie.
Well, great talking to you.
Thank you for coming to the show and checking in.
You know, I'd like to see you more often, you know,
and I'll try to make, you know,
look out for you better than I did last time.
I know I still have, you know,
a lot of little work to do myself, but hopefully.
We all do, you know, me too.
Hopefully we can, yeah.
Hopefully we can hang out again soon.
Love you, huh?
Bye. Thanks for stopping by.
Very good to see you.
Yeah, that was cool, guys.
Yeah, it's always nice to make peace,
to be able to come to understand.
So I'm kind of, this breakfast is like,
I'm a little bit disappointed,
but first of all,
they left off one of the coffees,
because I thought I ordered two coffees,
and there's only one.
Have to check my bill later. I can always like they're gonna be fun for that, but there's mostly pancakes. I
Already ate the bacon. I thought it would be bacon and sauce. It was just bacon
There are some eggs left
Those from pancakes
Can't say anything bro, okay
Okay, but yeah, I just didn't know because I was like when people said they're I see people that I reported the channel
Yeah, I get a little bit. Ah
It looks at a copy. I'll see if they did because I'm not a hundred percent sure they did I might have like this
I thought I thought it was the combo, but I'll check out the
Continue. Okay, so could you help help?
What can I help you with issue with items? Okay, and that should say
Okay, though, I guess there was no I guess there wasn't a hot coffee
It's I thought of the breakfast special they asked you
Well, they asked you what?
Drink you what and I put a coffee and then I ordered an extra coffee to get the bill up
Yeah
So it's okay
still worth it. You always joke around, yeah. I like to joke around, too. I love a good joke. It's like,
you know, I hope I don't lose my sense of humor, like dealing with some of the stress of the show.
Because it's like, I like to joke. That's why I like some of the jokesters. I like that
mischievous, prankster, you know, and I like the rule breaker
archetypes and, you know, people that are testing on boundaries.
There's a time and a place and it's like even they know it's like they know there's places
They behave and there's places that they can just go hog wild trolling, right? Yeah, I mean it's like
Really behave you couldn't go hog wild trolling in my chat as long as you
behave, you know, it's not do this like easy like illegal things or things that can harm the channel, right?
it's like just to protect the platform because there's a lot of people that are out to
Don't know little people successful at all kinds of stuff, but now you have too much sugar you go loco. Yeah, I
Know, you know, it's like all there's like a drug. It's like a serious drug
You go for loco
Yeah
But the thing about going crazy is that you can always probably claim temporary insanity
I love sugar, but I'm cutting back it down on it. Happy 4th of July. Traveling gypsy and happy July 1st
See you. I'm sorry. I forgot to wish you happy Canadian
Independence day your cookie jabroni
Well, do you think you're bad?
Sugar in this coffee has gotten me
wild
five loco
How about six loco?
Thank you, Vicky. Thank you everybody. I tried to put an emoji in the chat like in the members
They weren't uploading appropriately. So
I'll try again later
Infinite loco. It's crazy forever loco low key
Luck luck
Lucifer else okay, I'll see
Hello Vicky
Hi Vicky six-minute abs
Oliver we've been a personal trainer train me naked
Thank you travel AGFC
We can do some cards for the chat this morning
We'll do from the regular Alice deck
Let's do a little Alice reading collective. I'll do five. I'll do six card reading for the chat because it's special
Hold on fourth of July
But I'll give you a bonus two cards. So you still have six six cards
And I'll make a little story out of it as much as I can who's a dirty bird
Oh, it's your 28th anniversary.
Well, happy, oh, 28th anniversary.
Where's your X?
Okay, though.
Happy anniversary, as they would say in Alice in Wonderland.
Okay, let's see.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Well, it's kind of interesting.
A lot of little stuff going on.
Okay, there's a lot of little things going on.
Okay.
The flowers, I believe the flowers are going to be the wands.
Okay, so you get this three of flowers. So this is like this, you see how they're like all,
like this one's even, it's like coming in the opposite direction, but they're all kind of like in
the same vibe. They kind of fit together, they work together perfectly. There's some kind of
You need to collaborate with people.
It's always like, they also look like hands,
like extra hands are needed in this situation.
And so, you make sure you ask for support,
or maybe you've been asking for the support,
you've been asking for some kind of support
to come to you, okay?
And then we have the four of hedgehogs.
The four of hedgehogs is gonna be the four of pentacles.
And so this is like this happy home environment.
This is like you've been working to create this secure,
safe, happy, comfortable home.
You're managing your resources carefully
and you're comfortable and secure
in your settings right now.
I think, oh, the cat, no, my cat Lola just came over
and she touched this car, this is the page of Panicles, okay?
So this means that
There's something very new.
There's some kind of new venture that you're undertaking
or some kind of new, it's still a little kitten,
but this kitten is like, you know how cats,
even the kittens are smart,
but the cat will be even smarter, right?
So you're gonna gain some experience
as you go through this.
Look at things with a beginner's mind
or like a childlike mind, an innocent mind.
And,
And go for your dreams because the kid that could read the cat and then there's like she's looking at the store
The store novice she's like cats like how do I open that the cat will be eventually be able to figure out how to open the door
The cat will be able to you right?
This is the king of cups. Okay, so this is like
This is, you know, the King of Cups is like very, you know, master of his emotions, but
he's also, you know, he's kind of a softy, he's like, you know, maybe he cries, maybe
he drinks a little bit much, but he has a big heart, and, you know, he loves a good
drink sometimes.
It's the King of Cups, what it says here, you know, and the Cups are all about emotions,
But it says
The king of teacups represents a kind caring paternal figure who tries to his very best to help with his guidance is sought
When his guidance is sought if you're feeling overwhelmed by a challenge or conundrum
The king of teacups suggest that you seek out the wise advice of someone with experience on these matters and your best interests at heart
Well, that's great advice
Okay, next we have this to a source and so what doesn't say is this crossroads because I think like so that we've the cat and then the doorknob, okay, then
so there's this like the
some kind of
Crossroads, you know, because it's a cross right there, but it's also, you know, you can't see entirely what's ahead of you or entirely
What's behind you so you have to know very much use your intuition at these next coming points to
Help you open the door and lock the door find the key. Maybe you can pick the lock with like a little one of these
Spears or maybe
These are like scissors or something like that cut something out of your life
You'll know what to do, but there's two of swords and
Finally we have the nine of flowers. Okay, so the nine of pentacles Wow
So this is like almost a ten of pentacles. This is like
You're gonna make the right choice at this path at this juncture. You're gonna make the right choice that will lead you to like this
material abundance and
You know you see the nine of you know the nine
I think he has his feet on
Penicles and he has the pinnacle on his head and his on in his lap. I think that's the nine. Okay, so nine says
It's the night of flowers, right, okay
Anna Flowers, advising you of courage when defending your ideas, you may not be feeling
like you're alone in the defense, but that doesn't mean you should back down, rely on
your vision and passion to overcome the current challenges.
Yeah.
And so you may be feeling a little bit defensive, but it's like, look, there's all this protection
around you, too.
And I said, you've got this really big thing growing, you were trying to get this to the
10 of Pentacles.
You're almost there.
You're almost there, right?
I'll pull like a word of advice for the chat.
Your word of advice is the king of pentacles.
Okay, so it's this guy, I think it's a carpenter, right?
You know, the member of the walrus and the carpenter.
Yep, there's the walrus and the carpenter.
And so this is the king of pentacles.
And so it gets this guy had a great idea about,
with oysters and, you know, shucking oysters
and, you know, it might not be the most humane idea, but.
I think it was maybe lucrative.
Let me see.
So the king of panicles, but it's also, you know,
he's basically a master of the physical world
and the material world and enterprising.
The king of hedgehogs is a masterful person
who has built his success through hard work and persistence.
Take inspiration from the carpenter
who uses his skills to build a restaurant
where he can make his dinner dreams come true.
Set yourself or set yourself up through discipline and dedication. So that is your that is your
Advice set yourself up you discipline it dedicated
Focus like this is like a
There's a lot of just things you can look at cards
See how they're they're connecting and stuff like that
We demand we the door knob with the cat and we have all these
all these emotions all these flowers and a bunch of coins to start something and so
I do hope you found that useful and enjoyed that reading.
Anybody want a personal card? Please tell it low-key to do her barn chores. Oh.
Happy Anniversary!
Yeah, do circles of protection guys. That's the best, uh, you know always remember magic
They there was this circle of protection you would evoke around yourself first because it would keep out these other entities
But it gets tricky when you're inviting these entities into invoking them
So it gets tricky with like letting the circle be open around you or letting the circle be like you within the circle
Who said what?
They have me blocked
Oh, and the circle of protection is Dingle.
Happy Anniversary Low Key, Traveling Gypsy, I don't know,
Dingle, Dingle says circle of protection.
Maybe your chat is on, not on all chat,
it might be on top chat,
and so you don't get all the chat messages,
but if I put this on,
if they should come up on the screen now.
Or not those ones but everyone from now on
So my hair is kind of a mess
They must know me or they blocked you to do your barn chores
They must know me here, but your barn chores, what do you you're not talking about some kind of cow
Easy what's up easy? Oh my god. I've seen some videos that are like wow. I'm just that made me go wow
Okay back to work. You have a wonderful day. Happy 4th of July or you know, I know you don't celebrate it, but
You two you have a great day. You have a great day at work. Thank you for coming Teresa
Hey easy. Yeah easy. I saw the video you tagged me in where that you're it was said like I said, oh
patrols are on their way or something and then that woman
tagged me in a video and
I'm in the video in my speedos
With my legs be on my head
But I do like how you handle it like I like how you handle it
That was kind of a
Shock but they hey buddy we're in this together. Okay, I got your back
Crazy
Yeah
None of them except it's it's funny how some people just focus on certain people like and like how they found you or
Sometimes they're for more fans. Sometimes they're just crazy. Sometimes they're
These moral crusaders. I just have no idea what she's so focused on you and you know
But
Yeah, easy to be the great guy and I ordered my deck today. I'm going to order a deck today.
Yeah, new deck, new deck. Thank you, easy to get. Really appreciate you. Dingle has everybody in chat.
I hope you like that reading. She's, yeah, that's crazy. controlling has been crazy. Yeah, so Pi was
Yes, new deck, there's like a bunch of really cool ones.
I don't know which one I should get.
I'll have a look at my list.
Okay.
Yeah, I always love a new deck too, because it's like,
actually there's a lot of decks that I saw
that are like, some are like, the more like, you know,
One's called like the evil eye tarot. You met her before me. Oh, that's it. Yeah
I was there you remember before me. Yeah, I was mischievous
She we just said like a better nap like an hour about an hour interview and it wasn't really well
Yeah, I was real cool
I was here when I started I think actually I saw like one of her lives and I was like I'm gonna do stream
I mean, I thought about that before but I was like I really got motivated like this one night
That I thought I was on her show. And so then I sent up her stream yard
Then I've been doing lives ever since then I was like in January. He had a little bit of a little bit of a
Yeah, she's cool. So yep, she's very cool. So Amazon
Okay, yeah
Hopefully I'm getting better at running this show even gets hard I keep trying to like
Think I can like heal everything fix everyone and I'm not fix people
No, people don't really need to be fixed, but I can't fix anybody people can like only
Change as much as they want to change and fix themselves, right? Okay, so let me see. Oh, Amazon's choice
Okay, I'll find one
Let's see. Yeah, she's very cool. Let's see spirits of symbols in her world. Oh, that one looks good
In her world, let me see how these look
I mean this deck of them they had their pictures of it. Oh
It looks really cool. I'm gonna be getting this one. I'm getting this one. Okay. It's yeah
It's that's it. This is that price. Okay. Okay. Bye now
In our world's free two-day delivery
Okay, I ordered it
Okay, we're gonna have fun day though
You wanna see Lola, how you doing me and Laura?
Hi everybody.
Lola, you want to say hi to everybody? Hi.
Miss Lola? Her name is Lola.
Oh, thank you, Cat. Oh, I pet your neck like that. Oh, Lola's a sweetheart. She doesn't mind being on TV either.
Yeah, so they have I'm surprised at how many movie decks they have they have this like they have hocus-pocus the night before Christmas
They have a Beetlejuice
they have a
Much like monster movie decks Lord of the Rings
The garbage pail kids that's the one I think a hillbilly wants to buy me. There's the bumpy the vampire Slayer deck. There's
Yeah, that's all the ones all the ones are showing up in that row the Wizard of Oz there's
Mmm
Yeah, there's the evil eye Oracle that looks pretty interesting. I feel like I still want that one
Yeah, that's just Lola
Lola
There's we already can't I baby. Oh, she's so sweet
Guys people say oh my god, you're grabbing your cat guys. I'm I touch it very gently or okay, and I don't it doesn't box
He's purring so I know how to hold my kitty cat
That's tricks his mom little tricks his mom of course, you know
Rudy's over there.
Hey, Rudy's looking over and you saw me petting Lola?
Rudy's looking over like, hey, what are you doing?
She looks chill, yeah, she's very chill.
She's okay, she's sitting right here.
I think there's like a,
there's probably some catnip all over there.
Oh, meow, meow, hi.
She's a very sweet cat.
Where's Trixie?
I don't see Trixie, she must be outside.
So let's do, let me see, yeah, so, you know,
interesting statistics, okay, so I said 250,000
at watch hours, I've gotten, that's a quarter of a million.
Guys, that's a lot, a quarter of a million people
have watched my videos and stuff, wow, that's crazy.
But unfortunately, all the videos I delete,
I don't want to be using the 60,000 hours logged
So every time I delete videos, which I do so many videos just they're gone and
This is it lose all the watch hours and stuff for them. You can never be there's gone
So it really does hurt probably in the long run when people do form ball man stuff and actually like delete streams and
so
That you know
I expect to like learn some lessons because they're sometimes expensive lessons the first year, but
You know, I think I'll be able to get better and better at it. Okay, so that I had that I had
You know, two thousand five hundred and sixty subscribers. I have
Like half a million impressions and then it's like out of those maybe like
Never for Christmas Day. That sounds pretty cool. Yeah, I love Jack Skellington. I
Yeah, I was charmed by that movie, you know
And I like those Tim Burton kind of looks and the
Those animated ones I haven't seen in a quite a long time
That's so crazy how easy it is to adapt movies and
different things to tarot decks you know because in a movie they'll have all
these elements of the tarot you know you can like go through some movies
sometimes they do they do it the fool's journey on in sequential order and
stuff you know yeah now 40 people in chat good morning everybody everyone
shout out
Where you're from and anybody everybody say hi, how do I get everybody to comment sometimes it's hard
People are a little bit quiet. I don't know if it was just like watching me. I was like, where's watching you?
You know, we don't we're not we don't want to talk to you. We just wouldn't watch you. Okay. I
Don't mind. Oh gosh. Yeah
You should make your own custom deck using yourself and all this from chat. You can draw them yourself
Yeah, exactly. I would love to you know, I just and they have these blank decks
that you can
Just draw on it, you know, you see my art. It's a little bit
Not like it's not bad it's like, you know
Interesting it's like it's a little bit abstract, right? We say a little bit abstract, but
Oh, thank you
Yeah, and I'm still like, you know, I should have been like a lot more active doing art and stuff like that
But I do like doing portraits. I see a lot of elements in these drawings that are like elements throughout my life
But I've always drawn like the eyes like that and like the face and I did my hair. It's like, I don't know where I learned it
Is the who's in the chat made for 20 and you
At Christine's luck fozzy and I stay at the eldest 30 diamond gaudy. Yes, I can prove gaudy
JT penis
And Chris K is Chris K
Chris K
Smoking I don't know he's holding that he's holding there
No, it looks like bent chopsticks or something are you smoking weed? I'm not sure. He's at a roach clip. What's the fuck would I think?
I don't know what I was thinking
Okay, here's another some weed or something. I drew some
I drew I drew Christine
Okay
I drew, um, stay turned, I drew, stay turned, I have, stay turned, I drew, I, I'll just,
you know, I'll just keep for anonymous, but you know, you know, you know, okay, and
Pretty diamond.
And, oh my God, what's going on there?
Okay, and there's Goddy.
That's the second picture I tried to draw.
I'm not sure.
Eldo, big Eldo.
That's what it looks like, kind of.
Another one of the more realistic ones.
There's Alex.
Ghosts
Like Picasso, thank you, there's ghosts
That's it. I got baby Homer since then spunky
Didn't go I have jingle here, too. I've been going here somewhere. Oh, yeah, here's jingle
You're on the dingle from the chat.
JT.
Okay.
There's easy.
Yep.
There's another one of Goddy.
His god loves bananas and donuts.
Avatar.
And...
There's DJ Electra
Ah
Speak of the devil. Oh, it's Jacob Gotti. Yeah, that's the thing like hey Gotti
Ah, hi stranger. Yep
Guys, they're all also like portals whenever I like hold up the
drawing it seems to summon
Some in the the person in the drawings, maybe it's magic. What's up, Goddy. How are you happy 4th of July?
Yo
Prosta, I don't know. I mean it's just one they say
How they do chairs in Russia, oh I see
Forgot how they do it
Yo, happy fourth. Here is its hair does. Oh, Nostrovia. Nostrovia. It's like that. Nostrovia.
Happy 4th of July, everybody. The guys I have. Everyone's so excited. Guys, happy 4th of July.
Yeah, got my
Fourth of the helmet
When I see from the side, huh? Look at look at my the actually the underwear itself is hung like look at that
Like that's what you mean without me in it. Look how big it is
Beautiful shape
One of the great guys remembered last time I was in these yeah look even better another war in and
Yeah, I'm gonna auction off the speedo and got the bidding will start at $20
included shipping is included you know and they'll be slightly soiled they'll
be washed at request but if I would want me to do that nobody everyone wants
them slightly soiled right that's the way to go and you have a little piece of
me forever just put them in I'll put them in like a ziploc bag just take
take a mountain take a whiff whenever you
You're not opposed to the idea. No, I think it's a good idea. It's like selling your bathroom
No, I'm not taking a jar of my bath water. Oh, you're not open to the idea. Oh, I thought you said you were yeah
So, uh, so yeah, it's not something my bath water. Yeah, you miss pipe. I was here for like an hour gaudy
She was you can rewind we have a nice interview well
You're selling bathwater and at any point would you like to buy some if you guys if you'd like to buy a book bathwater for me?
We can make a deal. Okay, just contact me privately, okay?
Guys yeah, I look yeah pie's awesome fine. I was really cool. So was she to give me yes
She was she was I think one of the better better moods
I've seen her on the show. So yay
Um, yep, what can I say hi me Lola? Let's say hi to Gotti Lola Lola wants to say hi this morning
She wants to be on camera. Hi. Oh and Gotti looking got looking in your eyes. Got you looking to her eyes
Magical
Gotti, oh these here spawned to your voice. Well, that wasn't your voice, but it was close enough
Yeah, people are wild like that guys
These these underwear they are these speedos will sell, you know, and these guys is their piece of history
I'm where I've been I've worn them twice on my stream
This is a hundred of people. They're so they're they're famous
That's good. Oh, yeah. Oh, are you attacking my microphone? What are you doing?
Her eyes look you're a pure Jade. Hey, Lenore. No. Yeah, she's beautiful. I think her eyes are gorgeous
Yeah, she's hey. Oh, she's kissing Lenore here. Oh shit
No
Okay, okay problem over here. There we go
Any get saved burnt. Hey, I was it say turned get naked for psyche backstage. Yeah guys
Do you want to do a freak off to that we can do we can do a fourth of July freak off?
Maybe I'll set up off a firecracker from my butt. I don't know. I'm sure about a rocket
Rack is the hazard of speedo any
Hello, I don't look over my camera. My dream is for pie to ask these again at once from her pie. Yeah
Well, I think she's heard that pickup line
That's the issue. Oh, yeah, someone might buy that bathwater. Yeah
I mean if you want to buy if you want to buy my bathwater, you know
Contact me on Instagram discord as we can work out deals, you know
Can you say rest in peace? No, I cannot say that because then I'll be clipped and then King Vaughan will think that I said
Oh, no, I've already said all the words. Okay
They're gonna be on eBay speedo. Yeah, but we're gonna we're gonna I want it to be like I want my chat to have first dibs
I want my I want people that are here
to be able to
Hear the motorcycle if you be able to get a piece of me why the person is dead. Who's that person? Okay?
He's dead this clip since yeah. Oh my god. Oh
This is it's passed away that he can't get mad at me, right?
He's gonna be deal with Alice. Yeah
God, do you don't want to put in your bids? Well guys, who's gonna be the first bid at $20, right?
So we'll have an auction today. It'll be an American flag auction
Don't talk about I
Forgot what I was just said, but
Okay, I don't know. I don't know what they're talking about. I don't know. I just don't know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
Don't know. Are you trying to get me in trouble? Doug?
And that's heroin and Sarah does
Easy better. Okay, never mind Doug
Yeah
No stability, I just got
error message. It says stability issues, studio instability issues. The latest
version of some browsers seems to have an interest of conflict that is causing
studio instabilities when using all virtual backgrounds or touch my
appearance features. At a temporary workaround we suggest turning off those
features where we're kind of fixed. Our engineers are actively working to ensure
I've never had it like an error message like that. Think of it. Okay well I guess
It's not appropriate
Pat there's a road mod banning BKG support. Is there guys the road mod is everyone
Let me know over the chat of somebody's timing out beat his people
I'm I do not support timing out beat its people this because of BKG beat his people. I'm I
Want to be on good terms. Sorry. Okay. Well, okay. I don't want to say his name anymore. What are you talking about easy easy said
Okay, he said he wants to
I got it once to buy them for a thousand dollars. Got it buy them now. You can have them right now
Although skip the auction you can just
They're gonna do yours. They'll be yours
Just close just
You won't have to do a bidding war. No none of that crap. Just buy it now
Easy is going to enjoy guard. Oh my god
Doug stop it
Oh, Lava
Squirting
What are you talking about now? What is the chat guys chat seems to be their head in a gutter
I remember people were really sad. Oh, okay
Well, I don't know. I don't know what's wrong
Yeah, his name is familiar
Squirting I know what my favorite it's one of our favorite topics to talk about is like, oh is it his squirt
P or is it like female female come and then people will say oh, it's like 90% T and 10% female
I'm like, well, what is female? Like what is it? I know chat come on. We're talking about female come right now, okay?
Guys get your minds back to me. Okay. I'm mr. McGoo. Hey
I love you guys. I'm from deal a good style in professor. How are I mr. McGoo you can never see
what? That's what Joe always says. Most people squirt something out of summer every day. I
know squirt, yeah, especially after too much Mexican food, but I'm talking about, you know,
women will like squirt. Isn't that just urine? I think so. I don't know what it is. They're like,
oh, it's mostly urine, but it's like, what else is it? I mean, what is it? I've never heard of any
Don't know
Does what he's talking about. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I don't is it Doug look a woman. I've heard Douglas like actually like this woman not sure who it is
It got he's laughing tingles laughing. Okay. Everyone's laughing a little bit
I don't know if this is the most appropriate questions to be asked in the lead guys if you don't ask if you don't want guys
You better not ask page of this question. Okay, you do you're in big trouble. You're not
Don't want to hear if it's any percent piss it might as well be
Yes, okay
Fair fair. Maybe it's maybe it's all that's mother liquid. I used to think it was like some different liquid
I don't know what I was thinking as like what what would this be like some kind of you kiss or something it for you
I don't know where is this liquid coming from?
It's more mysterious than 30 diamonds breast milk if it says any percent piss it might as well be yeah. Yeah, exactly
I don't speak to me like that. Oh my god. Well, that's what I'm saying. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm glokey
I'm sorry. It's lemonade
Yeah, I just remember didn't have it. Okay. I did like experience one time
I didn't know I didn't know my girlfriend peed all over my couch. I thought I just think you know
Done some amazing
Fingerwork, but anyway what happened is that yeah, she soaks with my couch and I
Remember tasting it was like didn't taste like anything. That's something very diluted
Yeah, who's sweepy yeah, no, you didn't miss a speedo still that was like 10 a.m.
Never forget the towel, right?
Yeah
Some people put up plastic and stuff like well they actually like you know, they're more honest about it that they know it's like
peeing on people as it might have touched like
I'm not good at like
Finger binging. I don't know. That's all I ever did
It must be improved. I know must have been like, you know
It's not wasn't obviously wasn't yellow. I'd be like, oh, it's pee. Oh, it was like like water and it tasted like water
Give you a little bit
Little bit like a like a loop like a loop texture to it. Yeah, I don't I don't know women are human boob machines
Kim squirts orange crush. Oh my god
Yeah
You've ever yeah, you know imagine a big asparagus and then it's like oh my gosh. We what would you squirt that you know that?
green you know
asparagus smelling
Water how like how did that happen?
So Goddy like Goddy you want you?
God if you want to pee on me, I would let you it was not gay
I would like close my eyes and not look at your wiener and you can just do it
And I just have mouth open and just like feeling like one of this
You know the the spare you squirt that like the clown's mouth and it fills up the balloon pops
That'll be like me. Yeah, I'm sticky. I haven't even finished my first cup of coffee. Oh, we are on the squirt talk. Yeah
Let's say you know something a little squirt in your coffee, right?
God we got into it all you like it got he got I don't I bet I don't want to do a brown a brown shower with God
He that's when like, you know
He's a bunch of McDonald's and comes and sits on my chest
Sounds disgusting would never do that
Never got he not for half a million dollars. No, maybe for half a million dollars
But we'll discuss it later
You're and it's not sterile it is just a friendly reminder. Oh, yeah, well, isn't it? I thought it was sterile
Thought it was sterile
God is into the sense of heat position. I don't want to be a part of a human sense of heat, especially with God, you know
Oh my god, I
Don't want to be in the human sense of heat. No. No, thank you easy
Easy I think easy might be insane. I thought I just saw a video tonight. He seems like I
Don't know if I know this person
I shouldn't have baked or wait and baked today clearly. Oh, I'm not the day for it
And yeah, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Oh my gosh
You easy alone. Thank you. Diddy says he wants me at the first freak off when he gets out. We'll see
Wait, she wants you. Let's get a picture of me or something. Okay. I just packed a bowl. Yep. Let me find my vape. Oh, here's one
Bottoms up
That's a good one anyway
So they have this this a club
Let me see if I can remember the details of this was that this club called the Pandora's box club or something like that
And so when they have a new rapper or something once they get a deal they get invited to this club I
Don't know all I know is that they go to the club thinking that they're gonna get a record deal
They come out with a record deal, but in between that time they like
Or put in a mask and like 10 black guys fuck them or something. I don't I don't know. It sounds very gay. It doesn't, you know, and
It's just like I probably anyone want to be in the industry that no wonder it's like
Little nods X is the only decent one left through anymore. But anyway, yeah, you know, the copy doesn't taste good anymore. Well
Put in some milk. It's been some extra milk
Isn't that the industry standard right now
Yeah
Well, yeah, it's like we think about the industry right think about how many people think about oh my god, it's like the
There's like a million guys like a mixtape and like you know that things you can wrap and like it probably sounds kind of decent
Maybe has some talent. Maybe doesn't you can you can do a nursery rhyme? You can basically sing rap, right or sing rap and
They can always make you sound cool in the studio, right?
So people really want these jobs.
I mean, these jobs with millions,
they can make millions, they have the fantasy,
and so they think they're gonna just be some star.
Well, no, it's like Hollywood and the music industry
are very, very selective.
They get to pick exactly who they wanna bring in,
and they have to make sure they're sufficiently compromised
so they can be able to use it like a puppet
instead of like having the actor go out
and be all controversial and talk about their own beliefs.
So it's really it's true Sally 2012. We have a easy
Well, if he's he goes to hell, it's okay cuz he probably has a throat in there
Are you do what it goes on that room goes on in that room what it gets cold it's cold
Yeah, what's up? What the hell gets cold? I gotta go down there. You don't walk shit back up
Well, that's the problem with hell is like, you know, it's really you know, the sunburn is terrible the ice cream all melts and you know
Yeah, but I don't know real hateful things to say hell's waiting for you like damn like I really hit I hit him hard this time
Well, you know, it's like
We all make mistakes and it's like, you know, so now as we regret them sometimes we don't
The biggest thing is that can we forgive? Can we forgive ourselves? Can we look at ourselves in the mirror?
Can we sleep if we sleep soundly during the night? Do we have a heart as lit light as the feather or I sleep like a baby every night
But then I'll say again if you don't feel any of that
Just be aware that maybe you could someday because there are repercussions to our actions, right?
And so and that goes for everybody, right?
It's like even if we're like we can't sleep well and it's like but maybe later in life
We will have regrets about some of our actions, right? But that's part of like
Living and growing as a human and doing better. And it's like, you know, sometimes we do it alone
Sometimes we do it with you
Some of the actions, maybe the decisions or like you what you wonder what would happen if you never did that
Right, but Dennis like the decision is like I mean, there's so many we make so many decisions, right?
It's and so it's like and so sometimes we are on
Autopilot sometimes we are under the influence of
Chemicals influences. We don't understand alcohol or other thing, you know, even you know weed is the
Is a big influence on the personality and in the person's like motivation and all kinds of weed only calms me down alcohol
alcohol
My legs me move relax liquor insane
Mm-hmm. They can make you go insane. Yeah, and so so guys if we go insane or we're gonna do some stupid shit
You know, right as they if we go insane like we'll do something stupid
And then it's like, you know, sometimes we'll have a sober person in our party that pretends to drink or
You know, just the designated driver and then they're always the one with some some camera around ready to catch you
You know with your you know underwear down around your ankles while you're peeing behind a Toyota
You know after coming out of the club, there's always gonna be that friend
Right
I mean, I mean, that's the typical Saturday night for most L.A.
That's Garry's typical Saturday night. I'm just saying.
Hey, Electra. Hi, how are you sweetheart? Yeah. And so, but anyway, you know,
you know, I would say make amends to it. I think we should think about if we do hurt other people and
you know, we can like maybe
make amends or even if we don't, you know, we can just say like at least like
Listen because you go pray for men so the next person you honed or whatever the case might be if they don't accept it
They don't accept it if you say it out the public or you say it up in that it is what it is
But be with that within yourself find that piece with yourself normally you found that piece
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I'm saying I'm saying the forgiveness the forgiveness or like the
For yourself, but the previous for others who is like a forgiveness for yourself. It's like when you forgive somebody
They don't really feel the effects of your forgiveness.
You feel the effects because you've let go of this big burden of anger.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it's just you're holding people, people hold on to this anger.
And it's like, it just distracts them from the real goal.
And it's like, it takes them away.
Why do you think they so mad at me?
Because I forgave him, I forgave myself, and I kept on moving on life.
Who did you forgive myself?
Are you pretty okay?
Okay, I'm making all the bullshit forgive and get moving and they mad that I'm happy with life. That's what it is
Who's mad there's like that person or is there people are personal porters
Okay, you know I support you if somebody harb you or gets up there
I'll probably be mad at them like you'll fuck you like you her psyche. They fuck you. They you know, yeah
Yeah, and they're I mean of course like and when we have friends and they're personally affected
It's like gonna be a lot different than if it's like a stranger or or something like that and you know
We've been it's great to defend your friends and it's like of course. There's more size
Subject because of that square subject was games real drifty. So, okay
I don't mean to yeah, I'll let you what do you would like to what would you like to talk about? No, we could talk about anything else
Yeah, anything else. Okay
I've been trying to build your confidence for this beat. Oh, so I want to see them on my confidence is there
My confidence is there. I was just like waiting for like the perfect time. I don't know. I just like maybe if I
Have another beer in the fridge. Maybe oh
I just thought it mine so
Yeah, I'm still finishing my copy. Unfortunately it got cold, but there's only one a cup of it
Yeah, so 39 people in chat
In front of my house today, but my cousin come come pick up me and my wifey and we're gonna head towards over there and watch
Oh, well fun. Are you going out in the speedo? I'm not gonna go out
Like to the beach or anything
I'm just gonna be home
because I
Don't want to be out in a speedo in public really
I think he's going to give everybody the confidence to go out of the speedo this summer like yo you ain't out matching me
Suckie you gonna have big jaw to it everybody watch
Charlie easy's not gay. It's like you understand a speedo is like it's like a comedic device
Okay, stop like yeah, he's not gay. He has never been experimented. He would not you would not
I got the tightest booty hole in the century. Oh my god. Oh my god, easy
He's Puerto Rican like I've known pure Puerto Rican guys to be kind of freaky like, you know, you know kind of like, you know
Freaky you're a little lady
Oh my gosh
Yeah, well
Whatever floats your boat easy. Okay, so it's a speedo is what male shippers wear. Yeah, it's straight and gay male shippers
Where you know women enjoy that if there's it's kind of a bunny cut, you know
Do you know pride men with like not pride like straight men wear speedos too?
Yeah, I mean they're functional for ever swimming like I used to swim and I you'd wear them for swimming cuz it's like
Yeah, that's back on the water resistance of that when you're in regular bathing suit very heavy your backstage can you show off where
Yes, you can the backstage. Yes
Be be
Backstage with this state to show you last night. He was showing you stick with the tank top drop a little bit draws
You pay me back. Yeah, I mean he was just like he was just giving me like this like
LL cool J expression and like sitting there like
Yeah, he was giving like little like his list for like
Purse up a little bit and he was like just showing up in dark glasses like all looking all cool and
Kind of like I don't know
But then I found out he's one of the people that was like I was like oh
He's with one of the trolls from that group. So I didn't say wearing this be it was gay
I said easy wanting to see another man in his one. It is Charlie
You don't like to see me in the speedo Charlie. You didn't like to see me in it. Everyone liked to see me in it
even if they didn't
We're attracted to it. It was so bizarre and strange of a
Thing that people thought was funny the comedy gods demand speedo. Yes. These are just appeasing the comedy gods
You know, you don't want to see the comedy guys mad. It's not a funny laughing matter
Psychic she's up lying
Yeah, ziggie. What no, we're not talking about you. We're talking about a stay turned ziggie, but i'll tell you what ziggie did
Ziggy I didn't he wasn't talking about you. He's talking about stay turn stay turn was trying to yeah
I ain't saying nothing bad about you yet. Ziggy we on good terms
What your avatar, you know
But took off its clothes or something your avatars a stupid avatar
I don't know you look like you could be 500 pounds your mother's basement. I would have no idea
Am I warm? Okay? I'm not sure. No, I'm just kidding
Yes, how many gods demand it her dad always wore a speedo growing up
RSBB you're sitting or BSBB you're gonna show me your speedo backstage. You never cammed up. I didn't see it
backstage
If you're gonna show it
I'll hold it down your psyche has a blast off in the back end
You know, I just hold down the string
Who wants to go to the 4th of July? Freak off
Oh, it's a big okay, it's a big times I think I think there's like, you know, I still tickets available on all these three K's
Go fund me. I think I think he's hired him as the must have hired him as his manager producer of the event
There'll be a tattoo free tattoo booth. There'll be
rodeo clowns. They'll be
That's gonna be there. He's gonna be the clown. We know we're all going guys my plane takes off in another two hours
I only have an hour left on stream board to catch the flight. So wherever he lives
I'm picking up sort of diamond at the airport and the one page and we're all gonna drive
Down to the the good times calm calm that we're calling it good time or no good stock. We're calling good stock and
Oh, thank you. Shelly and
Can't wait. He said he's gonna welcome everybody everybody except from good times to great times
Yep, it's gonna be it's gonna be to the to the amazing times. It's gonna be to
Unspeakable unspeakably good times. I enjoyed this video for everyone
I'm just because I bought them. I knew that she was gonna get you people don't like it
So of course he was gonna hate it
But you know they mostly after when they first when you first came up
It was all smiling from cheek to cheek like the Joker
Yep, because they were like, oh look now I can take a picture of him, you know
Everybody you had over a hundred people in here when you started showing that
40 people now because I put happy 4th of July party tarot cards and speedos
They're tarot cats and speedo and so it's been the title so everyone who's searching for speedos right now
It's my my my stream has come
You didn't know I suppose like you no matter what
You want something I say let me see let them hit let me stop you know my person you the first person I publicly started by
Everybody else. I did it on the low
What you brought it's some awesome stuff the whoo-doo tarot the uh, you heard the bomb you get ripped
Oh, oh, yeah, I wanted to tell you that when you take that hit of the bomb the next set you take don't just blow it out
Take that inhale and you're gonna get hired in a motherfucker right there
And I'll take that in now. I'm telling you take that in hell. Even if you hold it
I'm mixing a little tobacco sometimes with it and so it's like so that that's why it's okay
I call it in New York City is called gravel. They call I should grab it. Yeah
But then ship. Oh, it's you the smelly clipped and ship. I know now. It's a P
I'm appearing in other videos that I've seen now with my legs behind my head and
Goddy and JT both have it as an avatar selection
Hold it
They big fans
I just I'm I'm afraid of but I just think about like oh this I think the smoke starts to soak into your lung
I'm trying to get that video taken down. We'll try get that video taken down the copy right now
I mean, I mean, it's it's a I mean know what the underwear the dispute. Oh, I
You can keep it up. Oh that oh that one. Yeah, but it's fine. I don't care. It's like
It's like, I mean, it's like if you want to review but it's like
Me they could talk all the shit they want. I don't care. It's just
Yeah, she's going we almost almost almost purple with Q but I got no video on my page
So you could tell me the harassment is going
Yeah
Yeah, but I just don't want her to like get crazier about it
I don't want to get ugly and then me being a cotton across fire. I'd like to like
Not be involved in it. If you smoking tobacco with it. Yes, I put on soft porn sites
What it what would you put on?
I need to make me a joint right now. There's a there's soft porn the guy like I kind of like so soft what?
It's a soft porn. Oh, she Melly says he put my speedo video on soft porn. So you put my video up
Melly
No, they didn't okay. Thank God. I put it on soft point now life. I like he's okay. All right
Okay, I don't like damn at least give him percentage. It was his percentage
Yeah, well, I was looking I was looking on like on like
Pourn have you made 20 or so far? Oh my god
Well, it's come to me. Do I know him 10 so far you get 50 50 50 50
I think they might I mean they might have it might be I don't really care
I mean it's not like it's not first of all, it's not soft-core porn second of all
Like what kind of net is gonna like click on me and my speedo because I think just like it looks like a skeleton in a speedo
How gay is so he's over there like oh looks like he looks great
No, well, I do I did you have people that find me attractive. I mean, I do I
It's like you're catching you're gonna get a catch. Don't worry about it. Thank you. It's okay. No
Well, I don't know. I'm not like I don't think I'm the right about that self confidence guy
Well, I think I'm pretty competent to shower stream as fetus smelly wants me to take a shower. Yeah
Smelly, do you not clip this one? Yeah?
I'm just checking then I can't I can't read I can't see the screen when I read the chat can't see the screen
So, oh, no, no, I mean if I take a shower, I do it on on on the on stream in the speedo
You took a shower said man and elbows was here
Yeah, I'm gonna wait for them to come in this morning. Oh, I did it last time. I was cleaning and I was listening
I was sitting there laughing my ass. So if I'm clean, I'm like, yo, they really did? Oh shit. Yeah, look, I started laughing
That's the only back to come. Oh, they were there. They were there. They're like, oh
You're like, they're like, they're like, whoa, they're like
Me my opinion thought they would have been left like, you know
Yeah, they're like they're looking on the low. They're like, you know, they're like, oh, you know, we're you know
We're not gay and then it's like
Oh, oh, there's psyche in the speedo. Let's click over there and join the chat and watch to watch him in the shower
My crazy supporters even was watching and they you know Harry remember the last time you got
Speedos with him. He was all giddy. Yeah, I'm not watching
Yeah, but I don't know but then he like
Didn't he but didn't he like start being weird to me or something? Oh, no, it wasn't huge
He started saying F word after he thought it going crazy. Oh
Yeah, happy for it Ziggy. Oh, yes, we P. I will you know that low
today don't worry about it
You make low squirt home Charlie says
Only make my girl squirt
She's spicy smash. I'm sorry
Yeah, remember just
Do I bleach my a-hole no, I do not that's they're thinking of using a blogger
We are not the same person only asshole. You should try it bleach asshole. Not you who ever wrote it. I
Yeah, I mean, yeah
And yeah, you should just you know, just get a mirror and yeah, you know what?
Yes, he can reach the asshole and then come up on panel and tell us how he did it. Yeah
Oh my god, okay
No, that person can tell us how I did it that person that person. I don't know the male female that person can tell us how they did it
But recorded don't forget to record it and then you know, okay, break it down. Yes, baby. What color is your asshole diggy?
I'm not gonna
Dream is too spicy right now. Yes, it's spicy
Yeah
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I put on the speedo guys wait. So wait a last
No, well
Smiling I can see you smell through the screen
Yeah
Smelly if you buy if you buy me the anal bleaching cream and send another 50 bucks
I'll probably do that, but I don't I'm not gonna bleach my asshole just on my own or for the
I need a bleaching cream take paid for okay smash
Wait, I'll just show my face. I'll just do my face. I'll be
Have somebody apply it. I'll see it
Somebody wants to fly out and fly it anybody or any volunteers I had for my heads. I did my son. Oh, sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry
I apologize, you know, this is an adult show
Not drunk, but yeah, but what happened that happened to me with family coming in and out
But at least you gave a warning that they here so we could be a little bit more proper for the time. Yeah
Right
Well, I don't think anybody can understand like any of the most of the stuff they got
At least we know that that person's here. So we'd be a little bit more respectful. That's that. Yeah. Okay. I'm so sorry
Okay, guys, you might want to make sure it's also 18. Oh the show and I was all parents and people do not have their kids or
siblings or any minors around watching
Right. We always want to
Remember the panels 21 over like the chat participating chat to be 18 and over. Let's see what's out here. Sure. Yeah
Yeah, it's 18 and 21 older. I
Okay, so I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
Put it on my butt. I mean, you know that the the thong thing
I'm just I'm not gonna like make it the front too big. I'm not gonna have any a scato. Hey, you're a member
Scott oh look Scott oh smash low-key
Scott oh just writing a check cuz I already knew he was he was I had no problem with Scott oh
Scott is one of my cool people's and
This is before I even met you say you this is years already. This is I play around like this. You don't like it. Yeah, what?
Yeah, so
Yeah, okay, so let's see
Digi, what's the key say? What did Ziggy say?
Digi said love I love he said I'm 16
Ziggy no, you're not guys
Band you might get bad
Don't watch it. It's sticky don't heroes get banned
Yeah, Ziggy, you know if you're 16 you have to be banned from the show
So you do want to rephrase that or not if you don't rephrase that maybe we'll just have to ban you because I don't want
Those under 18 in the show
In the even the chat you make got a bit taken down because you two thought she was 13. Yeah, she's very young with me
Good times party. It's it's seven. Everyone's gonna go to the good times party today. Okay, everybody
I'll see you on the I'll see you on the bus we're gonna take a little party bus from the airport to the to the
Good stock compound, you know, there's
Yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, exactly. It was my ideas
Good bash good bash on a Sunday at three, okay, he's gonna be there
Are you are you 16?
Yeah, yeah
You know good times came on the show and then I said, oh, I was promoting his party and then he took out guns
Two of them, I saw that one.
Yeah, two, she put two like semi-automatic machine guns
and it started like, you know,
like he was like John Wick or something.
And then-
She wanted to do four photos of her life early.
Okay, don't go to Goodham's house,
you will never leave.
Oh yeah, well, because you know,
would you lock me in the basement
or has had too much fun?
I understand that.
Don't invite psyche for a good time.
You don't yeah, I don't want to go. Yeah, but if you invite him you over most likely scenario would be he doesn't have tied to the bed
I might as well leave
Okay
See what you did Ziggy Ziggy would you do?
Yeah, oh good stock. He's a good stock. Yeah
So but everyone's no bad. No one's really gonna show up to it. Of course. We know this is a joke
Look, look, they started it already. ZC Ziggy. You don't want to fuck around it. They already saying bad Ziggy 16
I'm sucking Ziggy's dick tonight. Oh my god. Oh my god. Look. Oh, okay, but it's easy. I don't know
Okay, I like my burgers well done
LMAO what don't say what it's happening. Oh, she's gotten the chef. Oh, we all go in the heaven
Are you like you guys like got it got is like a chef way or do you kind of
Alright, who's the guy we gonna throw the boy?
Don't the dunk the guy the guy that falls in the water
The dunk tank
Raging raging demon or flirty diamonds. Okay. I'm just kidding. Love. I got some meat with your name on it
Oh my god, who's doing the karaoke? Who's gonna be on the stage? Who's doing the comedy?
You gotta have a hole. I mean, I'm just I'm just there to do
drugs and you know
Who's on the pole don't a shipper pole
I might I might end up on the Super Bowl, but I'm not
The rope swing, I mean the sheet swing
That sounds like a clan rally, I mean, please let's not make it weird. Okay is calling you fat guy. Oh God
He's yeah, it's if we are D
I was describing the picture from Diddy's party. Oh
Okay, come at my kitty
Hey, Ziggy
Oh, he's kind of like sometimes like did you I'm just going to be there for the party. Exactly. I'm going to relax
We're supposed to wear all all white all white. Yeah, all white party and
Oh, good
There's gonna be a wet t-shirt contest and that's why everyone's gonna be wearing white so that you can see the nipples easier
Where is my girlfriend page? Hey, it's your girlfriend. I don't think she's your girlfriend
Are you another one of these delusional freaks that thing?
Yeah, listen that shit even creeps me out and I'm like
You know what I'm saying? I was well
Let's say page is very magnetic
But uh, she's very she's attracting a lot of uh, a lot of a lot of
I know I mean she like has to just like basically get get get get bodyguards escort her out of my chat because people are like
Being discussed in a dream about her people starting to dream about her
And then I was like I was like I was like I was like I was like do you see how people were sexually harassing?
He's a thing and no I didn't say I think well you're one of the people you say I was not he just grabbed a whole erotic dream with her
where they're holding hands and
falling in love and
Fucking I just grabbed a kiss
Yeah
Like you're just rat and you kiss me back. Yeah in your dreams Alex
Otherwise page would be calling the police and you haven't restraining order immediately
Pull up pull up
They be hating when once I share my trolls come in this shit
Has Aldi I think Aldi has them all he has. Okay, low low. Okay. How come look he said I thought there was body painting
Yeah, there's been body painting. Do I have any body paint? I have some markers. I can maybe draw myself with later
Tell him to save me a lot. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, I talked about the party. Yeah, there'll be facial painters there
Right, I said put some body paint on to make it look like you got a t-shirt
Okay, I'll be good
But I mean
It was very just okay. I'm like I'm disturbingly painted white free beer full back and green room
Even catering. Oh god guys. This is not the party of this century
I make paintings of
White is gonna have the swings. There's made out of sheets. It's gonna have the stripper poles everybody in white white outfit
They're gonna have the two to put the pool and the jacuzzi and we ducking somebody into the fucking pool idiot of the day
Look, you know, you know, we're white. I think you know we're off white humor a little bit off
I don't do the caravans a little bit like Excel
Would you be getting good times a lap dance in your speedo? I don't think so
I think he annoyed me this morning when he like said that I'm crashing out and
Then he just left the show before I could respond
How rude
I'm crashing out my hair is a little bit of spew
He was sitting there drunk telling me this and he said he's like 60 beers and
Like a quarter of whiskey or something like that one night, and then he woke up feeling fine
Do I have piercings and no and he woke up feeling fine and then I
Was like well, that sounds like
He was drunk drunk, right? You're in love with Jan. Okay. Hold on
It's like you saw that he took you put a shirt on because he had a party coming
Oh my gosh.
Pages that come across in us, how do we go?
Well, Pages, like last night, you know, Pages and this other woman that were on the panel,
we're talking about starting their own compound in Canada.
And then, you know, like, you know, I guess like, you know, females on YouTube streams.
And then I was like, well, I want to start a compound.
Sort of sex cult and then everyone like looking me like I was weird like I was serious
And they're like and the guy said sort of saying I was Charles Manson and stuff and I was like I was just kidding I
Wouldn't I have sex with my chat. It's like it would be too strange. You're like brothers and sisters to me
I love you though
When you bend over God here and make them walk again, no, oh my gosh
I got yeah
Why take they go what you go black you ever been the wheelchair?
Well
Hey psyche and when you hit it, he's gonna walk instead of roll
I'll just push around God Ian's wheelchair
Where he wants me, you know, I'll just do that. I'll walk really fast. I'm a fast walker. I'll take him where he wants to go
I have got cross and I'm stuck up bit. What are God cross? Are they black crocs?
And did you know low-key low-key low-key low-key low-key low-key low-key low-key low-key
Yeah, I love I got like a bunch of pairs with my dad's I got to turn broken socks when he passed away
You know, I know where his shoes
But I'll never I'll never feel them quite like heated there are bikes and heels
Very cool for the fam. How do you feel about bloody set? Are you talking about like like eating out?
I was offered that once and I was like I declined I was like no, that's the drink
I don't want to take okay, you know what? Yeah, so she's like, oh they want you yeah, but I'm on my peers
Well, I was like, well, that's perfect timing. I was like no, and uh anyway, so we did it
I don't know if this is my finger bankers. I don't remember my hand coming out obliety. I can't I can't
What's wrong?
What's wrong
It's okay. Can you do you have any conversation? Oh, yeah, no, no, is this too much? I'm sorry. I
Told my whole family that spaghetti sauce story even like
Are you okay?
Okay
Easy what you don't like it
Why do you think what's name is wolf because he eats the bloody coochie, but it's okay yesterday yesterday
Bathory and yes, he said be a man. Yes a bat. This is Lady Bathory and this guy and Vlad the Impaler
I forgot, Zimples, yeah, Zimples, they were like,
she was like, oh, it's like, you need to take a shower
or need to take a bath, and she's like personal hygiene.
I'm like, well, Lady Bathory, you only take baths
and versions blood, and then like the Zimples was like,
well, is there any other way to take a bath?
And she's like, no, there isn't.
And so I'm like, okay, people are crazy,
but they actually are like the...
Lady Bathory and Led the Impaler characters who did
The east is home, but that's not me. I'm just saying
If people are
You know milking versions of their blood, you know to bat and baton of her beauty
I think that's not to each of them. I mean, that's not that's because that's they're doing something to somebody
So no drinking unless it's your own blood. You should not be drinking it. Okay. Just drink your own blood
I tuned out. I'm sorry. I tuned out
Told you, okay. This is not my type of conversation. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry guy
I just gotta learn how to hold it down like me no brown, you know
Okay, okay, I just don't know it's like where you're in reaction. This is news like it's like
Okay, well, okay, it was 56 people in chat, so obviously it's not bothering
Good they can have it they can rock it out. Okay, look he says it's not weird at all. Okay, so what was I saying though?
Hi spunky
Uh, who's being with Zee's being weird?
Right, you're female right so you telling me it's okay. It's not running that wrong with that
So one day some guy will was eating you out and he looked up his whole chin was red
Yeah
As women, what are your thoughts? I want to hear about what are your thoughts on?
It's called a ragtime right a ragtime meal. What do you think about when the people do that?
Is it like magical? Is it like, you know, you should be making wishes and stuff when you're eating it
I don't know. Just tell me come here. Tell me your thoughts been there
You've been there. Oh my god, you'll take me to spunky town spunky town had a smile on hit face
Yeah, it's like, you know, it's like, okay, so there's a bird. It's like this little songbird in France and it's actually like
They, like, they, like, they, like, they, like, basically boil it alive and stuff like that and, like, cook it, and it's, like, so it's such a shameful of, like, a meal to cook this bird that it's, like, they cover their face with a napkin, and they eat it, like, under the napkin.
They do! It's, like, it's, like, that's, like, that's, like, how it goes either way.
They're red wings. Yeah, I don't know but it's like the bird is like they cook it like and the bones soften and like and so
It's like you eat the bird hole and they just take off the feathers off of it
But it's like you know, it's like little delicate songbird in France
So it's kind of kind of crazy look boy. Let's say he wish you were how I wish you know
I'm gonna look like a hyena feasting on a zebra, right? I like to be a funky town when the
Cartel that faces the narc. Okay boy. Let's say you wish what are you guys? I mean guys everything everything you guys talk about
Sounds like an episode of the sopranos. I think I'm being left out of the loop here. Can you use English please? I don't know
This is the only one I got loads of low while ago to my huh. Yeah, let me just shut up
I'm lost
Loss of the sauce. Oh, you're to the bloody Mary. Okay, so God. He likes that. God. He likes it. Okay, maybe
Him and whoop down with that
His name is whoop gotta eat world bloody males
Well, if and like and like I don't mean I don't need to give away too many secrets of like
secret societies, but I'll say, you know, a big part of it is
utilizing sex in in ratios and because there's like a lot of this energy and they also believe that like, you know, these entities
could come through and all kinds of things, right? And so there's these different degrees,
you know, along the way where you learn a new secret. A lot of these are sexual secrets.
Hey, try this doing this way doing this way doing this way try this way and
That's why Alicia Crowley was a big bisexual
who
Experiment with men and women. He was very out of a closet in his day. You've especially for his day. It was very
Okay, you'll blindfold me got it we blindfold me and
Then restrain and put I know I could wink me. Yeah, don't make my vagina bleed if you're going to say it again. Oh my god
Okay
It's gross. I got dizzy through to go after certain. Yeah, we guys people eat all kinds of strange things
Open up to Bible psyche
What page of it?
What page are you going to? What page?
What part of the Bible exactly?
The Bible is a big book. There's a lot in the Bible.
So I gotta open to a page. I'll start reading about, you know,
the family tree of some family. I don't know who's this.
So this is gross.
Oh, grow up catfish. That is why you will never be my hoe.
Don't know Christine like Christine. I like I said the chats like it's it's like
I went from bloody eating bloody koochie Christine. That's what it was drifted to right now
And we trying to drift away, but we was just talking about a whole bunch of shit, but she yeah
Yeah
But I don't know I was gonna try to see maybe I have something that kind of explains a little bit
But I know if you want to change the topic, but I still have I've been wanting to talk for like five minutes
But they want to continue so let them continue
Okay, how's the chat? I could talk to you about anything you know I'm saying but you got to support the chat what they would do
What they talk about too
Okay, chat. What do you want to talk with it? I don't know what they're talking about is weird things
I have no idea what they're talking about. They're like it's about my people. I don't know and
Okay
Okay, so listen to this. So it says the troubling truth of humanity is that some people simply
do not know what is best for themselves. These people need to be told what to do through indirect
means and only then will they operate in a way that pleases those around them. Since the average
person is unlikely to be motivated to do what you desire, it can be vital to find a way to convince
them that you are right so that they can see the world through your eyes. Being a bright person,
You may find yourself wondering almost immediately
how ethical of a process this is.
Simple answers that ethics are sometimes better debated
by the philosophers.
While humanity loves it as well and the right versus wrong,
both concepts fade away into nothingness
when compared with raw results.
The reality is that methods you find will not only work,
but it can help you rewrite your worlds
from natural preferred perspective.
for the kind of person willing to bend reality
for selfish reasons,
these techniques will be incredibly beneficial.
Well, I'd say be careful with anything that would say that,
but also like maybe learn how to protect yourself
from people that use these kind of techniques.
I'm like on the side of like,
not using these tech out of techniques
because they've been used on me so extensively.
I know it's not very fun.
And so that's why I like to reveal some of them,
but, you know, I'm not,
to misuse them or if we're any pretty to misuse though, I want us to
Learn how to protect yourself better. I think that black frost they killed my biome. How
I'm letting them go off your day. Um, yeah, because
She said she said okay, don't let your way
Oh my gosh. I mean, yeah, we're not talking about this
Let's go man. Let's get somebody else up in here show some love and respect. Yeah, you know time. It is happy 4th of July
If I'm correct the next holiday is what Memorial Day, I mean the other one in September
Hi, I get my morning
Yes, I just rolled out a bed when I don't work I sleep in it's nice
Well tonight's gonna be a good night. Oh, oh, oh psyche tonight. Oh black eyed peas
I'm dancing. Oh
Black eyed peas my gosh guys. Let's how did the how did the freaking red wing conversation get started?
Walked in do yeah
I thought we were talking about like a baseball team or something and they're like, no red wings is when you eat a woman
On the period on her period and I was nasty. I find that really disgusting
But I was joking about it. I know because I always do but the chat didn't even answer
I asked okay, was the chat big didn't really say like it seems like maybe
You know, they don't know at all or they
No, all too well. Oh god, it's lucky sounds like a man. No, oh come on. Fuck you. You know, it's monkeys
Be nice. I didn't make her bleed look. He she it was already bleeding and then I was just there
Okay, I
Awful if I did that to somebody I didn't you know, I didn't I was I refused to go near there at that time and then
Think we've probably just watched a movie instead or something. I don't know but uh, yeah, I didn't make you I didn't
Make her do anything. Okay, you guys with the toilet talk. That's what happened
Well, first of all, so God is already first of all God he's posted pictures of poo on my my
As a profile photo on my show and then he said his poo has been green for the last two weeks
And then he's talking more about poo today. Gotty got he's really upset. He's really obsessed with it lately
He's having a hard time and you know old men. That's what they focus on
They get on that one second. That's it. They stuck on it. So right now. Yeah
When it doesn't get out their whole world revolves around it. Oh my god, God, he gets them met amuseful and
You know some fiber
Started at the suggested dose right away. Otherwise, you'll
Before they call you mr. Greenpool
This takes all about or you know what we find something else that changes the color and you can like at least they have a more
Call it like a blood blend the color. You can have you three have some uh, what they go beats. It's a lot of beats
You know be ready in green and then it'll be like Christmas in your toilet. Yeah, I think about that. Wouldn't it be great?
I don't want to see I don't want to see it guy we're not supposed to show poo on my show
I mean, there's enough shitty content as it is.
How's it going?
There's enough shitty content as it is.
That was a good one.
Please tell her to blow her nose or something.
I hate females that sound.
No, she doesn't sound like a man.
Somebody asked, why would you ask that?
Oh, we're talking about like God, he loves rim jobs or something like that. We're talking about
Was that a dream or was like
He just leans forward to start licking ass, you know, okay, why do I sound like a man my nose is not
Hi Nicole
Okay, Christine. Look. He's talking about me. It's just okay. Okay. Don't okay. Z at the real KZ God
Everyone's Christmas. Yeah, beautiful Christmas
There's actually that poufery and here's the poufery they have like their Christmas spell and you put in the guest bathroom and it's like you
Definitely in all the bathrooms
Yeah, I need to get some of that
I think spunky says you do a toad looking video
I don't mind if mine are licked. Okay. Yeah, she will it
You're her boyfriend will lick to it. She'll make a video probably like a hundred dollars. You said
Toes have your man do that make a video out of it
Yeah, I want you to lick me tonight. It's my up to my head
I want this little piggy go to go to market this little piggy to stay home some pig ever
Spooky sponky like you know what that's kind of good idea. I'm about to be the first
That's how never came out. Yeah, and nobody never did it. So you gotta have your man do that looking from your toes
They had to your toes
Well, you know, actually my tongue would probably get tired. I don't know. I was just like
I'd like from like the probably like the shoulder blade to the ear and I get tired
Yeah, when do we see you?
How about like some motivational anyone want to like
No one's gonna send a donation. I'll do it right now. I mean I need like I need like people holding dollar bills
Like you know like ready to put into my you know, and then maybe I'll go get it
donations of dollar at a time
Yeah, Christine pray for this
Everything I put this video out next thing, you know all these pictures will be all over the internet again
And it's like oh my god. It's like it was just so embarrassing the first time and guys I really
Well, you know, so I really need some motivation
Hello
Hello, are you in the toilet again?
Please don't call my chauffeur in the bathroom.
I can hear the echo.
He's totally streaming from the bathroom.
Look how green it is.
Look how fucking green it is.
Ah!
No, no, no, no!
Stop it, please, don't show me, don't show me.
Jesus, daddy.
How do you get 50 seconds? I was trying to get that 50 second one. I got a 30 second one
I don't know. But yeah, I I thought it looks like a leprechaun threw up on your profile. Okay
That was a that was a painting of a leprechaun
Oh my god
It doesn't look healthy. It doesn't look healthy. I would that was a great
Then that picture to your
Doctor cook it's cold cold cold colonists or colonoscopy. I don't know
Proctology or a gastroenterologist, okay, you have those all checked out
Then maybe maybe if it turns your skin green there
We just hear about a good deal on a
anal bleaching kit
He was trying to show us his turns
Yeah, he put he does he feels like his green shit. I mean, it's like I said I don't want to see shit and he
Came up with his profile, but then he left as soon as I screamed
So he knew better
Who plays where I draw the line you're out of here. Oh, I mean come on. We're not doing poo play
We're just you know just mentioned it
Passing okay, there you are
I mean, we didn't freak out. We were kind of like he does not look amused
No, she never does she don't like the poo play there. This is all what do you think of the poo play?
This is always. Oh, what do you think about it? This is always her face. That's always
He said keep that green shit
Yeah, don't bring that around my litter box
Yeah, let's see blood. Oh
Well, we got a doctor in the building. We got a nurse in the building. So we got a
I got medical advice for you better than see okay, okay, so freak out or so no not freak out
It's a freak off Jay and it'll be after the show, you know
No more advice is for you yee yee who's yee yee?
Hold on freak and Chris freak out Chris more vices. Oh my god. Wow. You say you sound like Michael Jackson
Um, so you can say sound like Michael Jackson. Oh my gosh. Well, that's not a bad person sound like you had a beautiful voice
He's a wonderful spot. I love when he's in the Jackson five. He's saying Ben and then he did, you know, in the 80s, saying bad and it changed, changed the meaning of the whole word bad.
It just changed on his head. Then he'd be black and white. Remember that? It don't matter if you're black or white.
That's it. That's it. What was the song that was in the free Willy movie?
Is a
We really I love you and I don't know forgot
Those the first Michael Jackson song I ever heard
What? That's unusual. Because you'd say it would be a thriller or you would have heard something.
I know. My parents are really racist and never let us listen to music.
Oh my God! Well Michael Jackson's practically white. I mean, I don't know if he qualifies.
He must have been really white by that time then. They didn't notice anyone.
Oh, you still consider him white knowing that he was a black guy?
Well, my parents were stupid so they just figured what they saw was what it was, you know?
Well, that's I mean sometimes that is but I mean sometimes it isn't like and he's the master of illusion to hold will
You please we've been flirting for years. She has been an airpods on her nose. I'm sorry
Her voice reminds me of Michael Jackson in South or there are finally catching up to the comments
Yes, hey, you sound like the Michael Jackson in South Park today. It's like he I got the official paperwork. Oh good guys
Okay, this is great news guys
official government paperwork
from the Library of Congress to the copyright of
Dance to the Mystery. Guys, are we back? Are we back? I think we have, the lecture has the copyright
We want to celebrate guys. Bring it on up, bring it on up lecture. Come on up. No, no, now. Oh, yeah
Sorry, good news on the four-hole hell, yeah
Oh my gosh, it's right in here. Oh, I don't know if I have it there. Hold on
Oh my god, the mystery I don't know what she's referring to so can somebody
The whole dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So let the terror move with the rhythm
card an open door feel the romance in every arcane lore destiny entwined as the moon begins to
Your gaze, time can steal this moment
Life's uncertain, dance we chase
With love woven, potent dance to the mystery
Oh
Yeah, that's my original DJ electric created that you know
That song and a video and that was my introduction and then one day I got
Like three copyright strikes for someone claiming that it was their video and so my channel was supposed to be shut down
And of course I just went through the appeals and was successful and now she owns the copyright
Yay, did everything and she really helped me a lot through that and a lot of other people too was a difficult time sometimes
But so you start yeah, and then it's like in my show
It's still kind of like you know
I have to end the stream and start it over but I always play the song and so everyone has to sit through like the two-minute song again
And sometimes for a minute, but it's like I love the song so it was always fun. Yeah
Yeah
And then when they started but they did not only like he was like, oh, this is my song now
It's like a copyright your host you're you belong to me and then he's like, oh, well
You know, I don't know he's like
Oh, they started playing it on their shows and say, oh, we own the song.
And they're like, they, they, they own it and stuff.
It was just kind of just to mock me.
And, you know, they're, they're just not very nice to me or a lot of people in the show.
So, oh, so he lapsed.
Okay.
Catfish, you hate everything.
I see.
So anyway, that's the little story.
But, you know, T.T.
liked to did file for the copyright.
Um, I think it's a wonderful song.
I love it.
I'm going to put it back in the lineup.
W.
T.T.
Yeah.
Song for every restart. Yeah, thank you. I don't I'm coming up. Can you?
Remove spunky. I don't like oh come on. So you know, I think you're just lying but
That's not
Electra, he's been fine
Did he does not own the copyright
Yeah
Yeah, I mean he's yeah, or you have to get naked or if you're oh, we're really 16. Oh, yeah
No, no as this one you one year old is you can uh, yeah, well you get of course you couldn't
Can you make it ill if I any future?
I know I know I was able to fight these ones with you know before before the cop before the copyright then because
Ultimately the other person has to own the copyright and prove that and they
right
Seems like a lecture. No lecture didn't block you you're
Okay, can you show us your feet? No, she's not gonna show you know
He took off his wig you when you fell asleep and he looked it by itself
He took off his wig his glasses and everything I got screenshots
How much is that?
Someone said he could earn $100 and I'll show my fee.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
I'll sell my fee for you.
For money for you.
Yeah.
put money, put money's good money.
He went, no cocked locking it out.
So who's, no, I mean, I would say 900 bucks, guys.
You would like, if I, I'll copyright strikes
just like we were doing before,
but the official paperwork is in her hands.
Yes, yes.
But good bash everyone is going yeah, everyone's going to get there another rival event good bash and good stock
There might be two events on this property. I don't know. Oh, yes. Oh, thank you so much
Electra. Thank you so much. It's all the catfish. That is cock block. Yeah
Oh catfish. Was that the person that's in Florida or is there another catfish?
I think that was ridiculous and I would split that with, of course I would split that with, uh, with Spunky.
No, no, you can keep it all, Psychic, it's all for you.
Oh, well, guys, I bet she has some gorgeous feet, you know, not in a weird way, just, you know, sometimes...
Like to see the proportion of the toes and the look at the heel and that kind of stuff
They're well kept up
There is this guy on a Emma's you know Emma. She used to be like a phone sex worker
You know, she's a psychic on YouTube. We had a falling out
But she's be a phone sex worker or she had like a she did the blast for me fetish and other fetishes
And so there and she has some weird guys show up in her chat
Because she kind of like sexy like Elvira and she was like I was her mod once and she said to the mod
She's like, oh, she's this guy named Jason in the chat. She's like
Don't be alarmed by any of it. He sounds weird. He has something called a giant's crush fetish or yeah
And she's like it means he wants he likes to imagine a minute
I mean it's as giants and then like stomping him in his like with their heel like he's a bug and stuff like that
And he gets like a huge unit. I really get off on it. So it means that be all in different strokes guys
My fetish. Well, my fetish is like probably like, you know, I like kind of like
Criminals gangsters
I like tattoos I like
I sometimes I like got the big belly sometimes they like, you know, it's just like tall guys
We're talking about and like it put are you little Emma's by your
The second I thought he appears
Okay, spunky. What do you do?
Gross, that's your gross is better. I like probably like like armpits or like stick my tongue in someone's ear
Like a man who's wearing deodorant, but then has sweat, that's a good smell. Oh
Yeah, like if they're wearing deodorant not just like, you know, nasty
What about that natural stank stank? No natural stank is not my thing. I get plenty of that at work
You can't even say my name in her chat so how are you going to report me you can't even see my name there say my name, say my name, say my name, it's blocked in her chat so.
So there and I'm also blocked in chat. So I can't even go talk to her anyway. So what do I care if you report back to
You know, it's flying monkey demon face. You're B
Okay, bye does bunkie like to smell of paint. Well, who doesn't I mean guys
Oh my god
I can't I really I mean I've tried I can't I can only bend to my belly button basically how much for the butthole
Oh a thousand in a second. He gets all that shit. Oh my god guys
We're having a fire sale
$100 you can see sponkeys feet and for a thousand the butthole
I don't want to see sponkeys feet at all
Okay, but the butthole that a thousand dollars. No, no, no
No, he doesn't like me for some reason because I woke up with like a raspy throat
She's like a really deep voice person and that's okay. That's okay
I mean, I could I could I can give you like the valley girl. No, I don't want that either
That means you fake it that means you
Sorry, I don't think this is a big type for them. Oh, you're doing it. Yeah, the beach. Oh
My god, awesome. You're actually the Californians on Saturday live. You ever see that?
Yeah, I grew up in the other coast Cocoa Beach
So I had to teach myself hot and how not to say like like a million times. It's terrible
I would rather I would rather sound like Will Ferrell in the hot tub
Yeah
Oh, you like you're into men in the hot tub. No, do you not know that you don't miss skit?
Well, he's like, did he get naked in the hot tub?
Well, I mean they're in the hot tub and
Like I'd like to have my lover. I want my lover. Is it gay is it gay?
No, it's with the woman. Look it up. Oh
Fucking awesome. It doesn't sound very interesting. Okay. I'm making order
It's really or farming right now. Get away from my aura. Get out of my aura out of it. Oh
That's not creepy at all. I pay for good times Pete though. He's a sex symbol
Guys everybody protect your auras, right? I would like to hear what you do. He sounds like underwater. Well, you know
His microphone sometimes sounds like that or a girl. What was it funny me? I don't think that was a fucking great skin. Look it up, man
I'm like totally abhorning right now, but me too. Me too guys. We're talking on buttholes and your email worked up
Okay, sweet pee. Hey sassy Sam and the after 10 minutes. Hold on. He likes her. Yeah, I don't want her for 10 minutes
He's probably quiet three five. Okay. I wait for pay for GT speed though. He's a sex and good times feet
How about for my feet? I'm a sex symbol
Let's take pictures of my feet
Not for free
What are you gonna be are you gonna be there on Sunday or what?
That's a good bash or the good or the good stock. Yeah, I have a ticket for both
I mean, I'm gonna go the boat. I'm gonna try to make it appearance. I'm there on Sunday, man
Oh, that's that I'm really set Saturday the good stock and Sunday the good bash and then there's a secret
Good goody like it's a ditty party. It's like an after-party shit
Yeah, a goodie party and
Yeah, God, please
Why my
I think your butthole, Ilya, you showed me and everybody.
All the free cake, kale, who'll be gone by Christmas.
There's free kale.
I think Tommy is going to be there, man.
Fuckin', who else is?
Tommy, yeah, Aldi's going to be there.
I'm going to be there.
Yeah, he's supposed to be there.
Is it a backstage party or a back door party?
No, he has a front stage.
He's he is he's looky. You're the only one he's invited to a you must be a type. Let me see the guy mud wrestling will be hilarious
Yes, I want to I want to join into
Yeah, I'm gonna be a KY slip-and-slide to I heard. Oh, yeah. Yes. Yes. Oh, gross
I sure with cocaine
In the KY there's pink KY with cocaine in it. You get high going on the slide
Whatever you end up is where you end up. It's all okay. It's not gay. Well, Jan's coming with me too and
Yeah, I think it's gonna be a good time in
Yeah, you'll be fine
Yeah, and you won't even you won't even know who they are but fucking rain and JT's coming
I've seen it. I've seen their I've seen photos of them. Okay. Well, then you might know
I can baby oil bouncy house. Yes, and fencing with but plugs guys
How is he putting this on like this though, no, no, I think I think he's having Aldi do it all
I think all this all these problems already doing all this shit. Yeah. Well, he said he said I'm a go fund me
You know a hundred dollars a ticket, you know, I thought he was gonna chair honestly
All the other good times good times thought like yeah, no he well
He does have a I think he does have a pee bottle, too
But I think he doesn't get up occasionally what he's going on letting anybody in his house. So I mean come on
I don't I don't know. You got three tickets. You got three tickets. I already stuck up remember. Don't lose my you're gonna
I'm not talking to you filter. Oh my gosh. It kind of has a great circle of friends and helpers
Yeah, he has a he's loved staff. I have a plus one. Yeah, guys. We're all gonna be there. I can't wait for the party bus
I'm already getting started. Oh my gosh. Yeah, he does have a great effort dude. Yeah, of course
I mean, we all love good times, of course, man. I can't believe we started it on this is like kind of like remember
Wayne's world the second one. It's like, yeah, dude. Hey vaguely
Well, you know what good times said to me this morning
He said you know what he said?
It's you're crashing up. You're crazy
This you are you're crashing out. It's not the good look and then he like
Exited my show and he was like drunk and I wasn't crashing. I was talking normally to him
He's probably gonna be doing that whenever fucking everybody's around at his fucking place on let's get real. Let's get real
Nobody nobody in the right mind even then nobody's going. They're not there's not the person that you
What are you talking about? That it's that those actual tickets being sold for this, you know that right?
I mean, have you heard of the firefest when they like took everyone to some island and said
Oh, yeah party ever and then it's like they just had a sandwich with the you know a piece of lettuce and
You know, there's no porta-potties and everyone was it was like, you know, we had to be helicoptered off the island
That's what it's okay. It's gonna be it. Why did I get a free ticket?
Because Aldi scammed everybody. He like, you know, he just took the money and he's just he's still home and uh
There's no nobody there at good times except for good times. They'll be overwhelmed by like as Joe man. Joe got a free ticket
He's on the fucking damn flyer
Yeah, but it doesn't cost. I mean David heard of it. It's called a scam
It's like they're like saying there's a party and everyone get there. Don't be one listen
We have our fucking flight tickets
Driving the party bus right now. I'll post my route and I'll pick you up a long way if you want to come
But you're being streamed from the party bus right now psyche. Oh my gosh. Hi everybody
The party bus lose so is better is it better to have the kilt on?
Yeah, and ilia are you to come in the kilt with no underwear like last time?
I'm gonna pull it up. I'm gonna chase you
I'm gonna chase ilia in the skirt and in the kilt
Yeah, okay. Here's time. Yeah, we're gonna have so much fun guys. Oh, yeah
So we gotta catch my flight. I think it's gonna go like and you were even talking about like like tattoo guys
They're gonna be that man that I'm ready for that hardcore. Yeah
a lot
Yeah, I'll stop by a biker bar and pick up a bunch of guys for your psyche
You mean for yourself
Go go to like a Mexican restaurant go to a Mexican restaurant and check out the staff there and maybe pick those guys up
I'm more than yeah
Yeah, but
Look for you really, you know, I want dude. I want to know like I wish I could talk to good times right now, man
I want to know if there's any cool what strip clubs around
We've got all you go. He has a channel. I'm sure he's gonna be streaming today
He's probably having streaming live from the festivities. And so you're gonna ask for sure
Well, yeah, I mean, but every time you come serious and stole to me
I mean, he's like you're saying on drugs or I'm you know, no last time you said that he's like pulled a gun on you or something
Yeah, I've got my say like when I said, oh, we'll see it's the house tomorrow. He's like, oh, you will and he pull up guns like oh my gosh, like
Why would you do that? That's kind of weird. Oh, he said that he was unloading one though
Did you take it like too serious? Come on
He wasn't unloading when he put them up on his test like this and then I ended the stream
He wasn't in loading anything and then he already knew because he did that on beta stream and then beta
Extract his channel and stuff like that. So oh shit. It was not to do it
I didn't know the same the same lucky day the exact same day. Yes. Yes
Well, sometimes you need to hear the in the whole story
I know yeah, I need to pay attention like a lot more than you know what I mean
Yeah, they guys pulled a Google Maps for that the location of the party and there's the pink pussy club
It looks like
Yeah, big bottoms, I don't know if that's guys or girls though
There's cafe risque there is girls I might like that one though. Yeah, we'll see
Is there anything called the bottom girls make the world go around? No, I want to bottom. Yeah
Is there a butt plug or is there a?
Really, okay. Oh, yeah, there's a rusty trombone. Maybe that's your things
Did not strike he was
Recall you know doing you know she did not she said she did not he was
The other thing is I am in route in my RV. We have an indoor outdoor shower, indoor outdoor kitchen, and it sleeps night. We got this.
You need a hose with like a good spray radius on it. So for the people that really smell it, you can shoot from far away.
I can do that with the outdoor one.
Yeah, yeah, let's do that.
It is oh dude. Yeah, man. Hey, I don't know what he's like as far as hygiene
Fucking now. We'll just pour them down. Well, I mean, can I?
Possibly come up on the RV and like take a shower. Sure. I have an indoor outdoor one. We got this. Okay, cool
Keeps diggy outdoors. Just bring them down with us. Does your toilet have a bidet? What do you mean?
No, I'm
I have a portable bidet. There we go
My bathroom has a bidet and then when I have my certain family that come over, I put the bidet in the other bathroom
I just loaded my bags in the back of the RV so we're gonna paint eyelashes on the front
Yeah, we got this we're coming. We got this
Butterflies and unicorns they face paint it on you guys like there's a face painter. There's a
Lashes on the RV
Looks to kiss on the bumper. Yes jugglers. There are
Fransexual Clowns there are
Dwarfs are gonna be there's some doors. Ilya will show his
He's gonna have dwarfs there too. Yeah
Little people
Katrina me call the king size bed in the back bedroom
Have you heard of them
The
That's awesome. They're gonna be there. Yeah, the micromanians. They're like a stripper brigade that travels across the US that are of tiny ladies
Yep. Oh my god
Why was I already able to put this together like this because we are women we got this plan, right?
Okay guys
If
Places shut down you know kind of parties of this get shut down. Where will we go? Is there a nearby?
I already go with the popo. They're good with it. They're gonna show up
She already talked about like strip clubs and shit. Yeah, I was looking all the nearby strip clubs pink
We got a cafe risque big bottoms. Okay, so what if you're not joining that the goodie party you can come to the strip club
We're just fucking jump on her fucking RV and go there. Yeah, the party bus my my party bus has a bathroom though
No shower, but there's
Well, there'd be an orgy on the party
I don't be an orgy at a party bus where everyone's invited and just enough way
I it's got a really nice black stone and it's got an indoor and an outdoor kitchen, but you know
We'll have to travel together Christine. We need your kitchen and stuff, but we need the dance floor
We'll come back and we'll come back. We'll meet the party but somewhere
We can set up camp together
We need the RV and somebody has an adult bounce house coming so we got this oh my god
machine coming to a bubble in my trailer I have one of those blow-up slides and the obstacle points.
This is the kind of shit that I like man. When everybody comes together, I love that.
We're gonna have some fun.
Yeah, it's all that's a fun. Yeah, especially when it's not like some kind of the evil evil plot, you know, it's like it's like a
Gunza like it makes it sound like it's an evil plot
Yeah, I thought that I was gonna come topless and he was just in mixing. You know, he's pulling guns out. I was like, whoa
They were water.
Yes, they were water guys.
Well, where water proved best, what bullet proved best, please, you know, I think it
was in UBC.
Look both waterproof and you know, you know, they're you can swim in them and you can like, you know, not get shot
There'll be KY on everything
He's got a bunch of slugs, so that means there are a lot of moisture in his mug that means we can play in his mug.
Can we add leeches to it? Because especially when you have leeches.
He's got no leeches.
Yes, okay, perfect.
I like mud wrestling. Mud wrestling is fun.
Wait, hold on a question, though.
Like, Psyche, did you ever see the fucking schedule?
Yeah, it's not like it's an option.
Like, I'm scheduled for Sunday. You're supposed to be scheduled for Sunday.
Oh, no, I hope I skiddle the right time I got it. I probably already
Tomorrow I'll miss my flight knowing me. I'll miss my flight. Maybe I'll have to hitchhike over there
I don't even want coming through California on the way
Hold on
Okay
Has a catered
Exactly why you need women so they can go and think I'll go first. Oh my god
Guys
Yeah, okay, you be you guys be nice to page and you better not hit on her at this party. I
Can't hit on her. I'm with a woman. No, okay. Well perfect
Right. Everybody else that doesn't have a woman
Just smile and smile and shake her hand. Okay. Hey, we're doing her nails. Not for yeah
Joe's ship. We might be too wild for the civilized party. Yeah, Joe ship. We can't come so guys won't tell Joe
He's on it, I hope he's on a movie
Yeah, it's like a great it's a meeting
Joe your video of you and Joe
Yeah, did you guys see this yet?
I have to show this.
It's the bad.
It's not bad.
Of course it's not bad.
Apparently, we started a friend's summer.
He's my friend's shoe, guys.
Hold on.
We started a trend.
Okay, we'll see.
Are we joking here?
Come on.
Jesus, I hate AI so bad you guys are weird
Who's that? Oh my god, he's getting came there. Oh my god. Oh, so yeah
Well, if you go to Flirty Diamonds, there's one of me and some.
Did you hear me?
If you go to Flirty Diamonds, there's one of me and some of me and some of me and some
of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and some
of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and some of me and
What do you guys for a secret
Government clearance and they're like
This morning when you were there
I did
It looked very I figured that because it looked very nice very steady very great
Oh my god. Yeah, it was amazing. I loved it. Thank you
That was hot
So being a patriot is being shipped via train like a zoo
Draft for her special still through plywood box. I mean
Of course she would have a train because I would
Porn apply woodmuffs. Oh, hey, I
Be patient
Can go six feet under to worst worst blow job. I've ever seen a woman
Give me a boner as a header, man. That'll be a boner killer. What you?
Yeah, oh, yeah, there's a hole in the box
Guys, he's not a giraffe. Okay. Hold on. It's almost down in the cryptic eyes. See. Oh, glory hole. It's like a glory hole
You never saw the porn
Hard to see through the whole let me see there's a psyche you never saw her porn
Yes, no, I know she has I know she's the only
I've ever seen my life that was the worst on my
Fuck it was a similar
I think he has no idea. I just watched being a patriot a couple times
But I know she's the only fan. I was gonna do is sit in a cake
And kind of she fell in the cake with dude
She like takes her index finger and her thumb and like that's it's weird what she's like
What she put her in I mean if I if I see two exclusive things you'll kick me
In a glory old
She uses her index finger and her thought yeah, he's good. He's good for to do what is she coming to the party to
Yeah, she's gonna be
Fuck I hope she's coming to apply a plywood box with a hole in it by train
It was like really why don't you grab and you know what I mean? Like it was fucking weird, dude
Like oh, it should I don't know how anybody attracted to that thing. He has claw jobs
Well, you know women have nails guys used to you imagine having guys had to trust women had it was sharp nails
So close to their balls
I mean you trust with our teeth, so get get with the times. Well, I don't trust with I don't
I don't mean just men at this point. I'm just like, you know, I
Barely trust myself. Yeah, she ignored these questions about the whole thing for six months
But then she pays so that where is this hole get a worry hole in our house to where?
And no, she went to a glory hole and did like nine guys. I think
For gay men, it must have been so does the point when there's like a vegan patriot. Oh, they do
Yeah, bro, it's a real thing go go away right now
In UK and stuff like that they're real big in UK and shit like that
Like that? Is it like this guy? Like that?
I don't know. It's in the clouds like two fingers. I don't know. She ignored these questions about the whole thing.
Okay, so I
Ask your chat, dude
Trust your chat
The chat is the chat is very conflicted about everything. Okay, watch watch be patient
No, I'm not gonna google google be patient
From that hub. I'm not going to I don't want to see that
Okay, I know but it's the truth though
Glory holds to me for for men only a closet is straight men and gay men
Was you downtown
Yeah
Downtown dead in a muffle. I wrote to Johnny. I wrote to Cox Park
We were at Cox Park. We just left about 45 minutes ago.
Cox Park.
I rode to, I rode to, I rode to a brawl, 35th from Brawl,
where he's dead down there.
I'm gonna go back down there later on and ride around.
It's dead as shit down there.
Cox Park is where the glory holds are.
It's a nice little turn out at our event.
Make sure it's done.
Let's go.
You know what I mean?
All right, I gotta figure out what I'm doing today. You guys have a good day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice day. Have a nice
That was that was free diamond. Do you recognize that?
Yeah
This is when
Summer say I'm living in my second childhood
I like cleaning up my rise including the coop right around the hood man. That's what I like to do man
They bring back memories. They go
Yeah, it's so early everybody would be out in a little bit. Yeah, I'm gonna come back down town later on fire on my eight and nine
It's the fourth man fucking everybody
I'll be down my god 30
Stuff I forget where but I'll be around there later on around eight or nine 36 and Broadway 35
Yeah, I'll be around in that area. I cool it. I was just down there. It's dead shit down. I'm gonna go back down there later
I'm not I'm not here at a loop. I don't
California shit. I've not been in there
We're from the same city
One of the realest cities in the Midwest man with the realest man
Oh man, like people though color is two sounds dodge Charger. Happy 4th. Okay, Kate
Yeah, and the American soldiers brought us the gold. I don't need any more to educate about glory holes, please
I've never been to one never been to one only one time. Okay, just one time
Giraffe has so and that's the fact giraffe has okay
Drap is really smart enough to like, you know, put it on only fans or whatever
No, she wasn't smart enough dude. You can go and Google it dude. Oh, okay
I don't want to do that. Oh, but someone I've let in my speedo video, too
It's so everybody's you know getting free free show. Here we go
Yo yo yo, oh to Jones that it's out there
What have you been I haven't been to dark rooms like talking about the dark rooms like where you like
You're they're dark enough. You have sex with people or something like that. I don't know. It's like a red room
What do you think? No, basically what I don't think yeah, I played in seven minutes in heaven. Maybe when I was, you know, I
Don't think I've been in a dark room
She was basically I mean, that's what it was
Glory hole like there's like how nine dicks lined up man. She's sucking them off. That's what happened
Well, I don't know. I've always been I'm like important or whatever, but I know that yeah
I mean I watched like you know some Howard Stern people would they come in like they she used to in 500
She has a 500 guys and so
Ten guys you saying ten guys not like I think well I've heard somebody was like 50 times more guys than that already
So it's not like that's talking
Nothing is shocking to me ever
Me neither. I'll try that. I'll try that. I'll try that
Well, you know, I do like to have some soft value sometimes six blows. She made it for the first amendment. What a patriot
Yeah, she's a vegan patriot, but it's it guys has come vegan. I don't know because it's how it's from a
You know, is it vegan? She's vegan because she's
And there were some people that are vegan and they brought vegan stuff
Right. Yeah, vegan. She's from the well
No, I was saying is like
Like is it like okay to take any meat honey like a honey just made by bees and so like yeah
I mean, I know a girl that's I mean, I don't want to
Vegan stuff, but yeah, you're going that way. I'll fucking in exactly eat
No, yeah, I don't do that doll that man
She's a vegan. You're not supposed to just swallow it. I don't think
I don't think so. I don't know
She can't she can't swallow if she's a big and that's what he's saying
Honey you can't eat honey because
I don't know
It's like, you know, they're so tired about eating honey and then they can
Drink a lot of cum. I don't understand
Go ask the police
I guess the only person you have to worry about drink a cum is you
I know
And I do like to swallow it
Vegans, don't put meat in their damn mouth
She's clearly a real vegan
She's not vegan. Okay. I don't know but she's not vegan or she is good. I'm pretty confused. She calls herself. Okay
Yeah, I know how to break the vegan thing up. Does she eat eggs? Yes or no
That's their their animal products. She's not a vegan. She's eggs. She's a little oboe. He's an oboe vegetarian or something like that
Oh, right. Yeah, or she's confused. She wrecked her fucking scooter on a goddamn fucking live, dude
The shit, you know, they can pay sure this is kind of famous vegan
Christine it was fucking hilarious. You got to look at summer
Summer or whatever. I'm I live day-to-day man fucking this woman is on a fucking scooter
She has the camera propped up viewing her and she fucking gasses it and fucking takes off
It like her hair is back. She crashes the fucking thing. It's fucking hilarious. Good. Look it up
What's her name?
Be a patriot
Be a good preacher. Okay. I'll check her out. You have to get a lot of like
She's a cute little dog. She dresses in a dress and then she like well just so let's have like the camera on there
I heard like her bed with like the cover stacks up and like the dog sleeping on it's like five hours
Well, she does her makeup and then she's like, okay
Remember when you ate that little
No, I don't remember that you'll probably find it on like trip kick or fucking Jenny is where you'll probably find that clip
Why have that when she was on law and crime for hitting someone is that a show? I want to find that I
Heard about vegan patriot actually the first time
I'm doing a big
Oh
Well, I always I always lose those right person. Oh, no, glory hole killing. Oh, hold on
Oh, the dog or running people over. Yeah, that's the first thing I saw. So there's like a video
How I found a leasing in but she was like, oh, here's how I'm gonna crazy some live streamers are and then it should be in
Patriot like her dog
And then her like her hitting somebody you're actually hitting up really on the street. She's like, are you okay?
I was like, no
We are that murder. No, it's not a real murder. Okay. We're 16, right? It's biggy 16
Yeah
That means four o'clock that's what I'm in all Sunday
So, so is this all these being there's an LDS being three o'clock or something like that
Is that his but me times you or because you're both friends? I'm not every time. No fuck. What do you mean?
You know, you know LZ his friends with his friends with JT
Oh, no, he's on I don't think he's friends with him
Okay, buddy was oh my god long crime with his long premise show. What show is that? You don't see us
It doesn't lawn order kind of it
If there's like like a real like a reality version of it, I've never heard of it
Her dog shit on the door. Yeah, she has to solve that
Dude and the dog shit in her fucking car. That was
But she has her dog in like the dumbest out the outfits like there's these dresses like right the dogs are wearing
No dresses
These fucking suits
They're like almost like humans. They're like, they're wearing so many clothes, they're wearing more clothes than her.
Like, like, she, she's pretty, she's pretty, she has a pretty sense of being a gumster.
A pregnancy, why, why, why would she do that? Was that, was that, was that behind the liquor store?
She wanted to take it right away or she just like, pulled over to a dump.
Dude, dude, her boyfriend, her boyfriend was in the worst clothes ever and the dog was in like, the best thing.
Yeah
On yourself there was somebody shitting on yourself drunk
Who was that? It was not me. It was not me I swear. No, that was Michael Bruno from TPP. He was like, oh
That would be him. Who is it? What? Michael Bruno. Michael Bruno. Michael Bruno from TPP. Oh my god.
What the fuck? Hold on, hold on, hold on. One of my favorite pictures.
What is it? What is it? It's in the show. Hold on.
You know, I don't want to show Michael. I'm not a good terms with Michael Bruno. So maybe not show it. Oh, okay
Marcy, you know
He sucks JTN. Oh, okay, hon. Andy dick coveted those rags. Well, yeah
Here's the long time video. Oh, I want to look at that later
I was gonna use his headphones psyche but for work, but they just sound muffled
Maybe it's just me. Hold on my headphones or your headphones look my voice
Okay, so they picked the story because this most voice critical to that video on her. Oh, yeah
the penguins guy
Black pill press this guy about vegan when you're bored. Okay. Happy 4th of July everyone. Yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah
Marseille this a mercy or Marseille
Marseille, Marseille, Marseille, Marseille, Marseille, Marseille, Marseille, Marseille,
I don't think it was was it those things was it. I'm not sure
Celebrate our independence day is when they signed off on it
Right. Yeah
This was this was the day after Gettysburg man
Okay, you know it was not because that was Abraham Lincoln and he was the 15th president not the first president
So you're a little bit off in your years. Who's who's off?
You having to get no July 3rd was the end of fucking Pickett's charge of Gettysburg and today
The four I got your thing now. It's independence day, right?
We are own country
Yeah, man. What would you I mean? He played the slaves, man. That was awesome. Yeah, I mean he really
I mean, I don't know. Emancipation proclamation. Yes, but free. Yep. No, it was still a very difficult time for the slave
They still were using it. I know they probably went through hell. I'm sure
Third was the pickets. Yeah, you her. Oh, you heard
Picket charge
I'm a civil war. I'm an actual civil reenactor man. Did he laugh about it?
Right Kate home imagine living in a country that any amendments that don't let them take away. Yeah
I mean, aren't they didn't like pretty much the Bill of Rights go notify Patriot Act? I thought it did. Okay. I love America
Yeah, maybe to your Merca. There's actually called
I
Forgot what have probably the name come from like I suppose a couple of Mary go just this food she but that's very
disputed. I love America, America doesn't love. I love America, the divided states.
The divided thing that we're supposed to be I love medical. I love medical. The divided states
Really funny, okay, Nicole Ilya
I
Love America. I love my bed. Yes. We're spending some American love today
Nicole. Hey everybody. How's everybody doing? Kate here? What's up? Kate? How's your night?
JT good
My I don't know. I don't hate for you. Say hello, okay?
Hey, I don't Kate
Kiss me Kate. That's a no of a Shakespeare. Tiffany. Tiffany Kate Watson. I feel like it's like a
actress
Yeah, and I love active duty sweet kitty. Yes, she is yeah
Another one do JT's supposed to be at fucking the stock man
Well, I'm gonna donate for 4th of July the festivities. I'm gonna go ahead and donate a membership guys
And you know, this is they all it goes for random person. Good luck. You know, oh, come on
What is this to be in there? There's always a commercial with everything. It's not a commercial. This is me donating
Donation how much is one membership? I'm not gonna buy it. I'm gonna cash out
$5 $75 now put two memberships one for me one for you now ziggie
Even watch the Y files anymore without a fucking commercial
It's called it's called a giveaway. Hello. It's called me donating
Okay, all right, what are you giving away memberships
You're giving away a membership. So I have the what okay, what do I have to buy? No a member
No, if you wait if you know if you want to but if you want to purchase or give to membership to match
That'd be awesome. But you mean it's we're just having a little fun right now. Okay. Okay. All right
All right, I like that. I like that freedom. That's pretty good. I think I think I think it works
Okay, I thought you meant that like I had the purchase of membership to fucking like let you have everybody
Of course not yeah, that's okay. That's cool. I like how you're doing it. Okay, I think it should come through
What I remember that feels better. Thank you. There you go. There you go home. There's one
Yeah
Okay, so did you give me one don't give me one. No, I can't decide who gets one
Okay, I'll do I'll do I'll do another one. I'll do another one. I give myself a membership
Oh, give JT one. He deserves it man
This is coming from a random there were it ran
Let's go. Let me see who got it. Let me see who got it. Winner winner. No chicken dinner.
Light of fireworks. Oh
You guys gamble. I see. I don't even gamble
Okay, so the first membership went to
I didn't say oh, but BB King Kong the second one. I don't know got the first one
But somebody did get it sometimes and this is a show up on the thing for some of you make you're making it up right now
See, I knew it. No, I'm making it up. Is it said that right? I mean it's like two or two awarded
But it's like I don't know so somebody else got somebody got it
But I've seen it because they didn't come up my first couple times I did this but then they're on my page
So like those people those people show up as like green, right?
I got the first one. Hold on. Let me check my test for it. I might have got my membership one. Oh, I got my own membership
Do they do they show up? Yes, I did. I got it. I got the membership. Oh my god
Membership that's not fair
It's okay. It's okay. No, it's not that's not fair. That's not good game. I like I like I like that
Well, I'll do a third membership since I got that one. All right. What about they what about the other three?
There's supposed to be five you said
You know, I said, I mean, I'm doing I'm doing anything just the one for one right now
But I'm gonna I'll donate one more because I got to I got the membership. Oh
BB King Kong BB King Kong you're welcome
Well, no matter that one's from psyche because it's a gift to himself. So now this one well, this is officially
Yeah
I did it
It's random is random picking is basically gives a game of chance
Okay, so a I isn't really perfected yet. Okay. Yeah, they gave psyche his own membership. That's crazy. That's why
I should be a member of my own page
So sir, I see I see that you do
So Pat I see that you do boot the non-gaze so thank you for booting me yesterday, and that is why
That is why I don't stay on panel. That is why goes you're not you're not gay though. I thought you were gay
No, we didn't have a connection. Oh, no
They say you gave my friend they say a buffalo running your ass more than once. Hey, so you're ghost can have gay good gay time
Thank you
I'm not attracted to ghosts. He looks like
He wasn't even standing up to argue man, he was just like
Okay
What do you like whenever you stream like I'll stream twice like in the beginning that was in like 2019
But then I started having a blocky fast enough for I won't get strike so I'm a little nervous from sharing shit
Yeah, like what do you think?
My second page I can share it on recordings
Yeah, person has dreams that homosexual fantasies with time
There you go, no, it's
I've never been able to find where it says you get 10 free memberships to gift like I never saw that you were I
I know what she's talking about seem to once
When I when I got my time all of a sudden YouTube premium was activated. I don't think I paid for it that month
But then it's like then it started charging. I mean
Kind of an the look dude. I'm kind of inebriated of course, but I really feel that you said five
We're gonna be gifted and then you were one
I
Know there's a couple people from last night because I did last that I get to one that a couple people like Alex
But I don't think you will now because he's mad at me Alex and I think school of Athens and a couple maybe you should be mad at Alex
I am because he's he said like our a PE and like something he's accusing someone of that and it's just like disgusting
Bro you were being peaceful, but and no offense psyche you kept kicking me and JT and everybody else over Alex
Just hope you remember that man. I think I was off several times, but I gave him off about ten times last night at least
No, but you kept us out is what I'm saying
Yeah, but I just had to have you backstage for like a minute cuz you know
You're getting like a little I have to can give two memberships. Well, I'm getting okay. Yeah, but like with me
I don't know about JT but or any of the others
But with me the more you kick me off like the more I'm going to get irate
And there's no point eventually to bring me back up because I'm just gonna start yelling
You know, I don't I don't want I don't want to yell
No, I think it'd be a nice person. We're not Alex. We're not Alex over here. We can have a civil conversation
Hey, I just want to say thank you. It's like you for letting me on happy 4th everyone
Thanks for letting me in the community. You know, I
Got kicked out of last one because you know, I just like to use create take creative words sometimes like nigger and faggot
You don't you don't put me for that
What the fuck what happened I
Can't hear you man. You you turn the thing off
No volume
Hello, hello
What happened?
Wait, now I hear something.
Wait, are you there?
So I can come back?
I think everything's alright.
What's he doing?
I don't know is a viewer something or somebody give me a phone call
It would just get past time. No, I probably got a phone call or something. Yeah
Hey, man, yo, did you go and fucking get some fucking fireworks or I'm not
Well, I'm not trying to doctor anything but are you in a place where you can get fireworks and shit
My family can I'm not making. Oh, yeah, right, right
You're gonna blast them off
I'm the big kid. That's why they call me dude. I'm a huge ass kid bro. I love fire
Never lose the dinosaur
Oh hell no, man. That's why I look good, you know
Hell yeah
What's up with psyche man, what are you doing there space area zero
Yeah, I had to reset my microphone
Yeah, we hear you
Then you can hear you I'll be right back
Okay
All right, yeah, yeah, ma'am
Yeah, I'm gonna blast off some D. Marcy pox
Persons let's go
I job whatever
Persons awesome from here for me. Yeah, she seemed like a good person
He man is a good one
Yeah, you know like he man
Oh yeah, shout out to he man shout out to he man shout out to sassy. I didn't get to finish
Yeah, oh all the mob all the mob is a fucking awesome one, dude
You know funny guy. He like oh he was wearing a skirt the other day with the wig and I was dying
I didn't know he knew that who that was
Yeah, this Jans chicken army. That's my woman. Hi, honey. I hope you're having a good day
J don't open the building. He got everybody up here the regulars mostly. Oh, J dog. Yeah. Fuck. I remember J dog
Okay, then it was JT was in here. He said
Okay, and Goddy
JT and Goddy man. Sorry, buddies
They are yeah, they're like they're really good friends, man
I got it was trying to like make psyche of like that back on stage by giving him duck lips and
Taking off his t-shirt and stuff like that. Oh, no. No, what?
Yes, that was that guy stay tuned supposedly he was rubbing his shirt in and giving him face shoes
reactions like, you know
Ah
No, I don't get involved like that man, you know
It's crazy
Like hey, if you want him up there cuz he's you know, he's turning you on in the back think I had
I'll take the reef shit
Well, I only take it crazy everybody else action for that refund out of said no, but the host said you know
I want to bring it back on you know forget. All right
Mmm, right
You go over there give him a show so I thought he was gonna come up and give him a show and when he came up
He was you know camera dawn, but then once he realized he was up he camera did off again
So I was like, you know, are you are you maybe talking about Joe too?
No, no, not Joe. Not Joe. Oh
Is he sure? Uh, right got it. Yeah
There you go. Everybody knows him as the Luigi guy. He should name himself Luigi
Do you like Joe?
He's a cool asshole. Yeah, that's kind of I'm kind of like him
It's like it's like a drunken uncle
Joe
I'm fucking love job
Like the joking uncle is Alice, you know, like look at this dick
Dude if me and Joe party man, we would have a fucking blast
And fucking up the flow come on Joe you should know
Just don't fuck up the flow cuz you know how I go you have to restart and everybody you know come on
We have an old fun. Just right right right
And Joe's a funny guy
He got some jokes that that that I was it I was typing. I'm like, oh shit. I forgot what I was gonna say
Right. Yeah. Oh, yeah
dude like man
But you're gonna go to
fucking
Good times fucking
Good stock, right? Like you're going
Over there like fuck bullets man, we're trying to kneel until I get into the house cuz Joe is gonna be there on
Sunday, I'm gonna be I'm gonna be over there on Sunday, man
That's what I said
You forgot the eye
You know
He says he loves me everybody. He loves me. Hi, Harry
I got supporters and then I got super fans and they the fans are crazy for me
For my fans that goes crazy
Jesus oh my goodness
I don't want them getting real jelly out here. No, no, I saw the
We got my friend Ziggy out here and he said he's looking for a diamond to shove
You know as a butt plug up his ass nice and smooth though. What what what are you talking about? I don't know. My name is a pool
Okay, hold on. I'm just gonna catch up on comments. Oh, thank you Tiffany
Okay
Okay, the chance of entertaining y'all I have a job. I don't need to get paid for my help. Oh
Yeah, you're awesome person. Thank you for your help through the night box
See Ziggy, this is the only account, but the only person in the world who didn't know his history. I forgot about that.
Ziggy doesn't reach chat. Where's the feather?
Someone give me unban on streamer, please. Well, why did you do that random guy? Why did you say the N word and F-A-G-G-O-C to me?
Why did you say that?
First, even the Tony tells USB stick story almost every panel appearance. Am I okay?
Easy what's wrong with me? Oh, nothing's wrong. Is it a dog the friend who gave Tony the USB stick?
Don't flatter yourself. Oh my god person note. Take any things show food for what you do does, okay?
He's on Adderall and Coke Henry says because what do you know? Okay?
Marcy, okay. He's an odd stress look answer. Yeah, they're bothering me. I'm packing up the car for a good snack now, buddy
So it's guy. Thanks for the donut. Yes. Thank you. I am banned stuff. Nicole. No love
hiding
schemes
These things happen. Oh, I know
It's like but I was reading from this book
Really good though. I can read a little bit more. Oh
Okay, let's see. Oh my
This is a great book. Let me see.
These techniques are not for you to use, okay?
Okay
This is
One strategic way to come out ahead when it comes to friends is to make sure that your friends never feel like
They can do you any justice if they ever try to quote you or talk about how you feel regardless of what
Whether or not you said exactly that, immediately get upset and correct them.
Your friends should never be able to tell you how you feel because you are complex and
clearly they don't understand you in the slightest.
So no matter how true what they say is, your job is to become bothered and tell them that
they cannot be more wrong.
So keep them on their toes.
They can build the basis for your future where you consistently correct them and their faulty
memory.
It also sets the ground for giving you the opportunity to accuse them of rejecting it
any time they paint you, unless in flattery and light.
Thank you random guy. Okay. You want to be unblocked or unblocked you from shooting? Okay?
Okay
Hold on shit
Yeah, I think I did it. Okay. I did it. Oh, thank you for the super shot. Hold on
Okay, oh hi, I'm back. Thank you guy. Hey back. You're back
Before you put me in the backstage if somebody don't need one more time. I was gonna give another
Yay, man guy
Don't want to donate another membership. I won't be a man of my words somebody else don't need a third time
That's three members. Yeah, I um psyche get ready to give somebody a membership. I'm gonna send you $5. Okay. Okay
Do it. Thank you. Oh
Thank you so much on here's the key
Everyone's back everyone's back. That's crazy like how like is my shit like slower or something like all of a sudden I hear you being like
Here comes Iggy
Yes, it's like everyone for his own reasons nobody is inspiring. Who is who's this?
How he's like everyone for his own act time you're a member don't don't discourage or
Thank you. Oh
Thank you random guy. I didn't but I think I'm blocked you. I think I'm blocked you
Hey psyche, can I can undo something very important, please? What's up?
I'm not gonna do anything crazy. I promise
If I'm sorry or you put up a photo or do something that breaks to us no not a photo
No, no, no, like the the Tiffany girl that like donated to you
Very lovely girl, whatever
I'm sorry. Yeah, she said that
That's why you did your shit is a t-shirt because you're supporting Tiffany
No, no, no, no, no, that's what I'm know. That's what I'm trying to get to. Um, I need to apologize to her. I
I love I love I love I love my woman and
I wasn't fair
with her or her husband and
Just I hope she knows that that's all
Okay, let's see who's the winner winner for the second. Um
membership for easy
Why did they come in late though, I just I want to go look at it too cuz I can't see
It's like he sent out a gift. Let's see and it's Christine. Yo, my people get it
It's good. Okay. I'll see how the psyche's doing. He's not giving nothing to my people at all
Okay, that's crazy. Both of my people got both of my donations
Yeah, I mean, you know, that's magical, of course
Oh
Guys how many how many random guy how many how many you want with the hundred? Yeah
Thank you so much. I guess
I'll live to die to see Gotti get a fucking membership
You
Thank you so much, thank you very much
And I will not forget you. Thank you. I'm never I don't that is yeah
Do something else so
What's up? What do you want to do? Like can we get rid of the
We got somebody's got to change his fucking heads up man
for real
Okay, me or hold on guys because I just want to log this show. I'll be right back guys
It's been five and a half hours re-join when I start the news stream. I'll see you in a little bit. Okay